<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Christina Aguilera (born December 18, 1980) is an American pop musician."</item>
		<item>"In September 2007 it was revealed that Christina had been blacklisted by famed celebrity photographer David LaChappelle, after he declared her too difficult to work with."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera is of Irish and Ecuadorian roots."</item>
		<item>"On January 12, 2008 Christina gave birth to son Max Liron at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles, CA. He weighs 6 lbs., 2 oz. and 20.5 inches."</item>
		<item>"Christina sought comfort in soul music to help her cope with the pain of living in an abusive household while she was growing up."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera performed with Madonna, Britney Spears, and Missy Elliot at the 2003 MTV Video Music Awards, in which she and Britney kissed Madonna."</item>
		<item>"When she was a kid, Christina sang the National Anthem at many sport games."</item>
		<item>"Christina made a cameo in the movie Shark Tale doing the voice of a jellyfish named Christina."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera donated most of her wedding gifts to charities supporting victims of Hurricane Katrina."</item>
		<item>"It was rumored that Christina had sexual relationships with both Carson Daly and Fred Durst. Both were false."</item>
		<item>"Christina was voted Sexiest Teen Idol in 2000."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera has won two MTV VMA awards: Best Video of the Year, and Best Video From A Film for the song Lady Marmalade."</item>
		<item>"Christina's religion is Roman Catholic."</item>
		<item>"Christina's songs The Right Man and Aint No Other Man were inspired by her love for her husband, Jordan."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera is featured on the cover of the September 2006 issue of Allure."</item>
		<item>"Some of Christina's hobbies are shopping, watching movies, hanging out with friends, music, dancing, and playing sports."</item>
		<item>"Some of Christina's nicknames are Chrissy, X-Tina, and Christi."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera is part of the Aldo campaign to fight against AIDS."</item>
		<item>"Christina says she wants to legally change her name to Maria Bratman. 'Maria' is her middle name and her new hubby's last name."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera has four tattoos."</item>
		<item>"Christina's favorite sports are baseball and volleyball."</item>
		<item>"Christina has a duet with Ricky Martin called, Nobody Wants to be Lonely."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera wears bright blue contact lenses, even though her eyes are already naturally blue."</item>
		<item>"Christina is known for her powerful voice and her ability to sing acapella."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera was on The Mickey Mouse Club with: Justin Timberlake, Britney Spears, Ryan Gosling, JC Chasez and Keri Russell, who are now famous."</item>
		<item>"Christina has admitted a fear of the dark before, though she also says there's a sort of comfort in it."</item>
		<item>"People who have inspired Christina Aguilera in her singing career include Julie Andrews, Etta James, Mariah Carey, and Whitney Houston."</item>
		<item>"In 1999, Time magazine called Christina Aguilera \"One of the most strikingly gifted singers to come along since Mariah Carey\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina has been featured on many soundtracks, including: Shark Tale, Mulan, The Next Best Thing, Pokemon, and Moulin Rouge."</item>
		<item>"Christina has stated that she enjoys collaborating with other musical artists and is proving it, considering she's done five or more collaborations since 2001."</item>
		<item>"Christina Aguilera has a four octave voice range."</item>
		<item>"Christina is 5 ft. 2 inches tall."</item>
		<item>"For years there were rumors of a heated rivalry between Christina and fellow pop singer Britney Spears. However, this was false and the rumor ended when they presented an award together at the MTV VMAs."</item>
		<item>"\"Aguilera\" translates into the English word \"eyrie.\" It is also spelled \"aerie.\" It is the nest of a bird of prey."</item>
		<item>"After \"Genie in a Bottle\" came out, Christina went to prom with a friend and they played her song and everyone stepped off of the dancefloor. "</item>
		<item>"After her parents' divorce, Christina lived with her mother."</item>
		<item>"As of 2006, Christina is in line for the role of burlesque stripper Tempest Storm in a new movie about her life."</item>
		<item>"At first, Christina was rejected when she auditioned for the Mickey Mouse club because of her young age (9 years old). They called her when she was 12."</item>
		<item>"Christina appeared in the musical \"The Pussycat Dolls\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina appeared on Star Search in 1988 but lost to a boy who sang \"Hey There Lonely Girl.\" However, she won money and used it to buy a portable sound system so she could perform at local parks and events."</item>
		<item>"Christina began dating now husband Jordan Bratman at least two years ago. They got married November 19, 2005."</item>
		<item>"Christina co-wrote her songs, "Infatuation" and "Loving Me 4 Me" about her relationship with ex-boyfriend, Jorge Santos."</item>
		<item>"Christina co-wrote Kelly Clarkson's hit single, \"Miss Independent\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina has a duet with Nelly called \"Tilt Ya Head Back\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina has a duet with Ricky Martin called, \"Nobody wants to be lonely\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina has admitted a fear of the dark before, though she also says there's a sort of comfort in it."</item>
		<item>"Christina has four tattoos."</item>
		<item>"Christina has said she would be interested in acting, but she wouldn't like to \"play herself\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina has stated that she enjoys collaborating with other musical artists and is proving it, considering she's done five or more collaborations since 2001."</item>
		<item>"Christina has two papillon dogs named Stinky and Chewy."</item>
		<item>"Christina has won 3 Grammy Awards (Best New Artist, Best Pop Collaboration  Vocals \"Lady Marmalade\", Best Female Pop Vocal Performance \"Beautiful\") and 1 Billboard Music Award (Female Artist of the Year)."</item>
		<item>"Christina is known for her powerful voice and her ability to sing acapella."</item>
		<item>"Christina joined forces with singer Justin Timberlake in the summer of 2003 for the Stripped/Justified Tour. The tour won for Best Tour at the Teen Choice Awards and the Rolling Stone Music Awards."</item>
		<item>"Christina loves using MAC cosmetics; she was in one of their Viva Glam ads."</item>
		<item>"Christina recorded her popular single \"Beautiful\" many times, but writer Linda Perry convinced her over time to use the first take, which was just imperfect enough to help convey the message of the song. The first take is the one featured on \"Stripped\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina says she wants to legally change her name to Maria Bratman. 'Maria' is her middle name and her new hubby's last name."</item>
		<item>"Christina starred in tv commercials for Coke, but recently did a commercial for Pepsi. It will not be shown in the U.S.. "</item>
		<item>"Christina was Blender Magazine's Woman of the Year for 2003 and Glamour Magazine's Woman of the Year for 2004."</item>
		<item>"Christina was on MMC with Justin Timberlake, Britney Spears, Ryan Gosling, JC Chasez and Keri Russell, who are now famous."</item>
		<item>"Christina wears bright blue contact lenses, even though her eyes are already naturally blue."</item>
		<item>"Christina's favorite sports are baseball and volleyball. "</item>
		<item>"Christina's first breakthrough hit was \"Genie in a Bottle,\" which came out in 1999. "</item>
		<item>"Christina's first single off her fourth album, Back To Basics, is \"Ain't No Other Man\"."</item>
		<item>"Christina's hit single \"Beautiful\" (written by Linda Perry) was originally offered to singer Pink (who worked with Christina on \"Lady Marmalade\"), who turned it down."</item>
		<item>"Christina's hit single, "What A Girl Wants", was the first #1 single of the new millennium (year 2000)."</item>
		<item>"Christina's new album is supposed to be out in early 2006. There is also a rumor about a second Spanish album."</item>
		<item>"Christina's parents divorced when she was young."</item>
		<item>"Christina's self-titled debut album has sold more than 12.1 million copies worldwide. Her highly anticipated second album, \"Stripped,\" has sold more than 8.3 million copies wordwide, according to the July 2004 \"Elle\" magazine article on Christina."</item>
		<item>"Favourite Celebrities: Johnny Depp, Julio, Ben Affleck and Enrique Iglesias "</item>
		<item>"Favourite Colours: turquoise and purple "</item>
		<item>"Favourite Disney Movies: Mulan, The Little Mermaid "</item>
		<item>"Favourite Musicians: Etta James, Madonna, Mariah Carey, Whitney Houston, Michael Jackson, Eve 6, Boyz II Men, Brian McKnight, No Doubt, Julie Andrews "</item>
		<item>"Favourite School Subjects: English and Science "</item>
		<item>"Full Name: Christina Maria Aguilera"</item>
		<item>"Goals: to be a successfull recording artist, continue in the 'business', move into acting a bit without leaving music (kind of like Whitney Houston did), learn Spanish and piano, visit South America"</item>
		<item>"Hobbies: shopping, watching movies, hanging out with friends, music, dancing, sports [baseball, etc.]"</item>
		<item>"Home Town: Wexford, Pennsylvania "</item>
		<item>"In 1988, Christina was on \"Star Search,\" but lost."</item>
		<item>"In 1998, Christina recorded the song \"Reflection\" for the Disney movie "Mulan," after sending in a recording of Whitney Houston's \"I Wanna Run To You\" in order to prove she could hit a specific note (high E above middle C). \"Reflection\" led up to Christina's record contract, and was her first music video."</item>
		<item>"In 1999, "Time" magazine called Christina \"One of the most strikingly gifted singers to come along since Mariah Carey\"."</item>
		<item>"In the Latin Grammy Awards in 2001, Christina was nominated for Record of the Year, and won Best Female Pop Vocal Album for her album Mi Reflejo."</item>
		<item>"Parents: Jim and Shelly "</item>
		<item>"Siblings: Michael, Casey, Stephanie, and Rachel."</item>
		<item>"Simon Cowell of \"American Idol\" says that Christina is probably the most talented person in pop music today."</item>
		<item>"Sports Activities: baseball, volleyball."</item>
		<item>"When Christina did the hit remake of \"Lady Marmalade\" with Lil Kim, Mya, Pink, and Missy Elliott, people said it was \"too urban\" for her."</item>
		<item>"When Christina sang at Kearney, Nebraska, she insulted them, say that they were \"Hillbillies\" for not having everything for her like eight dressing rooms, fruit that wasn't in the state, and called it a peice of crap!"</item>
		<item>"When Christina went up to get her Grammy for Best New Artist, she looked into the camera and said, "Mommy" before she was even on stage."</item>
		<item>"When she was younger, she was called "the little girl with the big voice" because she was so petite and yet could sing so well."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
