<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"No matter what a woman looks like, if she's confident, she's sexy."</item>
		<item>"One night stands are not for me. I think it's gross when you just give it up."</item>
		<item>"Some girls are just born with glitter in their veins."</item>
		<item>"Some people change when they think they're a star or something."</item>
		<item>"That's hot." </item>
		<item>"The Backstreet Boys were so ten years ago. Whatever."</item>
		<item>"The only rule is don't be boring and dress cute wherever you go. Life is too short to blend in."</item>
		<item>"The way I see it, you should live everyday like its your birthday."</item>
		<item>"There's nobody in the world like me. I think every decade has an iconic blonde, like Marilyn Monroe or Princess Diana and, right now, I'm that icon."</item>
		<item>"This is Earth. Isn't it hot?"</item>
		<item>"Wal-mart... do they like make walls there?"</item>
		<item>"What's a soup kitchen?"</item>
		<item>"When I was younger, my family would go camping and fishing on our ranches. My dad loves being around all kinds of animals. He's the one who got me to be a really big animal lover."</item>
		<item>"When Paris has to pee, Paris has to pee!"</item>
		<item>"Yes, I've kissed a lot of guys. I like to kiss, but that's it. I don't go home with anyone. I sleep with my animals, like my baby monkey, Brigitte Bardot."</item>
		<item>"You don't have to be an heiress to look like one, if you act like one then everyone will just presume you are one."</item>
		<item>"I love Africa in general South Africa and West Africa, they are both great countries."</item>
		<item>"I really don't like going out anymore. I used to love it, but now it's not fun. I'd rather have friends come over and hot have to worry about crazy people taking pictures."</item>
		<item>"I take my dog Tinkerbell seriously. I take my job seriously. But I don't take myself all that seriously."</item>
		<item>"I talk in that baby talk voice when I'm on TV, it's a put on."</item>
		<item>"I think it's important for girls to be confident. Believe in yourself and... everybody's hot."</item>
		<item>"I'd imagine my wedding as a fairy tale... huge, beautiful and white."</item>
		<item>"I'm blonde and tanned and normal-sized! I'm sweet, shy, funny, have a big heart and I'm nice - and I like to eat."</item>
		<item>"I'm not a kid anymore. And I'm excited for all the amazing things to come."</item>
		<item>"I'm the kind of person who, if I see a shooting star, I wouldn't stay there and watch it. I'd run to my friends and tell them because I would want everyone to see it too."</item>
		<item>"I'm the nicest, most loyal person in the world when it comes to my friends."</item>
		<item>"I'm very intelligent. I'm capable of doing everything put to me. I've launched a perfume and want my own hotel chain. I'm living proof blondes are not stupid."</item>
		<item>"I've made all my money on my own without my family and I work very hard."</item>
		<item>"It will work. I am a marketing genius."</item>
		<item>"It's been my dream to have four babies by 30. I look after animals, so I'd have a lot to give my kids."</item>
		<item>"It's traditional for an heiress to be raised in a sheltered way. No one thinks that's true of me, but it actually was."</item>
		<item>"Life is too short to blend in."</item>
		<item>"My kitchen looks like the one from my childhood - very homey, with a little bit of Alice in Wonderland!"</item>
		<item>"My mom decorated with lots of antiques. I never liked it when I was a little girl - I wanted to live in a modern house. But now I love it."</item>
		<item>"No matter what a woman looks like, if she's confident, she's sexy"</item>
		<item>"One night stands are not for me. I think it's gross when you just give it up."</item>
		<item>"Some girls are just born with glitter in their veins."</item>
		<item>"Some people change when they think they're a star or something."</item>
		<item>"That's hot."</item>
		<item>"The Backstreet Boys were so ten years ago. Whatever."</item>
		<item>"The only rule is don't be boring and dress cute wherever you go. Life is too short to blend in."</item>
		<item>"The way I see it, you should live everyday like its your birthday."</item>
		<item>"There's nobody in the world like me. I think every decade has an iconic blonde, like Marilyn Monroe or Princess Diana and, right now, I'm that icon."</item>
		<item>"This is Earth. Isn't it hot?"</item>
		<item>"Wal-mart... do they like make walls there?"</item>
		<item>"What's a soup kitchen?"</item>
		<item>"When I was younger, my family would go camping and fishing on our ranches. My dad loves being around all kinds of animals. He's the one who got me to be a really big animal lover."</item>
		<item>"When Paris has to pee, Paris has to pee!"</item>
		<item>"Yes, I've kissed a lot of guys. I like to kiss, but that's it. I don't go home with anyone. I sleep with my animals, like my baby monkey, Brigitte Bardot."</item>
		<item>"You don't have to be an heiress to look like one, if you act like one then everyone will just presume you are one."</item>
		<item>"Every woman should have four pets in her life. A mink in her closet, a jaguar in her garage, a tiger in her bed, and a jackass who pays for everything."</item>
		<item>"The way I see it, you should live everyday like its your birthday"</item>
		<item>"The only rule is don't be boring and dress cute wherever you go. Life is too short to blend in."</item>
		<item>"No matter what a woman looks like, if she's confident, she's sexy."</item>
		<item>"Thank you, officer. We love the police."</item>	
		<item>"I think it's important for girls to be confident. Believe in yourself and ... everybody's hot"</item>
		<item>"Wal-mart... do they like make walls there?"</item>
		<item>"King me, baby ... it's oh-so fashionable."</item>
		<item>"A true heiress is never mean to anyone - except a girl who steals your boyfriend"</item>	
		<item>"I don't really think, I just walk"</item>
		<item>"You don't have to be an heiress to look like one, if you act like one then everyone will just presume you are one."</item>
		<item>"That's hot!"</item>
		<item>"Who are you wearing?"</item>
		<item>"I'd imagine my wedding as a fairy tale... huge, beautiful and white."</item>
		<item>"It will work. I am a marketing genius."</item>
		<item>"All British people have plain names, and that works pretty well over there."</item>
		<item>"I would never speak to him again after what he did to me. After all the stuff he said about me on Howard Stern? That guy is a joke."</item>
		<item>"I do not want to make that mistake."</item>
		<item>"I loved all the Aaron Spelling shows, Beverly Hills 90210 and Models Inc. At that time, I had pet rats I was raising and I always named all the baby rats after the characters in the shows."</item>
		<item>"I like it, ... but it's yellow, and I'm like, I didn't want yellow for my engagement ring."</item>
		<item>"When Paris has to pee, Paris has to pee!"</item>
		<item>"Quote In Editing"</item>
		<item>"It's really exciting, ... I've been wanting to do this forever, and now it's finally coming together. I'm so happy."</item>
		<item>"What's a soup kitchen?"</item>
		<item>"I'd rather sit in bed and watch TV. All of my ex-boyfriends-of course, not Paris-would be like, 'What's the problem? You're so not sexual."</item>
		<item>"It's no big secret that Nicole and I are no longer friends, ... I will not go into the details of what happened. All I will say is that Nicole knows what she did, and that's all I am ever going to say about it."</item>
		<item>"Those cup-cakes still look good to me."</item>
		<item>"I'm still young and still have a very active career that I'm not prepared to give up, ... I have worked very hard to get to where I am. Paris is a great guy and we will handle this with dignity and respect."</item>
		<item>"At the end of the day what seems to be going on here is that Paris is the only victim, ... She's going to be stuck with the tab of repairing that car."</item>
		<item>"I've made all my money on my own without my family and I work very hard, ... Just listening to my father . . . So just basically following that and following my heart."</item>
		<item>"All the networks are fighting over it"</item>
		<item>"I don't want to be known as the granddaughter of the Hiltons. I want to be known as Paris"</item>
		<item>"I will see everyone back here on New Year's Eve when I officially open Club Paris in Las Vegas and Orlando on the same night! That's hot."</item>
		<item>"I'm sad to announce that I've called off my engagement. Over the last couple months I've realized that this is the right decision for me. We remain best of friends, and I'll always love him."</item>
		<item>"It's traditional for an heiress to be raised in a sheltered way. No one thinks that's true of me, but it actually was."</item>
		<item>"Las Vegas is hot, Planet Hollywood is hot and I wanted to be part of the newest, hottest resort in Las Vegas."</item>
		<item>"It's pop-rock, with some hip-hop, and there's going to be some surprises."</item>
		<item>"I'm not ready for marriage."</item>
		<item>"1 Night in Paris."</item>
		<item>"The best accessories a girl can have are her closest friends."</item>
		<item>"When people you don't even know hate you, that's when you know you're the best."</item>
		<item>"One of my heroes has always been Barbie. She may not do anything, but she always looks amazing doing it."</item>
		<item>"People think I'm stupid. But I'm smarter than most people."</item>
		<item>"I have seen the breakups between people who love each other and rush into getting married too quickly and I do not want to make that mistake."</item>
		<item>"It's disappointing that Mr. Sizemore has to use my name to sell his DVDs. He is not an acquaintance of mine nor have I ever had intimate relations with him."</item>
		<item>"I live a life that is fun to watch and I think people are interested in that."</item>
		<item>"Both her family and Fernanda Romero are from the same town in Mexico."</item>
		<item>"A mean person told me it wasn't true."</item>
		<item>"Mean people don't succeed."</item>
		<item>"I don't even know the girl. And I couldn't care less. It seems like she's the one trying to stir up a rivalry. I've never said a word about her in my life. But she seems to be spending a lot of time thinking about me."</item>
		<item>"It's been a long hard process getting this CD together. I'm really proud of the album. It's hot."</item>
		<item>"People will trash [the still unnamed album] because it's me, but once they listen, they'll be shocked. I know this is good."</item>
		<item>"We are really happy, ... We had an amazing summer together. Right now I’m finishing work and then we’ll do the wedding."</item>
		<item>"think I'm sexual in pictures and the way I dress and my whole image, but at home I'm really not like that."</item>
		<item>"Whatever I write in email, it doesn't mean anything. It is just words I write"</item>
		<item>"No one writes about my charity work, they'd rather write about me dancing on a table, which I've never done."</item>
		<item>"I'm really excited to meet you and I know tomorrow's your birthday. I just wanted to show you my house and also give you a surprise!"</item>
		<item>"My phone has become an all-in-one entertainment device and mobile games are an integral part of that. Mobile gaming is really hot right now and I'm excited to be part of this project."</item>
		<item>"We love it. We play at tournaments."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
