<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"She has been noted to often work with Alan Cumming, Cheech Marin, Mike Judge, Tony Shalhoub, and Selena Gomez TriviaDaryl Sabara. Her film credits include an appearance in the movie Spy kids 3-D."</item>
		<item>"Selena is an only child."</item>
		<item>"Selena would love to collaborate with Drew Seeley."</item>
		<item>"She only auditioned once for Wizards, but she says it took her two years to get ready for it."</item>
		<item>"She is of Mexican and Italian descent." </item>
		<item>"She took part in Disney Channel's Earth Day celebration."</item>
		<item>"She wears a purity ring that says \"True Love Waits\"."</item>
		<item>"She and best friend Demi Lovato have matching guitar pick necklaces."</item>
		<item>"Disney filmed a music video of Selena singing her version of \"Cruella De Vil\" for the bonus extras on the \"101 DalSelena Gomez Triviamatians: Platinum Edition\" DVD. The video made its TV premiere on February 10th, 2008."</item>
		<item>"Selena was featured in Disney Channel's 2007 New Year show Happy U Year."</item>
		<item>"Selena's favorite candies are Snickers and Good and Plenty."</item>
		<item>"She wears a bracelet that her co-star Jake T. Austin gave her."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite band is Fall Out Boy. Another band she likes is Paramore and she says that she would love to do a collaboration with them one day. She also likes Christina Aguilera and the Jonas Brothers."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite song to sing is Rockstar by Hannah Montana."</item>
		<item>"Selena prefers acting to singing."</item>
		<item>"Selena loves chocolate!"</item>
		<item>"Selena is in the tenth grade and her favorite school subject is science."</item>
		<item>"Selena's favorite pizza toppings are cheese, mushrooms, and jalapenos."</item>
		<item>"Ryan Gosling and Shia LaBeouf are her celebrity crushes."</item>
		<item>"Since Selena's stepfather Brian grew up in Detroit, Michigan, her family often returns to visit his relatives for vacation."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite Thanksgiving food is stuffing."</item>
		<item>"She has four dogs, one of them she named Chip."</item>
		<item>"If Selena could have any magical talent it would be to zap food when she's hungry so she could have a snack anytime."</item>
		<item>"Selena has never been to New York City but would like to go."</item>
		<item>"Selena was on the show Barney for two years."</item>
		<item>"Selena counts her young Disney co-stars as some of her best pals. She says she's friends with Miley Cyrus and Emily Osment, who she reports are \"some of the sweetest girls ever, I have their number and I text or call them all the time\"."</item>
		<item>"At 12, she traveled to Austin for a nationwide casting call for the Disney Channel."</item>
		<item>"After Barney, Gomez boSelena Gomez Triviaoked a few commercials and a small part in Spy Kids 3."</item>
		<item>"Selena's first appearance on Radio Disney was on October 26, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Selena went to Danny Jones Middle School located in Texas."</item>
		<item>"Selena received a Mickey Mouse charm necklace as a gift from Disney Channel."</item>
		<item>"Gomez got the acting bug from her mother, who did local theater in Dallas."</item>
		<item>"She attended the World Magic Awards on the 13th October 2007."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite type of shoes are Converses. She owns over 20 pairs."</item>
		<item>"She played the character of Emily Grace Garcia in the movie Brain Zapped in 2006."</item>
		<item>"She enjoys cheerleading, singing and acting."</item>
		<item>"Since Selena's stepfather Brian grew up in Detroit, Michigan, her family often returns to visit his relatives for vacation."</item>
		<item>"Selena's mother is named Mandy and her stepdad is named Brian."</item>
		<item>"Selena is a fan of Lady Sovereign."</item>
		<item>"Selena's a huge Johnny Depp fan."</item>
		<item>"Selena's show Stevie Sanchez was cancelled before it ever aired on Cablevision."</item>
		<item>"She is five feet five inches tall, has brown eyes and naturally curly black hair."</item>
		<item>"Selena is very good friends with Demi Lovato, former co-star on Barney. They met while standing next to each other in the audition line and Selena asked Demi if she wanted to color."</item>
		<item>"Selena was discovered in a nationwide casting call in her hometown of Dallas, Texas."</item>
		<item>"Selena starred in Barney as Gianna not the commonly mistaken name, Gionna."</item>
		<item>"Selena is represented by Creative Artists Agency and Jamie Freed of Nine Yards Entertainment."</item>
		<item>"Her acting career started when she was only in 5th grade as Gianna in Barney."</item>
		<item>"Selena has kissed Dylan Sprouse from the Suite Life of Zack and Cody. The episode was A Midsummer's Nightmare."</item>
		<item>"Although her show supposedly started on certain providers her show Stevie Sanchez is yet to be on cable."</item>
		<item>"Selena loves skateboarding, acting, surfing, cheerleading, dancing, and singing."</item>
		<item>"Selena's name matches Selena Gomez, a Latino singer."</item>
		<item>"Selena has said in Go Girl magazine that she would like invent Pickle Flavored Gum."</item>
		<item>"Favorite sport is Basketball."</item>
		<item>"While filming that animated movie Horton Hears a Who! (2008), she played Steve Carell's daughter but she never got to meet him."</item>
		<item>"Selena says that John Corbett, who played her father in the 2010 film Ramona and Beezus, caused her to change the way she signed autographs. She used to just write an "S" and draw a heart next to it, but Corbett looked at it and said, \"What is that?\" From then on, Selena started signing her full name."</item>	
		<item>"During the National Council of La Raza's ALMA Awards, Selena Gomez won the award for comedy for her performance in Wizards of Waverly Place."</item>
		<item>"Selena signed TI-Nspire graphing calculators for patients at City of Hope, a research center located in Duarte, California that treats cancer, diabetes and other life-threatening diseases, for use in their math and science courses."</item>
		<item>"Selena attended public school until fifth grade and she use to get into trouble for talking during class (Usually because she was trying to help other students with their tests). She prefered to sit in the back row because she didn't fit in with the popular kids that sat in the front of the class."</item>
		<item>"Selena says that the best gift a guy ever gave her was a CD of Frank Sinatra love songs."</item>	
		<item>"If Selena could have any magical talent it would be to zap food when she's hungry so she could have a snack anytime."</item>
		<item>"Selena has never been to New York City but would like to go"</item>
		<item>"Selena was on the show Barney for two years."</item>
		<item>"Selena counts her young Disney co-stars as some of her best pals. She says she's friends with Miley Cyrus and Emily Osment, who she reports are \"some of the sweetest girls ever, I have their number and I text or call them all the time\".</item>
		<item>"At 12, she traveled to Austin for a nationwide casting call for the Disney Channel."</item>
		<item>"Selena's first appearance on Radio Disney was on October 26, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Selena went to Danny Jones Middle School located in Texas."</item>
		<item>"Selena received a Mickey Mouse charm necklace as a gift from Disney Channel."</item>
		<item>"Selena Gomez got the acting bug from her mother, who did local theater in Dallas."</item>
		<item>"She attended the World Magic Awards on the 13th October 2007."</item>
		<item>"She played the character of Emily Grace Garcia in the movie Brain Zapped in 2006."</item>
		<item>"Movie premieres she has attended: Surf's Up, Harry Potter and The Order of the Phoenix, Pirates Of The Caribbean: At Worlds End, High School Musical 2, Shrek the Third, The Game Plan, and Hannah Montana: The Best Of Both World's Concert Movie."</item>
		<item>"Selena's mother is named Mandy and her stepdad is named Brian."</item>
		<item>"Selena's show Stevie Sanchez was cancelled before it ever aired on Cablevision."</item>
		<item>"She is five feet five inches tall, has brown eyes and naturally curly black hair."</item>
		<item>"Selena was discovered in a nationwide casting call in her hometown of Dallas, Texas."</item>
		<item>"Selena starred in Barney as Gianna not the commonly mistaken name, Gionna."</item>
		<item>"Selena is represented by Creative Artists Agency and Jamie Freed of Nine Yards Entertainment."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite subject is Science."</item>
		<item>"Her role model and favorite actress is Rachel McAdams."</item>
		<item>"While filming that animated movie Horton Hears a Who! (2008), she played Steve Carell’s daughter but she never got to meet him."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite band is Paramore."</item>
		<item>"Loves to sing \"Rockstar\" by Hannah Montana and anything by Paramore."</item>
		<item>"She adopted her dog named Chip from an animal shelter."</item>
		<item>"Discovered by Disney in a nation-wide casting call."</item>
		<item>"Sings the theme tune to her Disney Channel show \"Wizards of Waverly Place\" (2007)."</item>
		<item>"Her best friends are Demi Lovato and Taylor Swift."</item>
		<item>"Is an only child. Though she was bought up with lots of children."</item>
		<item>"Has four dogs – Chip, Willy, Fina and Wallace."</item>
		<item>"Is learning how to play guitar, drums and piano because she wants to be in her own band."</item>
		<item>"Her mom, Mandy Cornett, remarried in 2006 to Brian Teefey."</item>
		<item>"Her mom gave birth to her at the age of 16."</item>
		<item>"Her parents divorced when she was 5 years old."</item>
		<item>"She is named after Tejano singer Selena Quintanilla Perez."</item>
		<item>"Her name Selena means Moon in Greek."</item>
		<item>"She and best friend Demi Lovato have matching guitar pick necklaces."</item>
		<item>"Her celebrity crush is Shia LaBeouf."</item>
		<item>"Both her family and Fernanda Romero are from the same town in Mexico."</item>
		<item>"Has a YouTube show with her best friend Demi Lovato called \"The Demi and Selena Show\"."</item>
		<item>"Has a song written and sung about her on YouTube called \"Selena Gomez\" by Greg Kurka."</item>
		<item>"Selena Marie Gomez was born to Mandy Cornett and Ricardo Gomez on July 22, 1992."</item>
		<item>"She stands 5' 5" (1.65 m)."</item>
		<item>"Is from Grand Prairie, Texas."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
