<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"She has older sister called Angela and younger brother called David."</item>
		<item>"This California Girl was born on 25 October 1984."</item>
		<item>"She’s the second child of three siblings. She has an older sister and a younger brother."</item>
		<item>"She grew up in a very religious family with both parents being pastors."</item>
		<item>"Her father (Keith Hudson) was an ex- groupie in the 1960s and her mother (Mary Perry) divorced her first Zimbabwean husband because of a \"stormy\" relationship."</item>
		<item>"Katy owns a cat, creatively named Kitty Purry. "</item>
		<item>"She began singing in the church choir, she started taking singing lessons and she enrolled at the Music Academy of the West for a while, where she studied Italian Opera - all at the age of nine!"</item>
		<item>"She recorded her first album at the age of 15 under Christian record label, Red Hill. "</item>
		<item>"Performing as Katy Hudson, she released this self-titled Christian-rock album in 2001. Sadly, because of Red Hill’s closure, this album failed before she could leave any impression."</item>
		<item>"Katy says she met her boyfriend Russell Brand by throwing a bottle at him."</item>
		<item>"Katy Hudson sounded too close to actress Kate Hudson, so she became Katy Perry instead, using her mother’s maiden name."</item>
		<item>"She left home at the age of 17 to pursue her music career. She was signed by Island Def Jam Music Group and went to Los Angeles to work on a new album, which unfortunately never saw the light of day."</item>
		<item>"In 2004 she signed with Columbia Records. She almost finished an album, but then they also dropped her...poor Katy! "</item>
		<item>"In 2006, she starred in Gym Class Heroes’ music video for Cupid’s Chokehold in which she played the eventual love interest of the lead singer Travis McCoy."</item>
		<item>"In early 2007 Katy was signed by Capitol Music where she began recording songs for her official mainstream album One of The Boys, which was released in 2008."</item>
		<item>"The One of The Boys album's hit single, I Kissed a Girl was released in May 2008 and peaked at number one for seven weeks on the Billboard Hot 100."</item>
		<item>"Katy and Gym Class Heroes lead singer, Travis McCoy, dated on and off for several years until they split for good in 2009."</item>
		<item>"Katy was still dating Travis when she recorded the video for I Kissed a Girl. Travis also has a cameo in the video."</item>
		<item>"Katy has landed the role of Smurfette in the Smurfs movie, due in 2011."</item>
		<item>"Fans have taken to throwing cherry Chapstick at Katy when she performs I Kissed A Girl on stage."</item>
		<item>"Katy says she was not allowed to listen to secular music as a child, and got into trouble one day for singing Alanis Morissette's Ironic in the school playground. "</item>
		<item>"Early converts Blender Magazine named Katy as \"The Next Big Thing\" in October 2004."</item>
		<item>"Katy is releasing her own perfume named... \"Purr\"."</item>
		<item>"She appeared as herself in a 2008 episode of The Young and the Restless. "</item>
		<item>"Katy nearly caused a glitter war when she tweeted that blasphemy as entertainment was \"cheap\" – referring to Lady Gaga's Alejandro video."</item>
		<item>"She is a natural blonde."</item>
		<item>"On December 1, 2010, Perry performed at the first ever Grammy Nominations Show, which aired on CBS."</item>
		<item>"In March 2009, Perry blogged about being urinated on by a chimpanzee during a recent magazine photo shoot."</item>
		<item>"Perry was rumored to be dating Benji Madden after the couple were spotted in Las Vegas together in February of 2009, however, Perry denied the rumors in a post on her blog stating \"Oh kittens! It's two pseudo famous people sitting next to each other, doesn't mean we were bumping uglies!\"."</item>\
		<item>"Blog sites reported in late March of 2009, that Perry is dating singer Josh Groban."</item>
		<item>"On January 16, 2009, an alleged photo of Perry nude in her bathroom appeared online. Publications from the Village Voice to Idolator argued that the photo is a fake."</item>
		<item>"Katy Perry: \"I have a song out called 'I Kissed a Girl' [which features a line about cherry-flavored ChapStick]. If I want I could create a Katy Perry cherry ChapStick line...but I'm never going to hawk something that I don't believe in.\""</item>
		<item>"Katy Perry has 'Jesus' tattooed on her left wrist. \"It's always going to be a part of me,\" she told EW. \"When I'm playing, it's staring right back at me, saying, 'Remember where you came from'.\""</item>
		<item>"Whoopi Goldberg kissed Katy Perry on the lips after the singer performed on The View. \"I liked it,\" Goldberg told the audience."</item>
		<item>"Her star sign is Scorpio."</item>
		<item>"She was born in Santa Barbara, California."</item>
		<item>"Her real name is Katheryn Elizabeth Hudson."</item>
		<item>"Katy Perry admits Googling herself."</item>
		<item>"While she’s all for flirting up a storm, she’s very selective about who she’ll plant a kiss on."</item>
		<item>"Miss Perry is doing her bit for the environment and has stated on her MySpace page that while she is not a vegetarian she does drive a hybrid car."</item>
		<item>"She knows she’s lucky to achieve what she has, referring to her top 3 'rock star' moments as eating dinner with Mick Jagger, having a release party for her album, and seeing a full-body tattoo of herself on a fan’s arm."</item>
		<item>"Katy Perry: \"If you're presenting yourself with confidence, you can pull off pretty much anything.\""</item>
		<item>"Her all time favourite artists are Beach Boys, Heart, Joni Mitchell, Paul Simon, Alanis Morissette, Imogen Heap, Gwen Stefani, and Rufus Wainwright, but she maintains Queen is her biggest influence."</item>
		<item>"The girl deserves props for throwing herself face-first into a giant pink wedding style cake in front of her audience."</item>
		<item>"She knows how to entertain her fans, in the past having appeared on stage as a Christmas tree, as well as ridden a giant lipgloss!"</item>
		<item>"Katy had a continuing spat with Lily Allen for several months last year, sparked after Katy said that she was a \"skinnier version of Lily Allen\"."</item>
		<item>"Forget about a garden or a castle, Katy and Russell got married in a Indian tiger sanctuary. No joke!"</item>
		<item>"Russell also presented his bride with a ruby ring, which, according to AllieIsWired.com, \"he believes possesses protective powers.\" For the groom's gift, Katy gave him a baby elephant! (Try fitting that into a box!) Russell Brand Knew He'd Marry Katy Perry on First Date."</item>
		<item>"There were 80 guests at the wedding, but, surprisingly, Katy's (former?) BFF Rihanna was a no-show."</item>
		<item>"The night before they exchanged vows, the couple threw a Bollywood-themed bash and engaged in a traditional Mehndi ceremony where Katy's hands and feet were drawn on with henna. "</item>
		<item>"Instead of a white wedding dress, Katy opted for a gray-colored Elie Saab Haute Couture gown, which she wore with a pair of $7,000 beaded satin heels, reports People"</item>
			
	</string-array>
</resources>
	