<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Let's just say Mason is the best birth control ever! I'm definitely happy to wait a while."</item>
		<item>"My balance is really bad. I just hope my clumsiness doesn't show through."</item>
		<item>"I am Armenian, so of course I am obsessed with laser hair removal! Arms, bikini, legs, underarms... my entire body is hairless."</item>
		<item>"We met the Jonas Brothers. Nick [Jonas] is so cute ... I don't think Reggie will get mad because [Nick] is, like, 15. I really shouldn't say he's cute. It's a little inappropriate!"</item>
		<item>"He [Barack Obama] just seemed very firm about the change, and that’s, like, his motto."</item>
		<item>"I don't understand why everyone is always going on about my butt. I'm Armenian. It's normal."</item>
		<item>"t's [her new house] kind of like my relationship. I'm like nurturing it and like spending a lot of time there and making sure that everything is perfect. It's like my new boyfriend."</item>
		<item>"EWW. I'm at lunch, the woman at the table next to me is breast feeding her baby with no coverup."</item>
		<item>"I'll have surgery at some point. I'll never do my butt -- I mean how would you sit down? But I'll do my boobs for sure. I think at some point after I have kids they'll need a lift and I'll get them done."</item>
		<item>"I don't like big balls on a dog."</item>
		<item>"Leggings killed velour sweat suits! I used to only wear them until leggings came along."</item>
		<item>"It would be really sexy to have George Clooney once. I think he is so sexy!"</item>
		<item>"[After a monkey peed on her] Ashton said the monkey had pooped on him, so I didn't feel too bad, haha. Gross little monkey!"</item>
		<item>"If Paris Hilton thinks my butt looks gross, I really don't care. At least I have a butt."</item>
		<item>"For me, skinny is just a style of jeans -- not a goal."</item>
		<item>"I love to bake, especially cupcakes. I'm really good at it."</item>
		<item>"I hate when women wear the wrong foundation color. It might be the worst thing on the planet when they wear their makeup too light."</item>
		<item>"I buy myself a gift every year, so this year I bought everything I wanted."</item>
		<item>"I couldn't care less if they [the media] say I'm pregnant with twins by my brother."</item>
		<item>"I've never been a drinker, I've never gotten into drugs ... You know, I think I have such a close family ... I think you know my sisters do enough drinking to kind of fill up the whole family."</item>
		<item>"You have a better, like, looking vagina than I thought."</item>
		<item>"A few people have asked if it's real. You can grab it [her backside] if you want."</item>
		<item>"The word trill really REALLY bugs me! Like who made that up???"</item>
		<item>"She [Britney Spears] said she loves me and she loves my butt and how she wants to be my lesbian lover. I mean, what do you say to that other than 'No thanks'? Actually, maybe I would do it for a million bucks."</item>
		<item>"[When asked about going on a date with Gerard Butler] How about barf?"</item>
		<item>"Every girl who has dated a football player ... They all have sex the same way."</item>
		<item>"[About Botox injections]I think I can handle it, I have a really high tolerance for pain."</item>
		<item>"This [housewarming party] is just too much anxiety for me."</item>
		<item>"[About going blonde] They say I look like a different ethnicity, and nobody's been recognizing me."</item>
		<item>"I have to be in a relationship in order to be intimate. I'm not the one-night-stand kind of girl. Despite the rumors."</item>
		<item>"I am a huge Eminem fan and find it flattering that he would rap about me."</item>
		<item>"I urge people to learn from the mistakes of others. Please drink responsibly and it's never acceptable to drink and drive!"</item>
		<item>"It doesnt matter if you have a valentine or not just love yourself and be your own."</item>
		<item>"I love curves. Being super skinny just isnt attractive to me."</item>
		<item>"There's nothing better than getting up and going right to the gym."</item>
		<item>"I'm totally not against plastic surgery. I've tried Botox before. That's the only thing that I've done."</item>
		<item>"I swear, I would say my prayers at night hoping that I would stop developing."</item>
		<item>"I love my sisters. Kourtney is the most loyal and responsible person I know and Khloe definitely has the biggest heart."</item>
		<item>"The perfect date for me would be staying at home, making a big picnic in bed, eating Wotsits and cookies while watching cable TV."</item>
		<item>"White is actually one of my favorite colors. I have a white car. I love white."</item>
		<item>"So many people rush into it and its all pressure because they see weve been together for a while."</item>
		<item>"I think my sense of style is evolving. Im figuring out ways to be sexy without having to flaunt it."</item>
		<item>"I want to be pregnant by the time Im 30, hopefully."</item>
		<item>"When I was 17 I made these headbands, and I would sell them to stores. I would sew in these flowers with fishing line. I'd match them with everything, like with my sweater and eyeliner."</item>
		<item>"Holidays are the best. I couldn't imagine being from a small family."</item>
		<item>"[on Jessica Simpson] LEAVE HER ALONE!!! She is so drop dead gorgeous, and the fact that the media is sending this message out to young girls is mind blowing!"</item>
		<item>"The real Kim is very shy and reserved and not outspoken and loud like everybody assumes she is. [Dancing with the Stars] was the perfect opportunity to show the real Kim."</item>
		<item>"Im the girl whos too shy to dance in a nightclub maybe for one song, and then thats it."</item>
		<item>"Believe it or not, fame is not as glamorous as it seems. I think it is much harder now with all of the media outlets, and people can be pretty nasty and harsh."</item>
		<item>"My balance is really bad. I just hope my clumsiness doesnt show through."</item>
		<item>"I urge people to learn from the mistakes of others. Please drink responsibly and its never acceptable to drink and drive!"</item>
		<item>"Ive just had enough of people misrepresenting me. Get to know me and see who I am."</item>
		<item>"[on the paparazzi] You have to have fun with it, you have to be cool with it."</item>
		<item>"Theres a misconception that were all trust-fund kids and we have it so easy. If anything, I find it the complete opposite."</item>
		<item>"Im not poor; Im not desperate, I would never attempt to sell a tape. It would humiliate me and ruin my family. I dont need the money. Its humiliating; its embarrassing."</item>
		<item>"(about sex tape) Its something I feel very betrayed by, but Im not pointing any fingers."</item>
		<item>"I used to be so dependent on the guys I was in a relationship with. I don't know why, because I wasn't raised that way. If I looked at myself at 19, I would shake myself and be like, Wake up; you are way too smart for this."</item>
		<item>"I would absolutely characterize myself as ambitious."</item>
		<item>"As I've gotten older, I've learned so much from relationships. My tolerance level is so different. So after years of being in not the best relationships, you grow up."</item>
		<item>"Always thought my nose was a little big, but I guess people think that I had it done and I guess I should take it as a compliment. I am not against plastic surgery whatsoever."</item>
		<item>"If Im older and definitely after I have kids I might need to get a breast lift if that something that I might choose to do, but Im not the type of person that will ever be too afraid to admit you now, something that Ive done."</item>
		<item>"I think that people are so quick to judge, I mean just a photograph you know, and I understand everyone wants to make someone a target, but some of the people even you have put up on your site that I have never even met before."</item>
		<item>"I was always really shy so I'd never try to get a guy's attention. I always had a boyfriend."</item>
		<item>"I wanted to be a teacher. My dad was a teacher."</item>
		<item>"What my parents were telling me: know your self-worth, demand respect, and be very respectful. Treat others how you would want to be treated."</item>
		<item>"I have curves and that's never going to change, so I'd better start embracing them."</item>
		<item>"I remember crying in the bathtub. I took a washcloth, made it really hot, put it over my chest, and prayed, Please don't let them grow any bigger! They're embarrassing me!"</item>
		<item>"When it comes to jeans, always opt for styles that have stretch in them no matter what the brand."</item>
		<item>"When it comes to bags, Chanel is always a classic, but I also love Balenciaga because their styles are fun and edgy - I'll always rock those!"</item>
		<item>"I'm loving the ripped jeans look! Also, I've been embracing \"recession-ista\" style which is why I co-founded ShoeDazzle.com."</item>
		<item>"Women need to be able to stay trendy and fashion-forward without having to spend a fortune."</item>
		<item>"I used to love heavy makeup and smokier eyes, and wouldn't really try new looks. Now, I will try anything and love fresh, lighter looks."</item>
		<item>"If I'm having a casual day, I put on tinted moisturizer and some blush and I'm ready!"</item>
		<item>"I always change my shampoos and conditioners, anything from Finesse to Pantene. I also don't wash my hair every day so that it stays thick and healthy."</item>
		<item>"Im so mature now. Im a grown-up version of myself."</item>
		<item>"After watching that music video and now hating myself, I'm convinced her and Kim Kardashian have the same producer."</item>
		<item>"I wake up and just thanks the lord for my family and friends! Seriously I love life! I love all of the people who are in my life!"</item>
		<item>"I love to bake, especially cupcakes. Im really good at it."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
