<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"He maintained a 4.0 grade point average at Queen of All Saints Middle School."</item>
		<item>"He was often called by his nicknames: The King of New York, The Black Frank White, Big Poppa, Frankie Baby, and B.I."</item>
		<item>"He has a song featuring R. Kelly entitled \"F---ing You Tonight\". The first verse was re-used as the main rap verse by Notorious B.I.G. in RnB singer Ashanti's \"Unfoolish\"."</item>
		<item>"His song \"Big Poppa\" Samples \"Between The Sheets\" by The Isley Brothers. This sample was used nearly a decade later after \"Big Poppa\" for Gwen Stefani's \"Luxurious\"."</item>
		<item>"He was only alive for the release of one of his albums Ready to Die."</item>
		<item>"When he died he was signed to Puff Daddy's (now known as Diddy) label Bad Boy Records."</item>
		<item>"He apparently had 5 albums worth of songs in his head when he was killed."</item>
		<item>"He is the only singer to ever have two posthumous #1 hits with \"Hypnotize\" and \"Mo Money Mo Problems\"."</item>
		<item>"In 1993, he signed his first record deal with Uptown Records."</item>
		<item>"He is one of the first MCs ever to successfully bridge the gap between commercial and underground success."</item>
		<item>"In 1996, he shattered his leg in a car accident which forced him to use a cane for the rest of his life."</item>
		<item>"Many have dubbed him the \"King of New York\"."</item>
		<item>"He was named Lyricist of the Year by The Source magazine in 1995."</item>
		<item>"His first single was Party and Bullshit."</item>
		<item>"He attended George Westinghouse High School along with musicians Jay-Z and Busta Rhymes."</item>
		<item>"Even though he only released 2 records, he is still considered one of the best artists."</item>
		<item>"He dropped out of school when he was 17 and became a drug dealer."</item>
		<item>"He attended Westinghouse High School."</item>
		<item>"He has a father, George, and a mother, Loretta. George left the family after he was born."</item>
		<item>"He was a drug dealer in Bedford-Stuyvesant."</item>
		<item>"Birth name: Christopher George Letore Wallace "</item>
		<item>"Date of birth: 21 May 1972 "</item>
		<item>"Place of birth: Brooklyn, New York, USA "</item>
		<item>"Date of death: 9 March 1997 "</item>
		<item>"Death details: Los Angeles, California, USA. (homicide)"</item>
		<item>"Nickname: Biggie Smalls, The King of New York, The Black Frank White, Big Poppa"</item>
		<item>"Height: 6′ 3″ (1.91 m)"</item>
		<item>"He had a top 10 hit in the UK with “Mo Money, Mo Problems”, which featured Sean ‘P. Diddy’ Combs and Mase, in August 1997. His solo song was the other top 10 success he had in the UK later that year."</item>
		<item>"Mother and father are Jamaican. Has a son named Christopher and daughter named T’Yonna."</item>
		<item>"Was killed in a still-unsolved drive-by shooting. He was an MC who had released two albums before his death, plus another released posthumously."</item>
		<item>"Awarded the 1995 Billboard Magazine Award for hip-hop artist of the year."</item>
		<item>"Could not be billed officially as Biggie Smalls because someone else trademarked the name Biggy Smalls years before. Thus he became The Notorious B.I.G."</item>
		<item>"He also made a little known song with Michael Jackson, entitled \"This Time Around\"."</item>
		<item>"Married his wife 9 days after meeting her!"</item>
		<item>"Released a song called “Who Shot Ya?” just after Tupac Shakur was shot. Although Wallace insisted the song was recorded before the shooting and had nothing to do with it."</item>
		<item>"Got his nickname Biggie Smalls’ from the gangster character played by Calvin Lockhart in the film Let’s Do It Again (1975)."</item>
		<item>"Frequently referred to himself as \"Frank White\" in his raps. This name was taken from the drug lord character played by Christopher Walken in the film King of New York (1990)."</item>
		<item>"Unlike Tupac Shakur, Biggie never got a chance to star or appear in a movie, but he was confined to music videos and an early episode of New York Undercover."</item>
		<item>"He was writing a screenplay at the time of his death."</item>
		<item>"Was in fact originally good friends with Tupac Shakur. He would call Tupac, \"Duke\" and Tupac would call him \"Christopher\"."</item>
		<item>"When Tupac was shot five times and robbed by gang members linked to Biggie’s Bad Boy records, the two had a fatal falling out."</item>
		<item>"Ironically on the night he got shot, he was in California for the Soul Train Music awards, so he could promote peace between east and west."</item>
		<item>"When on stage, he got booed by the Californian crowd (a response to the Shakur murder, the previous year) and an embarrassed Biggie left the stage. He was killed hours later."</item>
		<item>"During his early years, he opened for Tupac Shakur on shows. He impressed Shakur for his ability to flow his rhymes right on the beat."</item>
		<item>"His clothing line, Brooklyn Mint, was launched in 1996. He also had plans to open a fast food chain called \"Big Poppa’s\" which was going to be served in his old neighborhood 24 hours a day."</item>
		<item>"His posthumous album, Life After Death, is certified Diamond. This means it sold more than 10 million copies."</item>
		<item>"B.I.G. stands for \"Business Instead of Game\"."</item>
		<item>"Weighs over 400 Pounds."</item>
		<item>"Was Rapping for only 2 years when signed."</item>
		<item>"Died exactly one year after George Burns."</item>
		<item>"Biggie was an A grade student before his run-in’s with the street."</item>
		<item>"There was also talk that Biggie himself wanted to become a dentist or a graphic artist."</item>
		<item>"Biggie first started gaining alot of attention as he appeared on the remix of Mary J Blige’s hit single \"Real Love\"."</item>
		<item>"Biggie had two children including one daughter and one son."</item>
		<item>"His first child was his daughter from his girlfriend ‘Jan’ in his old neighborhood. "</item>
		<item>"His second child was a boy who was born through B.I.G.’s wife Faith Evans."</item>
		<item>"Before biggie was famous, him and Tupac Shakur were good friends, Tupac would often let Biggie appear on stage with him, to help get Biggie’s talents noticed."</item>
		<item>"Notorious B.I.G. had the ability to write songs in his head and then freestyle them to make tracks right on the spot."</item>
		<item>"Biggie died with five songs in his head which he never got the opportunity to drop them for us to hear."</item>
		<item>"B.I.G.’s first DJ was 50 Grand back from his old neighborhood in BK and his other Dj was Mr. Cee who was Ol’ skool rapper Big Daddy Kane’s Dj."</item>
		<item>"Tupac also stated many times that Biggie never came to visit him in jail, and never came to give him thanks for helping him get his career in rap going."</item>
		<item>"In 1995 Biggie debuted at number five in the pop singles chart with the single \"One More Chance\", tying Michael Jackson’s \"Scream\" as the highest-debuting single of all time? "</item>
		<item>"Biggie was asked to work with the \"king of pop\" Michael Jackson on his album \"History – Past Present and Future Book 1\″ on the infamous track \"This Time Around\", were Mike even cursed on the track!"</item>
		<item>"B.I.G. made an appearance on the top rated urban show \"New York Undercover\" playing as himself on a talk show next to rapper M.C. Lyte and Sticky Fingaz."</item>
		<item>"Biggie appeared in the top rated T.V. show \"Martin\", playing as himself as an old friend of Martins looking for a backup singer for his tour."</item>
		<item>"B.I.G. is an acronym that stands for \"Books Instead of Guns.\" The acronym itself used to stand for \"Business Instead of Game\" but since his death, his foundation gave it a new meaning which now helps benefit the CWMF Inc."</item>
		<item>"Biggie was going to open a fast food chain called \"Big Poppa’s\" which would serve soul food and would be open 24 hrs a day to serve the community in which he lived in."</item>
		<item>"BiG was asked to appear in a movie with Robert De Niro and Christopher Walken and the concept of the movie was to play a role as a New York City drug lord. Unfortunately BIG never got the chance…"</item>
		<item>"In the diss track \"Hit Em Up\", which is aimed directly at Biggie Smalls and his Bad Boy crew, biggie’s arch rival Tupac claims that he had slept with Biggie’s wife, Faith Evans!"</item>
		<item>"When Tupac was first shot five times, Biggie and his fellow Bad Boy Records artist, were upstairs in the same hotel the shooting took place in. "</item>
		<item>"After Tupac was shot, he dragged himself into an elevator and got out on the floor biggie was on."</item>
		<item>"Tupac said he recieved no help from BIG, and the look on biggie’s face was one of suprise, as if Biggie was shocked to see Tupac alive. To the day of his death Tupac believed Biggie was invloved in the shooting in some way or another."</item>
		<item>"At the height of Biggies beef with Tupac Shakur, Biggie put out a track called \"Who Shot Ya?\" which is thought to be a reply to the many diss tracks Tupac was hitting at Biggie , such as \"Hit Em Up\"."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
