<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Robert Pattinson was born on May 13, 1986, in London, England."</item>
		<item>"He enjoys music and is an excellent musician, playing both the guitar and piano."</item>
		<item>"When Robert was 15, he started acting in amateur plays with the Barnes Theatre Company."</item>
		<item>"He took screen role like Curse of the Ring (2004) (TV) (Kingdom of Twilight) as Giselher."</item>
		<item>"In 2003, Robert took on the role of Cedric Diggory in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (2005)." </item>
		<item>"He is 6' 1" (1.85 m) tall. "</item>
		<item>"He began taking piano lessons at age three, and classical guitar at five."</item>
		<item>"Attended Harrodian private school in London."”</item>
		<item>"He has two older sisters, Lizzie and Victoria."</item>
		<item>"Remains close friends with Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (2005) co-stars, Stanislav Ianevski and Katie Leung."</item>
		<item>"Was taught how to scuba dive for his role in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (2005)."</item>
		<item>"Has said that darts and pool are more his sport, and that he made up that he liked snowboarding and soccer for his Harry Potter audition."</item>
		<item>"Robert admires Jack Nicholson."</item>
		<item>"Was ranked #23 on Moviefone's "The 25 Hottest Actors Under 25" (2008)."</item>
		<item>"Chosen by the Hollywood Film Festival Award Committee as the recipient of the 2008 New Hollywood Award."</item>
		<item>"Awarded Best Actor 2008 at the Strasbourg Film festival for his performance as "Art" in the film How to Be (2008)."</item>
		<item>"One sister, Lizzy, 25, had a top ten hit with the band Aurora. The other, Victoria, 27, works in advertising."</item>
		<item>"Most of his earnings from his first acting job - a supporting role in the television film Curse of the Ring (2004) (TV) - went on paying his own fees at The Harrodian School in Barnes."</item>
		<item>"He beat 3,000 people to play Edward Cullen in the movie Twilight (2008/I)."</item>
		<item>"Named as Yahoo's Top Movie Heart Throb of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Named as Rolling Stone Magazine's Hottest Actor of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Named by "Entertainment Tonight" (1981) (ET) as their top hunk of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Named as one of the LA Times Breakout Stars of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Named as one of Forbes Breakout Stars of 2008."</item>
		<item>"His small, but would-have-been-memorable part in Vanity Fair (2004), was cut out in the final production."</item>
		<item>"Awarded Hello Magazine's Most Attractive Man Award of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Invited an obsessive fan out for dinner when he was having a bad day."</item>
		<item>"Father is a car salesman."</item>
		<item>"Supports Arsenal Football Club."</item>
		<item>"Splits his time residing between London, UK where his family is from and Los Angeles, CA."</item>
		<item>"One of People Magazine's Sexiest Men Alive 2008."</item>
		<item>"Moviefone's Number 1 Hottest Young Star Under 25 2009."</item>
		<item>"Sarah Barry Williams wrote song \"She wants to be Mrs Robert Pattinson\"."</item>
		<item>"Named AOL Moviefone's Sexiest Male Star of 2009."</item>
		<item>"Named GQ (UK) Best Dressed Man of 2009. \"Extremely elegant and inspiring, the true essence of a contemporary man.\" Domenico Dolce and Stefano Gabbana, designers."</item>
		<item>"Learned to drive in a ten hour crash course on the set of Twilight."</item>
		<item>"Merited a place in Time magazine's - The 100 Most Influential People in the World (\"Artists\" category) - with a tribute provided by Chris Weitz. [May 10, 2010]"</item>
		<item>"A distant relative of Vlad the Impaler who Bram Stoker's Dracula was based on. This is an coincidence because Rob plays Edward Cullen a 100 plus year old Vampire in the Twilight Saga."</item>
		<item>"Very private about his personal life. In 2010, many main stream media outlets began referring to his relationship with Twilight Co-star Kristen Stewart as matter of fact instead of rumored."</item>
		<item>"Adopted a puppy from a shelter in 2011 in Louisiana where he was living while filming The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn. He named his new friend Bear."</item>
		<item>"His nickname is Rob."</item>
		<item>"Robert lived with his best friend for a year, in a apartment with just one chair, a TV and homemade furniture."</item>
		<item>"Robert was called up by the assistant director for Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, who told him they'd be putting him on a personal training programme."</item>
		<item>"Despite being slated to star in the stage production of The Woman Before in May 2005, Robert got fired shortly before the opening night."</item>
		<item>"Robert auditioned for a chorus part in a production of Guys and Dolls, as a Cuban dancer, which he successfully got."</item>
		<item>"When Robert was at the age of six (6), he began starring in numerous school productions including Spell for a Rhyme and William Golding's cult classic, The Lord of the Flies."</item>
		<item>"Robert was nicknamed 'Patty' as a child because of his surname. It's now the name of his dog!"</item>
		<item>"Robert's first school was Tower House School, which is an all-boys school in Barnes."</item>
		<item>"Girl's fashion trend, Ugg Boots, leaves Robert confused."</item>
		<item>"Robert began modeling when he was twelve years old. His modeling career ended four years later when he was stopped being offered jobs."</item>
		<item>"It has been often reported that Robert doesn't wash his hair."</item>
		<item>"Robert has performed two songs in the soundtrack for the movie Twilight called Never Think which he co-wrote with Sam Bradley and Let Me Sign."</item>
		<item>"Robert loves drinking diet coke. His favourite cereal is Cinnamon Toast Crunch."</item>
		<item>"According to Robert, he has a terrible memory."</item>
		<item>"Robert worked on his first big movie, Kingdom in Twilight, at 17 years of age. It was the first time he went away from home and he was in South Africa by himself for three and a half months."</item>	
		<item>"At the age of twelve (12), Robert moved to the Harrodian School, which is a mixed private school in southwest London."</item>
		<item>"Robert says his worst habit is speaking too much."</item>
		<item>"Robert loves to watch American Idol and X Factor."</item>
		<item>"Robert's first kiss was at the age of 12."</item>	
		<item>"Robert's celebrity crush is Kristen Stewart, his Twilight co-star."</item>
		<item>"Robert was once in a band called 'The Bad Girls' and has also developed himself as a solo artist, performing under the stage name of Bobby Dupea."</item>
		<item>"Willow is one of Robert's favorite films. He was a little star-struck when he met Warwick Davis on the set of Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, since Davis starred in Willow."</item>
		<item>"Robert describes himself as \"immature\"."</item>
		<item>"Robert hadn't read any of the Harry Potter books before he landed the role of Cedric; however, he caught up after he was cast! He read the novel version of the movie in two days flat after that."</item>
		<item>"Robert enjoys rap, and likes Eminem. He likes old blues music, listening to John Lee Hooker and Elmore James."</item>
		<item>"Robert got himself a paper route when he was ten years old. He earned £10 a week for his troubles."</item>


	</string-array>
</resources>
