<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Adele was born in Tottenham, London, to a single teenage mother on 5 May 1988."</item>
		<item>"At the 2009 Grammy Awards, Adele won the awards for Best New Artist and Best Female Pop Vocal Performance."</item>
		<item>"Her birth name is Adele Laurie Blue Adkins."</item>
		<item>"Adele attracted the attention of XL Recordings with a three-song demo posted on MySpace and then signed with the label."</item>
		<item>"\"19\"album debuted at number one, and has been certified four times platinum in the UK." </item>
		<item>"Her career in the US was boosted by a viewer record–breaking Saturday Night Live episode in late 2008."</item>
		<item>"Adele released her second album 21 on 24 January 2011 in the UK, and 22 February in the US."</item>
		<item>"The album 21 debuted at number one on the Billboard 200 in the US, selling 352,000 copies in its first week."”</item>
		<item>"21 has charted at number one in 17 European countries and the US."</item>
		<item>"After performing at the 2011 BRIT Awards, the album track \"Someone Like You\" reached number one in the United Kingdom, while the album also remained at number one."</item>
		<item>"The Official Charts Company announced that Adele is the first living artist to achieve the feat of two top five hits in both the Official Singles Chart and the Official Albums Chart simultaneously since The Beatles in 1964."</item>
		<item>"21 has spent eleven consecutive weeks at number one in the UK, the longest ever by a female solo artist on the UK Albums Chart, surpassing Madonna's nine weeks at number one in 1990 with her greatest hits compilation."</item>
		<item>"The album 21 has  broken the record for the most UK digital downloads."</item>
		<item>"She began singing at age four and asserts that she became obsessed with voices."</item>
		<item>"Adele has cited the Spice Girls as a major influence in regard to her love and passion for music, stating that \"they made me what I am today\"."</item>
		<item>"Adele would impersonate the Spice Girls at dinner parties as a young girl."</item>
		<item>"To make her look like singer Gabrielle, her mother made an eye patch with sequins, which Adele said was embarrassing."</item>
		<item>"At the age of 11, Adele and her mother, a furniture-maker and adult learning activities organiser moved to West Norwood, South London."</item>
		<item>"West Norwood is the subject for Adele's first record, \"Hometown Glory\", written when she was 16."</item>
		<item>"After moving to South London, she became interested in RnB artists such as Destiny's Child and Mary J Blige."</item>
		<item>"Adele graduated from The BRIT School for Performing Arts and Technology in Croydon in May 2006."</item>
		<item>"She was classmates with Leona Lewis and Jessie J."</item>
		<item>"In school, she was more interested in going into AnR, and hoped to launch other people's careers."</item>
		<item>"She had recorded a three-song demo for a class project and gave it to a friend who posted it on Myspace where it became very successful and led to a phone call from music label XL Recordings."</item>
		<item>"Adele's breakthrough song, \"Hometown Glory\", was released in October 2007."</item>
		<item>"Two of his other albums – Bad and Dangerous – are also among the world’s best-selling records."</item>
		<item>"Adele supported Will Young at the 2007 MENCAP Little Noise Sessions, a charity concert at London's Union Chapel."</item>
		<item>"In 2008 she was the headliner and performed a stripped down acoustic that was supported by Damien Rice."</item>
		<item>"In July 2008, Adele paid £8,000 for a commissioned painting by Stella Vine in a charity auction in aid of Keep a Child Alive, a charity that helps African children and their families living with HIV/AIDS."</item>
		<item>"Adele said she planned to ask Vine to paint a portrait of "my mum and me."</item>
		<item>"She has described her musical style as \"heartbroken soul\"."</item>
		<item>"Adele, comparing herself to Winehouse and Duffy, said \"I think Amy is hardcore,\" \"I think Duffy is really soft – she's got the pin-up look going on\"."</item>
		<item>"American singer Beyonce cited Adele as an influence for her upcoming album."</item>
		<item>"\"Her song "Daydreamer\" is about her bi ex-boyfriend running away with another man. "</item>
		<item>"A Guardian journalist reports that the album 21 has sold 1,754,319 copies in the UK in 69 days. That's 25,425 per day, 1,059 per hour and 18 copies per minute."</item>
		<item>"Adele's ship-worker father did not have a hand in raising her. "</item>
		<item>"Her mom worked as a masseuse and made furniture to make ends meet."</item>
		<item>"Adele's mother was only 18 when she was born."</item>
		<item>"As a youngster, Adele would sing for her family and her mother's friends at dinner parties,"</item>
		<item>"Adele's interest in singing carried over into school when she gave her first performance at a school event."</item>
		<item>"Into her teenage years, Adele discovered the soulful sounds of Ella Fitzgerald and Etta James by accident (when perusing CD covers for hairstyles) and became swept away by their musical style."</item>
		<item>"Adele's MySpace page, which launched in 2004, has been visited by thousands, and her experience playing at British pubs showed the locals that this young songstress was for real."</item>
		<item>"Adele has also performed with Paul McCartney and Bjork on TV, been given special mentions on Kanye West's official blog and been praised publicly by Beyonce."</item>
		<item>"Her weight bother her directly."</item>
		<item>"Many of Adele's songs are based on her past relationships."</item>
		<item>"Some of Adele's fateful relationships include an ex who subsequently cheated on her and a bisexual buddy (whom she fancied) who hooked up with one of her gay friends instead."</item>
		<item>"When she's performing she can't help but start chattering - a trait she says she inherited from her grandmother. "</item>
		<item>"Before concerts he would drink Ricola candy dissolved in hot water."</item>
		<item>"Her dad, Mark Evans, regrets becoming estranged from his daughter after he started abusing alcohol ten years ago, and admits he still can't bear to see her perform on stage. "</item>
		<item>"Adele was told by her teachers she would never be a success."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
