<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>Rihanna was ranked #78 on Notarized: Top 100 Videos of 2007 for her music video featuring Ne-Yo \"Hate That I Love You\".</item>
		<item>At the 2007 American Music Awards, Rihanna was chosen as the Favorite Female Artist for SoulR&amp;B category.</item>
		<item>In the 2007 Teen Choice Awards, Rihanna won in the category \"Choice Music: R&amp;B Artist\".</item>
		<item>"Rihanna ranked #8 in Maxim's 2007 Hot 100 List."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is tutored 15 hours a week."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's biggest pet peeve is when people are dishonest."</item>
		<item>"She preformed Mariah Carey's \"Hero\" in a school talent show."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is very picky when it comes to food. She won't eat Mexican, Chinese, Japanese, or Indian food. She also hates vegetables."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is the official sponsor for the Barbados Tourism Agency."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's nickname is RiRi."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna says she had much more control over her new album \"Good Girl Gone Bad\" than she did in \"A Girl Like Me\"."</item>
		<item>"She is of African, Creole and Guyanese descent."</item>
		<item>"Unfaithful is based on a relationship Rihanna had when she was 14-years-old. Her relationship \"was not physical\" though."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is the eldest sibling to her two younger brothers named Rorrey and Rajad."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna dislikes dishonest people. She prefers people to be honest and loyal."</item>
		<item>"Her mother, Monica, is an accountant."</item>
		<item>"She was in cadets approximately for 5 years."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna loves to put color on her nails, and changes weekly!"</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is a Covergirl."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna said that her favourite song is \"I'm Losing It\" by	Roc City. But the best song of 2009 is \"State of Mind\" by Jay-Z and Alicia Keys."</item>
		<item>"Plans to learn to play the acoustic guitar, or the keyboard or piano."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna had a cameo role in Bring It On: All or Nothing (2006). She has been offered numerous film roles but has been waiting to choose one of them."</item>
		<item>"In 2006, Rihanna landed several endorsement deals, including	ones for Nike and J.C. Penney."</item>
		<item>"She was discovered by music producer Evan Rogers while he was vacationing in Barbados, with his wife."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's celebrity crush would be \"Chester\" from \"Linkin	Park\", \"Trey Songz\" or \"Justin Bieber\"."</item>
		<item>"Robyn Rihanna Fenty was born February 20, 1988."</item>
		<item>"Born in Saint Michael, Barbados, Rihanna moved to the United States at the age of 16 to pursue a recording career under the guidance of record producer Evan Rogers."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna has sold more than 15 million albums and 45 million singles worldwide."</item>
		<item>"One of Rihanna's major influences and idols is Mariah Carey."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's music contains strong influences of caribbean music which include reggae and dancehall."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna created her Believe Foundation in 2006 to help terminally ill children."</item>
		<item>"She holds the honorary title of Ambassador for Culture and Youth in Barbados."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna considers Madonna as one of her idols and biggest influences."</item>
		<item>"She was named \"International Female Artist of the Year\" at the 2010 NRJ Music Awards."</item>
		<item>"As of July 23, 2010, Rihanna has sold approximately 5,563,000 album units in the US."</item>
		<item>"Plans to study Business and Psychology."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna‚Äôs most famous song \"Umbrella\" stayed on the UK chart for 10 weeks in 2007. "</item>
		<item>"When Rihanna was about 13 or 14, she snuck out to a club."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is a BIG prankster. She can do anything from pushing	you into a waterfall or fool you!"</item>
		<item>"She is a Tattoo enthusiast and has over 11 tattoos."</item>
		<item>"Her horoscope sign is Pisces"</item>
		<item>"Her favourite actors are Terrence Howard and Denzel Washington."</item>
		<item>"Her favourite actresses are Jessica Alba and Halle Berry."</item>
		<item>"Her favourite TV show is Entourage."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's first number one hit was \"S.O.S (Rescue Me)\"."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna's favourite place in Barbados is The Boatyard Club."</item>
		<item>"Her pets are a turtle, dog named Marley, and DJ."</item>
		<item>"Psychology was Rihanna back up plan incase singing didn't work out for her."</item>
		<item>"Tattoos who hurted the most are on her fingers. \"Love\" on her left hand, and \"Shhh...\" on her right."</item>
		<item>"During Rihanna's audition for Jay-Z in New York, Rihanna	performed the songs \"The Last Time\", \"Pon De Replay\" and Whitney Houston's version of \"For The Love of You\"."</item>
		<item>"\"Umbrella\" won numerous of awards, and one of them was a grammy!"</item>
		<item>"Won the Miss Combermere school pageant in 2004."</item>
		<item>"She was discovered by music producer Evan Rogers while he was vacationing in Barbados, with his wife"</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is the eldest sibling to her two younger brothers; named Rorrey and Rajad."</item>
		<item>"Several other major labels were vying for Rihanna, but Def-Jam made such an amazing deal that,the scheduled meetings with the other companies were canceled."</item>
		<item>"\“Pon De Replay\” was heard on HBO’s hit TV show ‘Entourage’ in the ‘An Offer Refused’ episode during the club scene."</item>
		<item>"Jay Z was skeptical about Rihanna initially. Brown played him the record that’s turned out to be her first single, \“Pon De Replay,\” and Hova was nervous about it."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna’s \“Music of the Sun\” album was be produced by Vada Nobles (\“The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill\”)."</item>
		<item>"While growing up in Barbados Rihanna visited the beach everyday with her two brothers."</item>
		<item>"Fatima Robinson choreographed Rihanna’s videos’ for both Pon De Replay and If It’s Lovin."</item>
		<item>"Keeps in contact with her Bajan best friends Leandra and Melissa. Melissa travels with Rihanna whereever she goes."</item>
		<item>"Plans to learn to play the acoustic guitar, or the keyboard or piano."</item>
		<item>"Her show at Foxwoods marks her first visit to a casino."</item>
		<item>"Was in cadets approximately for 5 years. The famous singer \“Shontelle\” [also from Barbados] was there aswell."</item>
		<item>"Plans to study Business and Psychology."</item>
		<item>"Her father, Ronald, supervises at a garment factory."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna has 13 tattoos, which she never planned to get. \“I wake up and feel like, I have to get a tattoo\”. Those who hurted the most are on her fingers. \“Love\” on her left hand, and \“Shhh…\” on her right."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna loves to put color on her nails, and changes weekly!"</item>
		<item>"Rihanna’s accent is Bajan. When she was asked on the tv show \“Friday Night With Jonathan Ross\” about her accent she said \“I can’t help it\” with a cute smile."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna made a cameo appearance in the 2006 cheerleading romp, Bring It On: All or Nothing."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna is a pisces, which means she is creative, sensitive, and kind, but prone to melancholy. "</item>
		<item>"Her first name is Robyn and her nickname is RiRi."</item>
		<item>"Was in relationship with baseball player Matt Kemp."</item>
		<item>"In February 2008, Rihanna joined forces with HnM and Designers Against AIDS (DAA) to promote the global campaign, Fashion Against AIDS. It works to raise awareness about the disease and combine fashion with the message of safe sex."</item>
		<item>"She won't eat Mexican, Chinese, Japanese, or Indian food. She also hates her vegetables. Rihanna claims to stick mostly to local fruits and water to keep healthy."</item>
		<item>"In February 2008, Barbados created a national holiday to honor Rihanna. She accepted the honor and as a thank you she put on a free concert for her fans."</item>
		<item>"When she was just a kid, Rihanna's mother was a professional make-up artist but wouldn’t allow her daughter to use beauty products. Rihanna grew up and became the face for CoverGirl cosmetics."</item>
		<item>"Her first hit was \"Pon de Replay\" off her debut album Music of the Sun. It peaked at Number 2 on Billboard’s Hot 100. She toured with Gwen Stefani to promote that album."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna banned fans from bringing umbrellas to her U.K. concerts. She was afraid people would get injured if fans tried to copy her dance moves with the umbrellas when she performed Umbrella."</item>
		<item>"Her other favorite singers are Mariah Carey, Whitney Houston and Alicia Keys."</item>
		<item>"Her success was falsely rumored to be in thanks to a romantic involvement with Jay-Z. Then he was dating, and is now married to Beyonce, one of Rihanna’s favorite singers."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #43 in the 2010 FHM UK list of \"100 Sexiest Women in the World\"."</item>
		<item>"At the 2011 BET awards, Rihanna was mistakenly announced as the winner of the Viewer's Choice Award. The actual winner was her ex-boyfriend Chris Brown, who later received the award."</item>
		<item>"The song SnM featuring Britney Spears become her 10th No. 1 song on Billboard Hot 100."</item>
		<item>"Became the youngest black female to grace the cover of American-Vogue [March 2011]."</item>
		<item>"Q Magazine named her one of the top 100 acts of the last century. [November 2009]."</item>
		<item>"As of March 1st, she's reached over 1.2 billion YouTube views on her official Vevo page."</item>
		<item>"Her controversial music video for "SnM", was banned in 11 countries within a day of it's release. This is Rihanna's second video to cause controversy as \"Te Amo\" was banned in many countries due to its same-sex nature."</item>
		<item>"Is worth an estimated $143 million. [Forbes Febuary 2011]."</item>
		<item>"Billboard named Rihanna the Digital Songs Artist of the 2000s decade."</item>
		<item>"Her 5th studio album 'Loud', sold 2.8 million copies worldwide in 3 months. The album also marks the launch of her business \"Rihanna Entertainment\"[Febuary 2011]."</item>
		<item>"She has Seven number one singles in Australia as of Febuary 2011, making her the only non Australian artist to do so in the last 20 years."</item>
		<item>"In the UK, she became the only female; and the only artist in 52 years to have three top ten songs at once on the 'UK Official Chart'"</item>
		<item>"Has attained nine number one Hot 100 singles. Three of them were achieved in 2010. She become the only female in American history to have her first single to go number one after the second. [Febuary 2011]."</item>
		<item>"Broke her own record by scoring her 7th US number one. \"Love The Way You Lie\" with Eminem became her 7th number one single in 5 years. This gives her the most number ones from an artist in the last 10 years."</item>
		<item>"Selling 62 million records since 2005, she's the most successful artist over the last decade. She also is the first ever artist ever to have 5, 3X platinum selling digital singles."</item>
		<item>"Is a big fan of Depeche Mode, The Prodigy and Chase and Status. She worked with Chase and Status on her album \"Rated R\" after calling member Saul Milton up at 3 AM."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
