<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Everybody can tell you how to do it, they never did it."</item>
		<item>"Only time they excited is when they mentioning Shawn."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather die enormous than live dormant."</item>
		<item>"I'm far from being God, but I work God damn hard."</item>
		<item>"The average rap life is two or three albums. You're lucky to get to your second album in rap!"</item>
		<item>"They say a midget standing on a giant's shoulders can see much further than the giant. So I got the whole rap world on my shoulders, they trying to see further than I am."</item>
		<item>"He who does not feel me is not real to me, Therefore he doesn't exist. So, poof... vamoose, son of a bitch."</item>
		<item>"I'm not a 'Business-Man'! I'm a Business... man! Let me handle my business, damn!"</item>
		<item>"I'd rather die enormous than live dormant."</item>
		<item>"No matter where you go, you are what you are playa."</item>
		<item>"When the grass is cut, the snakes will show."</item>
		<item>"He who does not feel me is not real to me, therefore he does not exist. So, poof... vamoose, son of a bitch."</item>
		<item>"Make these words find a spot on your brain and burn."</item>
		<item>"You haven't heard stress until you heard the cries of my mama."</item>
		<item>"Niggas is hotheads and the bullets is heat seeking."</item>
		<item>"Pussy is one of the most powerful things in the world, and a lot of people don't understand how powerful pussy is."</item>
		<item>"Said she liked my necklace, started relaxin - now that's what the fuck i call a chain reaction."</item>
		<item>"Ma, cry me a river, build a bridge, and GET OVER IT!"</item>
		<item>"I've got an appetite for destruction - but i scrape the plate."</item>
		<item>"This is food for thought, u do the dishes!"</item>
		<item>"What you eat dont make me shit."</item>
		<item>"Being broke is childish and i'm quite grown."</item>
		<item>"Couldn't sit down, big gun kept stickin' my pelvis Shit, it was either that or be living with Elvis."</item>
		<item>"Niggas wanna hijack the flyness."</item>
		<item>"Different toilet, SAME SHIT, and i'm sick of explaing this.."</item>
		<item>"Swear to everything when i leave this earth gonna be on both feet, never knees in the dirt - lucky me."</item>
		<item>"They say a midget standing on a giant's shoulders can see much further than the giant. So I got the whole rap world on my shoulders, they trying to see further than I am."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather die enormous than live dormant."</item>
		<item>"Can I live?"</item>
		<item>"I will not lose, for even in defeat, there's a valuable lesson learned, so it evens up for me."</item>
		<item>"If you dont gimme heaven i'll raise hell.. 'till its heaven."</item>
		<item>"How you get so fly? From not being afraid to fall out the sky."</item>
		<item>"Ain't nothin' wrong with the aim, just gotta change the target."</item>
		<item>"If ya'll can't already see I ain't worried about ya'll cause I'm already me."</item>
		<item>"Lord forgive me I never would've made it without sin."</item>
		<item>"Middle finger to the law, nigga grippin' my balls."</item>
		<item>"Remind yourself. Nobody built like you, you design yourself."</item>
		<item>"Life is for living. Not living uptight."</item>
		<item>"Sisters hold you down, bitches hold you up. Sisters help you progress, bitches'll slow you up."</item>
		<item>"You ain't seen money in your life, when it comes to this cheese ya'll like three blind mice."</item>
		<item>"When you first come in the game, they try to play you. Then you drop a couple of hits, look how they wave to you"</item>
		<item>"No one on the corner gotta bop like this, can't wear skinny jeans cause my knots don't fit"</item>
		<item>"Lets get faded, Le Meurice for like 6 days. Gold bottles, scold models, Spillin Ace on my sick Js."</item>
		<item>"Yall dont know that dont sh*t phase me. The Nets could go 0-82 and I look at you like this sh*t gravy."</item>
		<item>"Whats 50 grand to a muhf*kaa like me? Can you please remind me?"</item>
		<item>"Represent, Watch The Throne, niggall be pissed off. Earth is boring to im, shit is makin my dick soft."</item>
		<item>"Im out here ballin, I know yall hear my sneaks. Jesus was a carpenter, Yeezy, laid beats. Hova flow the Holy Ghost, get the hell up out your seats...Preach."</item>
		<item>"Tears on the mauseoleum floor. Blood stains the coliseum doors. Lies on the lips of a priest. Thanksgiving disguised as a feast."</item>
		<item>"Uh, everythings for sale, I got 5 passports Im never going to jail."</item>
		<item>"I invented swag...Poppin bottles putting supermodels in the cab."</item>
		<item>"B**ch behave, just might let you meet Ye, Chi towns D. Rose, Im movin the Nets to BK."</item>
		<item>"I wish I could give you this feelin, Im planking on a million. Im riding through yo hood, you can bank I aint got no ceiling."</item>
		<item>"Mummy wrap the kids, have em cryin for they mummy back. Dummy that your daddy is, tell em I just want my racks."</item>
		<item>"Wassup, mafucka, where my money at? You gon make me come down to your house where yo mummy at."</item>
		<item>"Bueller had a Mueller, but I switched it for a Mille. Cause Im richer, and prior to this shit was movin freebase."</item>
		<item>"Driving Benzes, wit no benefits. Not bad huh? For some immigrants."</item>
		<item>"I mean Marilyn Monroe, shes quite nice but why all the pretty icons always all white. Back to my Beyonces, you deserve 3 stacks for the Andre."</item>
		<item>"Go harder than a n-gga for a n-gga go figure. Told me keep my own money if we ever did split up. How can somethin so gangsta be so pretty in pictures?"</item>
		<item>"Look a man dead in his eyes. So he know you talk truth when you speak it, give your word, keep it."</item>
		<item>"Took me 26 years to find my path. My only job is cuttin the time in half."</item>
		<item>"Sorry junior, I already ruined ya Cause you aint even alive, paparazzi pursuin ya. Sins of a father make yo life ten times harder I just wanna take ya to a barber."</item>
		<item>"Im losing myself, Im stuck in the moment. I look in the mirror, My only opponent."</item>
		<item>"Im a tortured soul, I live in disguise. Rest in peace to the leader of the Jackson 5."</item>
		<item>"Move blocks and squares, move apples and pears. Work pots and pans, just to cop me some Airs."</item>
		<item>"Black Axl Rose, move halfs and wholes. Come down to the jungle, just ask for Hov."</item>
		<item>"Now shoot trigga, stop looking at her tits. Get ya own dog, ya heard. Thats my bitch!"</item>
		<item>"You belong with n-ggas who used to be known for dope dealing. You too dope for any of those civilians."</item>
		<item>"Beat the odds, beat the Feds. It wouldnt be wise, to bet against the kid."</item>
		<item>"Who gon stop me? No brakes, I need, State Farm. So many watches I need 8 arms. One neck but got 8 charms."</item>
		<item>"Black cards, black cars, Black on black, black broads. Whole lotta money in a black bag. Black strap, you know what thats for?"</item>
		<item>"No crying in public, just lying to judges. Risking my life, Im already dying, so f*ck it well."</item>
		<item>"I went through hell, Im expecting heaven."</item>
		<item>"Middle finger to my old life, special shout out to my old head. If it wasnt for your advice, A ni**a would have been so dead."</item>
		<item>"2 seats in the 911. No limit on the black card. Told yall I was gonna go HAM, to the ocean was my backyard."</item>
		<item>"Ok here, like a hare, like a rabbit, I like karatsl Im allergic to having bunny ears, like broke, like nope, like ha, I aint no joke."</item>
		<item>"Only spot a few blacks the higher I go. Whats up to Will, shoutout to O."</item>
		<item>"In sheepskin coats, I silence the lamb. Do you know who I am Clarice? No cheap cologne whenever I shh-shh. Success never smelled so sweet."</item>
		<item>"Its a celebration of black excellence. Black tie, black Maybachs. Black excellence, opulence, decadence. Tuxes next to the president."</item>
		<item>"I arrived on the day Fred Hampton died. Real niggas just multiply and they say 21 I was supposed to die. So Im out here celebratin my post demise."</item>
		<item>"All black everything, Ni**a you know my fresh code. Im out here fightin for you, dont increase my stress load."</item>
		<item>"Too much enemy fire to catch a friendly."</item>
		<item>"I spent about a minute, maybe less on it. Fly pelican fly, turn the jets on it but first I shall digress on it."</item>
		<item>"Fu*k you squares, the circle got smaller. The castle got bigger, the walls got taller."</item>
		<item>"When the grief is over, beef is over, Ill be fly when Easters over. I tried to teach niggas how to be kings and all they ever wanted to be was soldiers."</item>
		<item>"Same people that I fought for. That I fight for, that I ride for. That I live for, that I die for. Be the reason that these niggas is alive for."</item>
		<item>"Our apple pie was supplied through Arm and Hammer. Straight out the kitchen, shh dont wake Nana!"</item>
		<item>"F**k your awards like Eddie Murphys couch. The Roc is in the building we should have stayed in the house."</item>
		<item>"Elvis has left the building now. Im on the Beatles ass Ni**as hear Watch The Throne, yeah its like the Beatles back."</item>
		<item>"King Hov, Im exactly what the f**k you think. 11 in a row, Bill Russell rings."</item>
		<item>"Michael Jordan swag. Yall think Michael Jordan bad. Nigga I got a 5 more rings than Michael Jordan had."</item>
		<item>"Im bullet proof, b**ch you cant get nothin past me."</item>
		<item>"Give all glory to Gloria, they said "you raised that boy too fast, but you was raising a warrior." We victorious, they'll never take the joy from us."</item>
		<item>"New money, I found the fountain of youth. Im headed to Miami to f**k up the Fontaine Bleu."</item>
		<item>"As far as them 16s, Im 23 of it all Primetime, riding that 6 deuce. That 9-11 I only subtract the roof."</item>
		<item>"At 42 be better than 24, I carried the 4-5, mastered 48 laws."</item>
		<item>"Mo money, 40 year old phenom. Our 15 minutes of fame has stretched beyond."</item>
		<item>"This is where DiNero would be if he aint turn back. F**k Sosa, this Hova this is real life. This is what the ending of Scarface should feel like."</item>
		<item>"Just a f***in waste of time, a complete waste of bottles. Ni**as fashion is weak, they be wastin all the models."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
