<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I don't stand for the black man's side, I don' t stand for the white man's side.I stand for God's side."</item>
		<item>"Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you're living?"</item>
		<item>"Life is one big road with lots of signs. So when you riding through the ruts, don't complicate your mind. Flee from hate, mischief and jealousy. Don't bury your thoughts, put your vision to reality. Wake Up and Live!"</item>
		<item>"Tell the children the truth."</item>
		<item>"Life and Jah are one in the same. Jah is the gift of existence. I am in some way eternal, I will never be duplicated. The singularity of every man and woman is Jah's gift. What we struggle to make of it is our sole gift to Jah. The process of what th."</item>
		<item>"Your worst enemy could be your best friend, and your best friend your worst enemy."</item>
		<item>"Love would never leave us alone"</item>
		<item>"If I was educated, I'd be a damn fool."</item>
		<item>"Conquer the devils with a little thing called love!"</item>
		<item>"I have got a running stream of love you see. So no matter what stages.. they put us through, we'll never be blue."</item>
		<item>"I want to give you some love, I want to give you some good good lovin'."</item>
		<item>"The power of philosophy floats through my head, Light like a feather, Heavy as Led"</item>
		<item>"Jah will never give the power to a baldhead!"</item>
		<item>"When one door is closed, don't you know, another is open."</item>
		<item>"Every man gotta right to decide his own destiny."</item>
		<item>"Herb is the healing of a nation, alcohol is the destruction."</item>
		<item>"Don't forget your history nor your destiny"</item>
		<item>"Overcome the devils with a thing named love."</item>
		<item>"Don't gain the world and lose your soul, wisdom is better than silver or gold..."</item>
		<item>"I handle fame by not being famous...I'm not famous to me."</item>
		<item>"Excuse me while I light my spliff good God I gotta take a lift"</item>
		<item>"I don't stand for the black man's side, I don't stand for the white man's side. I stand for God's side"</item>
		<item>"I'm a man of God and me come to do God's work."</item>
		<item>"How good and how pleasant it would be before God and man, yeah to see the unification of all Africans"</item>
		<item>"Man can't do without God. Just like you're thirsty, you have to drink water. You just can't go without God."</item>
		<item>"An old jeep, so nobody will say I'm driving a BMW anymore. I couldn't stand that BMW, ha ha ha! BMW make pure trouble!"</item>
		<item>"Get up, stand up, Stand up for your rights. Get up, stand up, Don't give up the fight."</item>
		<item>"Emancipate yourselves from mental slavery, none but ourselves can free our minds!"</item>
		<item>"Me only have one ambition, y'know. I only have one thing I really like to see happen. I like to see mankind live together - black, white, Chinese, everyone - that's all."</item>
		<item>"None but ourselves can free our minds."</item>
		<item>"Hey mister music, sure sounds good to me I can't refuse it what to be got to be"</item>
		<item>"I like Wagner's music much better than anybody's. It's so loud that one can talk the whole time without people hearing you."</item>
		<item>"My music will go on forever. Maybe it's a fool say that, but when me know facts me can say facts. My music will go on forever."</item>
		<item>"My music fights against the system that teaches to live and die."</item>
		<item>"Life is one big road with lots of signs. So when you riding through the ruts, don't complicate your mind. Flee from hate, mischief and jealousy. Don't bury your thoughts, put your vision to reality . Wake Up and Live!"</item>
		<item>"Rastafari not a culture, it's a reality."</item>
		<item>"People want to listen to a message, word from Jah. This could be passed through me or anybody. I am not a leader. Messenger. The words of the songs, not the person, is what attracts people."</item>
		<item>"One good thing about music, when it hits you, you feel no pain."</item>
		<item>"My future is righteousness."</item>
		<item>"Man is a universe within himself."</item>
		<item>"In this bright future you can't forget your past."</item>
		<item>"If you get down and quarell everyday, you're saying prayers to the devil, I say."</item>
		<item>"I've been here before and will come again, but I'm not going this trip through."</item>
		<item>"Every time I plant a seed, He say kill it before it grow, he say kill it before they grow."</item>
		<item>"Bob Marley isn't my name. I don't even know my name yet."</item>
		<item>"You have to be someone."</item>
		<item>"When you smoke the herb, it reveals you to yourself."</item>
		<item>"The more people smoke herb, the more Babylon fall."</item>
		<item>"The harder the battle the sweet of jah victory."</item>
		<item>"The good times of today, are the sad thoughts of tomorrow."</item>
		<item>"If I was educated, I'd be a damn fool"</item>
		<item>"I drive a jeep. An old jeep, so nobody will say I'm driving a BMW anymore. I couldn't stand that BMW, ha ha ha! BMW make pure trouble!"</item>
		<item>"Free speech carries with it some freedom to listen"</item>
		<item>"No woman, no cry"</item>
		<item>"Love the life you live. Live the life you love"</item>
		<item>"Life is one big road with lots of signs. So when you riding through the ruts, don't complicate your mind. Flee from hate, mischief and jealousy. Don't bury your thoughts, put your vision to reality. Wake up and live!"</item>
		<item>"Who are you to judge the life I live?. I know im not perfect and i dont live to be. But before you start pointing fingers, make sure your hands are clean"</item>
		<item>"The good times of today are the sad thoughts of tomorrow."</item>
		<item>"None, but ourselves, can free our minds"</item>
		<item>"You ain't gonna miss your water until your well runs dry"</item>
		<item>"Don't forget your history, nor your destiny"</item>
		<item>"When the race gets hard to run, it means you just can't take the pace"</item>
		<item>"Don't gain the world and lose your soul, wisdom is better than silver or gold"</item>
		<item>"In this bright future you can't forget your past"</item>
		<item>"Herb is the healing of a nation. Alcohol is the destruction."</item>
		<item>"Don't worry about a thing, every little thing is gonna be alright."</item>
		<item>"Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you're living?"</item>
		<item>"You have to be someone"</item>
		<item>"Me only have one ambition, y'know. I only have one thing I really like to see happen. I like to see mankind live together - black, white, Chinese, everyone - that's all."</item>
		<item>"In this great future, you cant forget your past"</item>
		<item>"Don't gain the world and lose your soul, wisdom is better than silver or gold..."</item>
		<item>"Don't forget your history nor your destiny"</item>
		<item>"Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you're living?"</item>
		<item>"Don't worry about a thing, every little thing is gonna be alright."</item>
		<item>"When the race gets hard to run, it means you just can't take the pace."</item>
		<item>"You ain't gonna miss your water until your well runs dry."</item>
		<item>"Love the life you live. Live the life you love."</item>
		<item>"When one door is closed, don't you know, another is open."</item>
		<item>"Until the philosophy which hold one race superior and another inferior is finally discredited and abandoned...WAR! So that is prophecy, and everyone know that is truth. And it came out of the mouth of Rastafari."</item>
		<item>"Don't worry about a thing, every little thing is gonna be alright"</item>
		<item>"Just can't live that negative way...make way for the positive day!"</item>
		<item>"Most people think Great God will come from the sky, Take away ev'rything, and make ev'rybody feel high. But if you know what life is worth, you would look for yours on earth, And now you see the light, you stand up for right, yah."</item>
		<item>"Rise O fallen fighters, rise and take your stance again, He who fight and run away, live to fight another day"</item>
		<item>"I don't stand for the black man's side, I don't stand for the white man's side. I stand for God's side"</item>
		<item>"When you smoke the herb, it reveals you to yourself."</item>
		<item>"Facts an' facts, an' t'ings an t'ings: dem's all a lotta fockin' bullshit. Hear me! Dere is no truth but de one truth, an' that is the truth of Jah Rastafari."</item>
		<item>"Sun is shining. Weather is sweet. Make you wanna move your dancing feet."</item>
		<item>"Just can't live that negative way...make way for the positive day!"</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
