<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"His real name is Curtis James Jackson III."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent was expelled in 10th grade for possession of crack. Got his GED while in jail."</item>
	<item>"As a teenager, 50 Cent was fondly known as Boo-Boo."</item>
	<item>"He rose to fame with the release of his albums Get Rich or Die Tryin’ (2003)."</item>
	<item>"He has also pursued an acting career, appearing in the semi-autobiographical film Get Rich or Die Tryin’ in 2005, the Iraq War film Home of the Brave in 2006, and Righteous Kill in 2008."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent is one of the richest hip-hop performers, having a net worth estimated at US $440 million in 2008."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent has engaged in feuds with other rappers including Ja Rule, The Game, Cam’ron, Fat Joe, Lil Wayne and Rick Ross."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent borrowed his stage moniker from a late Brooklyn druglord named Kelvin Martin."</item>
	<item>"50 dabbled in boxing in his teenage years."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent was born  on July 6, 1975 in South Jamaica, Queens."</item>
	<item>"He grew up without a father and his mother was murdered when he was eight years old."</item>
	<item>"At the age of 12, 50 Cent began dealing drugs in order to get by in a tough neighborhood."</item>
	<item>"His rapping career began in a friend's basement in 1996."</item>
	<item>"In 2000, he was shot nine times and spent 13 days in the hospital."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent's big break came in 2002 when Eminem introduced him to Dr. Dre."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent established G-Unit Records in 2003 and proceeded to expand his career as a producer and entrepreneur."</item>
	<item>"He is left-handed."</item>
	<item>"50 never had a real job"</item>
	<item>"His favorite actor is Charlie Sheen."</item>
	<item>"50 shares the same birthday as George W. Bush"</item>
	<item>"His boxing name was \"BooBoo\"."</item>
	<item>"He lives in Mike Tyson's old house in Farmington, Connecticut."</item>
	<item>"He doesn't smoke or drink."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent's mother, Sabrina, was murdered when he was eight years old. She was a drug dealer."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent was raised in Queens by his grandparents."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent's first arrest happened at his high school when he was busted in gym class for the hidden crack vials in his sneakers."</item>
	<item>"His crack operation grew to gross over $5,000 a day, but he saw rap as a way to get out of the game and performed rhymes at parties."</item>
	<item>"His big opportunity came in the form of the late Jam Master Jay, who signed 50 Cent to his JMJ label in 1996."</item>
	<item>"After catching the attention of the Trackmasters, in 1999 50 Cent signed a deal with Columbia Records for $250,000."</item>
	<item>"In just over two weeks, he recorded thirty-six songs, some of which ended up on his Columbia debut LP Power of a Dollar, deemed by Blaze Magazine as a classic."</item>
	<item>"With the Columbia deal, he received a $65,000 advance. $50,000 went to Jam Master Jay and $10,000 went to an attorney."</item>
	<item>"This is what 50 Cent says he did with the remaining $5,000: \"I bought crack cocaine with it. How else you gonna provide for yourself? I did thirty-six songs in eighteen days for Columbia. Then I had eight months go by with no work going on\"."</item>
	<item>"In the summer of 1999, his first single was released. It was the comedic, and now classic, single "How To Rob," which jokes about jacking the hottest music celebrities of that time, including Mariah Carey, Master P, Timbaland and Jay-Z."</item>
	<item>"In the spring of 2000, 50 Cent was shot in the face, hand and legs by a man with a nine millimeter at close range. He survived a total of nine bullets. One of the bullets lodged in his lower gum. There's still a gaping wound where several of his rear teeth used to be."</item>
	<item>"After the shooting Columbia got really nervous and dropped 50 Cent like a hot potato."</item>
	<item>"According to 50 Cent, beef started with Ja Rule and Murder Inc. when Ja Rule was robbed by a neighborhood acquaintance of 50 Cent's."</item>
	<item>"He was allegedly stabbed during a recording-studio scuffle with Ja Rule's posse."</item>
	<item>"That's not a dimple on 50 Cent's left cheek. It's a bullet wound."</item>
	<item>"After Columbia released him, 50 Cent started selling his music straight to bootleggers."</item>
	<item>"Many or the covers of his bootleg CDs feature 50 Cent brandishing some sort of firearm."</item>
	<item>"These bootlegs gained him many fans, including Eminem, who, on a Los Angeles radio show, declared 50 Cent his favorite rapper."</item>
	<item>"After a label bidding war, 50 Cent signed with Eminem's Shady Aftermath for a reported amount of $1 million."</item> 
	<item>"His first single for Aftermath, \"Wanksta,\" first appeared on the 8 Mile soundtrack."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent once said that Ja Rule was the inspiration for \"Wanksta\"."</item>
	<item>"50 first received mainstream press in November 2002, when police questioned him in the days following the murder of Jam Master Jay."</item>
	<item>"A three man security detail isn't enough to protect 50 Cent. He wears a bullet-proof vest religiously, as does both members of his G-Unit crew. 50 Cent's SUV is also bulletproof... and bombproof."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent's favourite song from his album Get Rich Or Die Trying is \"Many Men\"."</item>
	<item>"In 2008, 50 Cent surprised actor Val Kilmer by composing a song for his children."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent bought a 1965 Chevy Impala for his Streets of Blood in Louisiana co-star Val Kilmer. The two share a love of vintage cars."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent was #83 on BET's Notarized: Top 100 Videos of 2007 for his video \"Straight to the Bank\"."</item>
	<item>"The title of his song \"I'll Still Kill\" featuring Akon was changed to \"I Still Will\" because of the violent nature of the name"</item>
	<item>"His third album \"Curtis\" sold 691,000 copies its first week of release."</item>
	<item>"After vowing to retire from music if Kanye West sold more albums than him, 50 Cent kept his word and canceled his European tour in 2007."</item>
	<item>"His music video for his new single \"Follow My Lead\" featuring Robin Thicke leaked online August 10, 2007 leaving 50 Cent angry."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent was voted as #8 of the \"Hottest MCs in the Game\" right now."</item>
	<item>"As of 2007, 50 Cent has appeared in commercials for Vitamin Water."</item>
	<item>"He recorded an album in 1999 titled Power of the Dollar but it was shelved by Columbia Records due to his "legal problems"."</item>
	<item>"50 was #8 on the annual Forbes magazine Celebrity 100 list in 2006. He was #32 in 2007."</item>
	<item>"He was named among Fade In Magazine's \"100 People in Hollywood You Need to Know\" in 2005."</item>
	<item>"The three books that 50 Cent has penned are entitled: Death Before Dishonour, Baby Brother and The Ski Mask Way."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent is to launch his own range of condoms in 2007. He will put his name to a new line of rubber sheaths and has revealed he is to donate a percentage of the profits to a HIV charity."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent appeared as a guest on The Howard Stern Show on Thursday, January 4, 2007."</item>
	<item>"His first fight in jail was in the showers."</item>
	<item>"He has featured on both Lil Scrappy as well as Ciara's albums."</item>
	<item>"His first music video was \"Rowdy Rowdy\"."</item>
	<item>"He recently called Oprah Winfrey an \"oreo cookie,\" stating that she has catered to a middle age group for so long that she in fact became a middle aged white woman. "</item>
	<item>"50 Cent has his own vitamin water called \"Formula 50\"."</item>
	<item>"He has signed on to star opposite Nicholas Cage in the boxing flick The Dance."</item>
	<item>"A judge has dismissed claims by the ex-frontman of rap group \"2 Live Crew\" that 50 Cent stole the opening line for the 2003 single \"In Da Club\"."</item>
	<item>"His first album, Get Rich or Die Tryin', was certified six times platinum by the RIAA."</item>
	<item>"He created a dance known as the \"two step\"."</item>
	<item>"He is the first performer to place at least four songs in the Top 10 of Billboard's Hot 100 since the Beatles in 1964."</item>
	<item>"50 sued a Philadelphia automobile dealer with a $1 million lawsuit, claiming the business used his name and likeness without permission."</item>
	<item>"Billboards advertising 50 Cent's film Get Rich Or Die Tryin', were to be removed in Los Angeles communities, following complaints that they glorify gun violence."</item>
	<item>"50 lashed out at fellow hip-hop star Kanye West for accusing U.S. President George W. Bush of racism in the wake of Hurricane Katrina."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent is set to appear on Ciara's sophomore album entitled \"The Evolution\" in a highly anticipated track called \"Dope Boyz\"."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent appeared on an episode of The Simpsons entitled \"Pranksta Rap\" in February 2005."</item>
	<item>"He recorded the track "Piggy Bank" on his album \"The Massacre\" and attacked Jadakiss and Fat Joe for their association with Ja Rule."</item>
	<item>"He released a memoir about his life up to his success entitled \"From Pieces to Weight: Once Upon a Time in Southside Queens\"; the book was released on August 9, 2005."</item>
	<item>"He has a video game called \"50 Cent: Bulletproof\", which is available on the PS2, Xbox, and PSP."</item>
	<item>"After the release of \"Beg For Mercy\" from his group G-Unit, he teamed up with Reebok to release his own G-Unit Sneakers and clothing line."</item>
	<item>"Since starting G-Unit as of 2006 he has signed three different artists including Mobb Deep, Ma$e, and M.O.P."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent is on the cover of the December 2005 issue of GQ."</item>
	<item>"The shooter of 50 Cent was shot 9 times and died, but it was not known who did the shooting."</item>
	<item>"Jay-Z, the late Big Punisher, Sticky Fingaz, Ghostface Killah and most recently Fat Joe, Jadakiss, The Game and Nas have all replied to 50 Cent's dissing songs."</item>
	<item>"50 cent was an orphaned child."</item>
	<item>"His debut album \"Get Rich or Die Tryin\" was the highest debut ever with 872,000 copies sold in the first week."</item>
	<item>"50 Cent has a son: Marquise, nicknamed 25 Cent."</item>
	<item>"G-Unit Records consists of: 50 Cent, Tony Yayo, Lloyd Banks, Young Buck, Olivia, Spider Loc, Mobb Deep, M.O.P., Ma$e, Young Hot Rod and DJ Whoo Kid."</item>
	
	
</string-array>
</resources>
