<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"If I hadn’t met Evan and Carl I might have just been dreaming forever."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce just put the level of female entertainment all the way up there. She does acting, she has a beautiful voice and that’s really the person I look up to… that type of entertainer."</item>
		<item>"I want to give people a taste of the Caribbean, and show them the fun side of me.".</item>
		<item>"I did one talent show at my high school, and I won it singing Mariah Carey’s Hero."</item>
		<item>"so just pull the trigger"</item>
		<item>"I’m not a wh*re …I”m a russian roulette."</item>
		<item>"baby put the work in like a champion."</item>
		<item>"they can say whatever imma do whatever no pain is forever yup you noticed"</item>
		<item>"release me now cause i did my time, of this cold case love"</item>
		<item>"baby let em play it maybe it’ll save the world, they gon miss hearing it when its gone"</item>
		<item>"Come on, come on, come on in."</item>
		<item>"There’s so much power in my name, if you pop off and say it, stadium gone do the wave."</item>
		<item>"They can say whatever, I’m gone do whatever, No pain is forever, Yup you know this."</item>
		<item>"I never play the victim, I’d rather be the stalker."</item>
		<item>"Where I’m going I dont need my brakes."</item>
		<item>"My heart dont stop, My Heart be beating over, My loving dont stop, Even though its over."</item>
		<item>"Breaking liars down to they knees."</item>
		<item>"I feel the love but I dont feel that way."</item>
		<item>"come here rude boi boi can you get it up"</item>
		<item>"Success for me isn't a destination... it's a journey."</item>
		<item>"It's all about working harder and getting better and moving up and up."</item>
		<item>"Everybody's working to get to the top but where is the top?"</item>
		<item>"Eating ice cream late at night is so bad, but I love it!"</item>
		<item>"All humans are born with the ability to be attracted to both sexes. I mean, I could see myself in a relationship with a girl."</item>
		<item>"That would be... ME, when I was skinny!"</item>
		<item>"I’m really scared of the actual childbirth situation but I do want to be a mom one day. Even if I have to adopt, I want to be a mom."</item>
		<item>"I have an ugly day every month... pimples on my face, I’m fat and in a bad mood. It’s more like an ugly week!."</item>
		<item>"I’ve been working out a lot and I eat pretty boring — boiled egg, fruit, tons of water and some chicken."</item>
		<item>"I want to learn the drums and I want to work with Depeche Mode so bad."</item>
		<item>"I want to stop shopping, being late, start waking up early, stuff like that."</item>
		<item>"I've taken some acting lessons so hopefully one day I will have time to do something like that, There is so much I want to do, something in fashion as well. I just want to keep getting better."</item>
		<item>"I'd love to be an assassin - either that or a lesbian. Maybe both! Hey, a gay assassin, there's nothing hotter than that. Megan Fox would play my girlfriend - hands down. She's yummy. She's hot."</item>
		<item>"With people that are close to me, if I tell them something that is bothering me, it will bother them, and I don't like that."</item>
		<item>"I don't know, I have always been that way, I have always been very guarded over stuff like that and I don't like people feeling sorry for me so I don't like talking about sad things."</item>
		<item>"I don't miss s*x because I still have fun by myself. You get what I mean?"</item>
		<item>"Dating would be fun to incorporate. It's a lot of commitment so I don't want a serious relationship."</item>
		<item>"I love flirting at the moment. I'm single and I'm enjoying my freedom. But I don't give my phone number out that often. But if I'm dating, I check the boy from the top to the bottom."</item>
		<item>"I'm usually a very guarded person, so having to go in and reach your emotions and personal things to say, it was very vulnerable."</item>
		<item>"I don't plan my tattoos. It's always something that I love."</item>
		<item>"The shoes, the clothes are pretty uncomfortable."</item>
		<item>"Nothing I wear is comfortable besides my underwear."</item>
		<item>"I went to sleep as Rihanna and woke up as Britney Spears. That was the level of media chaos that happened the next day."</item>
		<item>"Rihanna didn't get any lap dances herself, but she was tipping the girls a lot... And she was definitely with one of the guys in her group and kissing him all night!"</item>
		<item>"You had a good girl, good girl but didn't know how to treat her. So silly boy get out my face. Why do you like the way regrets taste?"</item>
		<item>"You fooled me once but you can't have that ego turning."</item>
		<item>"You can't even go out with a friend who's a celebrity and have a good time without people making shit up."</item>
		<item>"The hardest thing for me is to say no. I feel like a bitch. But sometimes I don't have a choice."</item>
		<item>"People ask me the most naive questions. Someone asked me if we have indoor toilets. I can't get upset. They just don't know."</item>
		<item>"While in America beautiful is skinny, in Barbados it's thick — girls with huge butts and nice curves."</item>
		<item>"Genetically my legs are supposed to be huge. I can't really think about it, or I'll go crazy."</item>
		<item>"The label didn't want me to do this look. But cutting my hair, it made me stand out as an artist. I don't care who likes it--this is me."</item>
		<item>"She's Beyonce, and I'm [Jay-Z's] new protegee. When we see each other we say hi. We're not enemies, but we're not friends friends."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce wrote me a note that said, 'When you get onstage, just let loose. Have fun. You're in control."</item>
		<item>"I keep working at it as I want it to be perfect, It makes my clothes look good and guys like it!"</item>
		<item>"I want to be the black Madonna."</item>
		<item>"People think, because we're young, we aren't complex, but that's not true. We deal with life and love and broken hearts in the same way a woman a few years older might."</item>
		<item>"Success for me isn't a destination it's a journey. Everybody's working to get to the top but where is the top? It's all about working harder and getting better and moving up and up."</item>
		<item>"It is one thing to record an album but it's a huge difference when people play it and listen to it and embrace it the way that I do. It has always been my dream to get my music out to the world and have people hear it."</item>
		<item>"People don't do them around me. I would never allow it. The people who are around me are people that I love, and I don't want to see people that I love hurt themselves."</item>
		<item>"There's nothing that I say \"I have to make this decision\". We all make our decisions together. I'm new to this industry and these are people who have experienced it and been here and seen it all."</item>
		<item>"Got my middle finger up - I don't really give a fuck."</item>
		<item>"I never play the victim, I'd rather be a stalker."</item>
		<item>"I'm so hard!"</item>
		<item>"I told ya baby, I'm a rockstar!"</item>
		<item>"Oh nah nah, what's my name?"</item>
		<item>"No pain is forever."</item>
		<item>"Tougher than a lion; ain't no need in tryin'."</item>
		<item>"My runway never looked so clear."</item>
		<item>"The hottest bitch in heels right here."</item>
		<item>"Baby you're a challenge; let's explore your talent."</item>
		<item>"I really wanna be with you, 'cause you just my type."</item>
		<item>"Every door you enter I will let you in."</item>
		<item>"You take me way past the point of turning me on!"</item>
		<item>"You're so amazing - you took the time to figure me out."</item>
		<item>"The only thing I'm missin' is a black guitar."</item>
		<item>"To be what you is you gotta be what you are."</item>
		<item>"Big cities and bright lights. Sleep all day; long nights."</item>
		<item>"Make sure you frisk me good. Check my panties and my bra."</item>
		<item>"I ain't got time to borrow."</item>
		<item>"Tonight I'ma let you be the captain."</item>
		<item>"Give it to me, baby like boom, boom, boom."</item>
		<item>"While you getting your cry on, I'm getting my fly on."</item>
		<item>"I may be bad but I'm perfectly good at it."</item>
		<item>"I hate how much I love you boy, but I just can't let you go. And I hate that I love you so."</item>
		<item>"Me just thinking on the time that I'm facing. Makes me wanna cry."</item>
		<item>"I need to get out of sight. Before I end up behind bars..."</item>
		<item>"What started out as a simple altercation. Turned into a real sticky situation."</item>
		<item>"I came to win, to fight, to conquer, to thrive I came to win, to survive, to prosper, to rise to fly..."</item>
		<item>"Sticks and stones may break my bones, But chains and whips excite me."</item>
		<item>"Cause I may be bad, but Im perfectly good at it. Sex in the air, I dont care, I love the smell of it."</item>
		<item>"Love is great, love is fine. Out the box, out of line. The affliction of the feeling leaves me wanting more."</item>
		<item>"Feels so good being bad. Theres no way Im turning back. Now the pain is for pleasure, cause nothing can measure."</item>
		<item>"You know what I need want you to see everything. Want you to see all of the lights."</item>
		<item>"Turn up the lights in here baby extra bright, I want yall to see this."</item>
		<item>"Oh lord a mercy now I am a criminal. Man Down. Tell the judge please gimme minimal."</item>
		<item>"Why did I pull the trigger. Pull the trigger pull the trigger BOOM! And end a nigga end a niggas life so soon."</item>
		<item>"Now hes no longer living. So Imma bout to leave town..."</item>
		<item>"I didn't mean to lay him down but its too late to turn back now. Don't know what I was thinking."</item>
		<item>"What do you expect me to do? If you're playing me for a fool I will lose my cool and reach for my fire arm."</item>
		<item>"Oh mama mama mama I just shot a man down. In central station In front of a big ol crowd."</item>
		<item>"Rum bum bum bum rum bum bum bum rum bum bum bum...Man Down"</item>
		<item>"Cause I didn't mean to hurt him. Coulda been somebody's son and I took his heart when...I pulled out that gun"</item>
		<item>"Take my heart from you and you come running after me and baby.I'm back with you."</item>
		<item>"Why is everything with you so complicated? Why do you make it hard to love you? Oh I hate it..."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
