<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I need more friends. It's kind of like my quest right now just to have more true friends."</item>
		<item>"I think my dad is a lot cooler than other dads. He still acts like he's still 17."</item>
		<item>"I probably have an earlier curfew than anyone. My mom wants to keep me really safe and my dad's not overly protective, but he's a dad no matter what."</item>
		<item>"I love to sleep. I'd sleep all day if I could."</item>
		<item>"I have four shelves covered with journals that I've written. Dad and I are writing songs together. I've probably written 100 songs."</item>
		<item>"I get more anxious than nervous before a concert."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to be perfect, but I do want to be a role model. My mom always tells me that imperfections equal beauty. All of us are imperfect."</item>
		<item>"I come from this really small town near Nashville, Tennessee, where everything was la-di-da and normal."</item>
		<item>"I am so excited to let fans in on how important my relationship with my family is to me. I hope to motivate mothers and daughters to build lifetimes of memories together and inspire kids around the world to live their dreams."</item>
		<item>"I am not very good at keeping secrets at all! If you want your secret kept do not tell me!"</item>
		<item>"I am fully committed to Hannah Montana. It's what gave me this amazing opportunity to reach out to so many people. I'm really excited about our new season. We are making great new episodes that I can't wait for our fans to see and I'm looking forward to the Hannah Montana movie that will be out in the spring."</item>
		<item>"As soon as I step on that stage, nothing matters. I don't think of it as work. It's just so much fun."</item>
		<item>"You don't have to go out and party every night. You can act because it's your dream."</item>
		<item>"You can't live a positive life with a negative mind and if you have a positive outcome you have a positive income and just to have more positivity and just to kind of laugh it off."</item>
		<item>"With yourself, I think you have to decide the kind of person that you really want to be, and for me, it's just a sweet girl."</item>
		<item>"When preparing for a concert, I do lots of training. I work with a choreographer to create great moves and then I have to keep my voice strong with lessons."</item>
		<item>"There's nothing more fun than being out on stage and getting the vibe from the crowd. There's nothing like being on a set where you are there to make other people happy and to make them laugh. That's the best job in the world."</item>
		<item>"There are so many people that have come up to me during our shows and tell me: The hour that we are watching your show is the hour that my kids are happiest and are smiling, they are laughing, and that is what I long to do."</item>
		<item>"The only people that you really have, that I learned, are your family, because they love you no matter what."</item>
		<item>"The best part of my carreer is getting to meet so many different people, because I learn so much from everyone."</item>
		<item>"Pink isn't just a color, it's an attitude!"</item>
		<item>"My mom is always telling me it takes a long time to get to the top, but a short time to get to the bottom."</item>
		<item>"My favourite sport is cheerleading!"</item>
		<item>"My dad says I could sing before I could talk, if that's possible. I was always humming and things like that."</item>
		<item>"Music is what I breath, what I love to do. It keeps me alive."</item>
		<item>"Life is all about having a good time."</item>
		<item>"If you believe in yourself anything is possible."</item>
		<item>"If I could get any animal it would be a dolphin. I want one so bad. Me and my mom went swimming with dolphins and I was like, 'How do we get one of those?' and she was like, 'You can't get a dolphin. What are you gonna do, like, put it in your pool?'"</item>
		<item>"I've got high standards when it comes to boys. As my dad says, all girls should! I'm from the South - Tennessee, to be exact - and down there, we're all about southern hospitality. I know that if I like a guy, he better be nice, and above all, my dad has to approve of him!"</item>
		<item>"I'm pretty outspoken."</item>
		<item>"I told my mom, 'I'm not buying another magazine until I can get past this thought of looking like the girl on the cover'. She said, Miley, you are the girl on the cover,' and I was, like, 'I know, but I don't feel like that girl every day.' You can't always feel perfect."</item>
		<item>"Hopefully people will take me more seriously as an actress. That's what I really want to do, it's my passion and it's what I want to be considered to do. I just want to continue to do film, it's what I love."</item>
		<item>"Bieber fever...I'm not necessarily a fan. I don't listen to that kind of music. But my little sister was obsessed with him, and he actually gave her a shout-out on Twitter, and I thought that was really sweet. So I was like, 'Thank you so much. That meant a lot too.' He called her a cutie, and I haven't stopped hearing about it."</item>
		<item>"I like Kurt Cobain. [He] is like my dream boyfriend."</item>
		<item>"Growing up is important, and I've got to do that gracefully, but also keep myself at a good pace."</item>
		<item>"I like being the girl nobody can have."</item>
		<item>"With yourself, I think you have to decide the kind of person that you really want to be, and for me, it's just a sweet girl"</item>
		<item>"My priorities are my friends and my family."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to be perfect, but I do want to be a role model. My mom always tells me that imperfections equal beauty. All of us are imperfect."</item>
		<item>"I have a heart that will -- never be tamed."</item>
		<item>"My heart won't let you go, and I need you to know, I miss you."</item>
		<item>"I know your in a better place, yeah. But I wish that I could see your face, oh I know that your'e where you need to be, even though it's not here with me."</item>
		<item>"You used to call me your dreamer and now I'm living out my dream. Oh, how I wish you could see everything that's happening for me. I'm thinking back on the past, it's true that time is flying by too fast."</item>
		<item>"Welcome to the land of fame excess, am I gonna fit in?"</item>
		<item>"There's always gonna be another mountain, I'm always gonna wanna make it move. Always gonna be an uphill battle, sometimes I'm gonna have to lose. It ain't about how fast I get there, ain't about what's waiting on the other side, it's the climb."</item>
		<item>"I probably shouldn't say this, but at times I get scared, when I think about the previous relationship we shared. It was awesome, but we lost it. It's not possible, for me, not to care. And now we're standing in the rain, but nothings ever gonna change, until you're here, my dear."</item>
		<item>"Hopefully people will take me more seriously as an actress. Thats what I really want to do, its my passion and its what I want to be considered to do. I just want to continue to do film, its what I love."</item>
		<item>"Growing up is important, and Ive got to do that gracefully, but also keep myself at a good pace."</item>
		<item>"With yourself, I think you have to decide the kind of person that you really want to be, and for me, its just a sweet girl."</item>
		<item>"I have a heart that will never be tamed."</item>
		<item>"I dont want to be perfect, but I do want to be a role model. My mom always tells me that imperfections equal beauty. All of us are imperfect."</item>
		<item>"My heart wont let you go, and I need you to know, I miss you."</item>
		<item>"I know your in a better place, yeah. But I wish that I could see your face, oh I know that youre where you need to be, even though its not here with me."</item>
		<item>"You used to call me your dreamer and now Im living out my dream. Oh, how I wish you could see everything thats happening for me. Im thinking back on the past, its true that time is flying by too fast."</item>
		<item>"I can't wait to see you again, I've got a way of knowing when something is right. I feel like I must have known you in another life."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
