<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Nicki loves Judge Judy and she even calls her a \"comedian\"."</item>
		<item>"Nicki would also enjoy playing a role in an action movie, like Angelina Jolie."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's dream role is to play someone in a Tim Burton movie, where she would get dressed up and painted and crazy."</item>
		<item>"Nicki thinks that Lady GaGa is \"badass\" and she would not mind doing a song with GaGa."</item>
		<item>"Nicki claims that she would do a song with Taylor Swift."</item>
		<item>"The outfit that Nicki wore to The Grammy's was by Givenchy."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's real name is Onika Maraj."</item>
		<item>"Her birthday is December 8, 1984."</item>
		<item>"The tattoo on her left arm is Chinese script for \"God is with me always\"."</item>
		<item>"Minaj is of mixed descent with African, Trinidadian and Indo-Asian roots."</item>
		<item>"She's a Saggitarius."</item>
		<item>"She's a native New Yorker hailing from Jamaica, Queens, NY."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj's fast food of choice is Popeyes Chicken."</item>
		<item>"She has a sister and two brothers."</item>
		<item>"She worked at a Red Lobster restaurant in the Bronx."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj has also referred to herself as \"Cookie\",\"Harajuku Barbie\" and \"Roman Zolanski\"."</item>
		<item>"Nicki is the survivor of a broken home. The product of a drug addicted father and a struggling single-mom."</item>
		<item>"She studied singing and acting at LaGaurdia High School in NY where she graduated."</item>
		<item>"Before rapping she sang background vocals and hooks for local rap acts from around her way."</item>
		<item>"In 2008 she won the Female Artist Of The Year at the Underground Music Awards."</item>
		<item>"She is the first female rap act signed to rapper Lil Wayne's Young Money Records and is the labels first lady."</item>
		<item>"Nicki sites beloved rap figure Lauryn Hill as one of her major influences and says that she wants fans to focus on her music and not her sexy image."</item>
		<item>"Minaj is openly bi-sexual."</item>
		<item>"Nicki is shittin' on all the other rap bitches."</item>
		<item>"Nicki remembers listening to George Michael as she grew up."</item>
		<item>"Nicki wears Chloe perfume."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's mom once had a dream that her dad would set the house on fire. The next day, her dad actually set the house on fire."</item>
		<item>"Nicki has been writing and recording raps for over 7 years."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's mom means the world to her."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's father dealt with alcohol and drugs as Nicki grew up."</item>
		<item>"Nicki started making \"weird raps\" when she was 11 years old."</item>
		<item>"Nicki loves her barbs and kens."</item>
		<item>"Pink Friday is PLATINUM."</item>
		<item>"Nicki was fired from about 4 red lobsters because they said she \"had attitude\".</item>
		<item>"Nicki used to be a waitress."</item>
		<item>"Nicki plans on making a perfume."</item>
		<item>"Nicki loves intelligent men."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says she loves white boys."</item>
		<item>"Nicki doesn't get drunk."</item>
		<item>"Nicki doesn't like saying \"men\" or \"women\". She likes to say \"boys\" and \"girls\"."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says that she is a perfectionist."</item>
		<item>"Nicki was asked if she was a dancer and she replied \"hell to the no\"."</item>
		<item>"In high school, Nicki put a b in front of people's names."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says that in her next album she might do some Trini accent."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says that her song \"Save Me\" is a more \"Onika\" type of song."</item>
		<item>"Nicki loves tattoos."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says that Wayne is little but he has a nice body."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's first kiss was in elementary school with a boy named Derrick or a boy named Travis. She can't quite remember."</item>
		<item>"Nicki claims that she had the most fun recording \"Roman's Revenge\" out of all songs on Pink Friday."</item>
		<item>"Nicki started rapping by just being funny and messing around and eventually joined a small rap group."</item>
		<item>"Nicki thinks a good wifey is naughty or nice. She says \"Too nice is not good\"."</item>
		<item>"Nicki says that \"Queen's girls are more girly than most girls\"."</item>
		<item>"Nicki eats rap bitches for dinner."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj became the first artist ever to have seven songs within the Billboard Hot 100 at the same time."</item>
		<item>"Some of Nicki's favorite comedians include: Martin Lawrence, Chris Rock and Larry David."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's favorite party anthem is Firework by Katy Perry."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's favorite love song is Just the Way You Are by Bruno Mars."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's favorite video shoot was \"Check it Out\" with will.i.am."</item>
		<item>"Nicki used to play the clarinet."</item>
		<item>"Nicki likes Kit-Kats."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's appearance on SNL gave the show their second highest ratings in the season."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj is a morning person."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's favorite color is pink."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj dislikes people that burp."</item>
		<item>"Nicki hates cats."</item>
		<item>"Nicki graduated from LaGuardia High School (Manhattan). There, she studied singing and acting."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite actress is Jada Pinkett."</item>
		<item>"Nicki's favorite movies are Gladiator and Set it Off"</item>
		<item>"Nicki loves to write."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Currently Lives in Atlanta, Georgia"</item>
		<item>"She likes to Shop in Costume Stores"</item>
		<item>"Niki is Afraid of heights."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
