<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Beyonce nickname is Bee."</item>
		<item>"Beyonces' two favorite things are ‘Pop Eyes Fried Chicken’ and her Antique Convertible Jaguar."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce Knowles wrote and produced almost every song on Destiny’s Child’s Survivor CD."</item>
		<item>"Destiny’s Child’s hit song, Emotion, is a remake of a Bee Gees hit from the ‘70s."</item>
		<item>"Kelly Rowland is Beyonce Knowles’ cousin."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce and mother Tina Knowles introduced fashion line House of Dereon in 2004."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce got her first name from her mother's name in order to prevent the name from getting lost as mostly the women of the Beyonce family carried the name."</item>
		<item>"Bee, Moth and Juju are the pet names that Beyonce's friends have given her."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce adopts the personality of Sasha Fierce, her alter ego, while performing on the stage."</item>
		<item>"Stevie Wonder and N'Sync are amongst her favourite musicians."</item>
		<item>"Tom Hanks is her favourite actor."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce was born in Houston, TX on September 4, 1981. Her parents are Matthew Knowles and Tina Beyince. She also has a younger sister, Solange."</item>
		<item>"She won her first talent competition when she was 8. She sang John Lennon's Imagine."</item>
		<item>"She first got together with LaTavia Roberson and Kelly Rowland when she was 8. The three of them were auditioning for a girls' rap group, Kids Tyme."</item>
		<item>"LeToya Luckett joined the other 3 girls in 1993 and they were rechristened Destiny's Child."</item>
		<item>"Destiny's Child toured for four years before signing a record deal."</item>
		<item>"The group's debut song was \"Killing Time\" for the 1997 film \"Men in Black\"."</item>
		<item>"In 1998, the group had a self titled debut album which featured the song \"No, No, No\"."</item>
		<item>"In 1999, Destiny's Child released \"The Writing's on the Wall\" which had their most popular music on it. This became their breakthrough album."</item>
		<item>"By 2000, Luckett and Roberson had been eased out of the group, replaced by Michelle Williams and Farrah Franklin."</item>
		<item>"During a hiatus by Destiny's Child, Knowles recorded her own album, Dangerously In Love."</item>
		<item>"About this time, she also started an acting career. Some of her credits include Dreamgirls, Pink Panther and Cadillac Records."</item>
		<item>"Knowles performed at Superbowl XXXVIII at the Superdome in Houston in 2004."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce also performed at the Neighborhood Inagural Ball for President Barrack Obama and First Lady Michelle Obama singing \"At Last\" a ballad first made popular by Etta James."</item>
		<item>"Her first solo album is \"B'Day\", which was released in 2006."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce's full name is Beyonce Giselle Knowles."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce had a cat named Master P who died in 2007."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce's favorite makeup is mascara, but she is allergic to perfume."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite book is The Rules."</item>
		<item>"She don't like cooking."</item>
		<item>"In 2003 she starred in a major ad campaign of sexy TV commercials for Pepsi."</item>
		<item>"Her sign is a virgo."</item>
		<item>"She has this habit whenever her friend, husband or herself releases a CD she goes to the store and buys 8 copies."</item>
		<item>"She is ranked fourth in the Top 100 Celebrity in Forbes.com (2008)."</item>
		<item>"In grade school, classmates use to taunt her about her ears."</item>
		<item>"The word \“bootylicious\” was added to The Oxford Dictionary because her song of the same name became a phenomenon."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce was named after her mother’s maiden name."</item>
		<item>"In the song \“Signs\” she claims her love for Jay-Z. Guess who’s the Sagittarius?"</item>
		<item>"Beyonce Knowles’ bodyguard once broke her toe after standing on it, while trying to protect her from a crowd of fans."</item>
		<item>"She is genuinely quiet and shy person."</item>
		<item>"Obviously, Bey is obsessed with the #4. Her birthday is Sept. 4th. Her husband Jay-Z’s birthday is Dec. 4th and they got married on April 4th, 2008."</item>
		<item>"As a child, Beyonce charged her parents' houseguests $5 each to watch her perform."</item>
		<item>"Though she's written most of her lyrics, Beyonce Knowles often has trouble remembering them."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce is pregnant - false rumor from 2010th."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z reportedly bought Beyonce Knowles $350,000 worth of designer handbags and purses for Christmas."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce Knowles has been named Hollywood's highest-earning popstar of 2010."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce was sued by a guy who claims his daily routine was turned upside down by a film crew shooting a Beyonce music video for \"Why Don't You Love Me\"."</item>
		<item>"Proving even divas can be playful, Beyonce got buried up to her head while at the beach in Hawaii, April 2010."</item>
		<item>"Her /"I am/"  World Tour DVD has become the best-selling music video DVD of 2010."</item>
		<item>"Beyonce was named Forbes Richest Celebrity Under 30, with a total earnings of $80 million."</item>
			
	</string-array>
</resources>
	