<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Birth Name: William Bradley Pitt "</item>
		<item>"Brad Pitt was born in 1963 in Oklahoma and raised in Springfield, Missouri."</item>
		<item>"His father, William (Bill) Pitt, worked in management at a trucking firm in Springfield."</item>
		<item>"He has a younger brother, Douglas (Doug) Pitt and a younger sister Julie Neal Pitt."</item>
		<item>"His mother's name is Jane Etta Hillhouse."</item>
		<item>"At Kickapoo High School, Pitt was involved in sports, debating, student government and school musicals."</item>
		<item>"Pitt attended the University of Missouri, where he majored in journalism with a focus on advertising."</item>
		<item>"He occasionally acted in fraternity shows."</item>
		<item>"He left college two credits short of graduating to move to California."</item>
		<item>"Before he became successful at acting, Pitt supported himself by driving strippers in limos, moving refrigerators and dressing as a giant chicken while working for \"el Pollo Loco\"."</item>
		<item>"Chosen by Empire magazine as one of the 100 Sexiest Stars in film history (#23). [1995]"</item>
		<item>"Turned down a role as an astronaut in Apollo 13 (1995) to accept his role in Se7en (1995)."</item>
		<item>"Posed for a campus calendar in college."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #32 in Empire (UK) magazine's \"The Top 100 Movie Stars of All Time\" list. [October 1997]"</item>
		<item>"Mutally agrees to split with Gwyneth Paltrow. [June 1997]"</item>
		<item>"Banned from entering China because of his role in Seven Years in Tibet (1997)."</item>
		<item>"Chosen by \"People\" magazine as one of the 50 most beautiful people in the world. "</item>
		<item>"Engaged to actress Gwyneth Paltrow. [20 December 1996]"</item>
		<item>"Donated $100,000 to the Discovery Center - a children's learning museum in his hometown of Springfield, Missouri. [June 1996]"</item>
		<item>"Chosen by People (USA) magazine as one of the 50 most beautiful people in the world. [1996]"</item>
		<item>"His first starring role in a feature film was in The Dark Side of the Sun (1988), shot in pre-war Yugoslavia during the summer of 1988."</item>
		<item>"Purchased a mansion is Southern California from the actress who portrays "Elvira" (Cassandra Peterson). He reportedly paid $1.7 million for the house."</item>
		<item>"Given title \"Sexiest Man Alive\" from People Magazine, after making Legends of the Fall (1994)."</item>
		<item>"May 1992: Lived in Southern California with friend Buck Simmonds, who starred with him in A River Runs Through It."</item>
		<item>"Dated Juliette Lewis. They met on the set of the NBC movie of the week Too Young to Die? (1990) (TV). They also did Kalifornia (1993) together."</item>
		<item>"He was the third choice for the role of J.D. in Thelma and Louise (1991). William Baldwin, the first choice, left to star in Backdraft (1991)."</item>
		<item>"Had to learn to fly-cast for his role in A River Runs Through It (1992). He practiced on top of buildings in Hollywood. During these practices he frequently hooked himself in the back of his head."</item>
		<item>"Voted "Best Actor" by viewers of MTV's \"The Big Picture\" (1988) in 1995."</item>
		<item>"Was a journalism major in college with an advertising focus."</item>
		<item>"Listed as one of twelve \"Promising New Actors of 1991\" in John Willis' Screen World, Vol. 43."</item>
		<item>"Graduated from Kickapoo High School in Springfield, Mo. [1982]"</item>
		<item>"Dropped out of the University of Missouri School of Journalism (Columbia, Missouri)."</item>
		<item>"In high school was a member of the golf, tennis, and swim teams."</item>
		<item>"Belonged to the Key Club and the Forensics Club in High School."</item>
		<item>"Listed in "People Weekly"s \"Most Intriguing People\" list. "</item>
		<item>"He has a brother, Doug, born in 1966 and a sister, Julie Pitt, born in 1969."</item>
		<item>"Given title \"Sexiest Man Alive\" from People Magazine, Mr. Pitt was also People's choice in 1995. [2000]"</item>
		<item>"Was considered for the lead in The Matrix (1999)."</item>
		<item>"Has his teeth capped."</item>
		<item>"He and ex-wife Jennifer Aniston spent $1 million on their wedding. [2000]"</item>
		<item>"For the last couple of years he has been the spokesman for Edwin Jeans ads in Japan. In 2001 he was also the face of the ads for a new Japanese canned coffee which is named Roots. Was replaced in these tv ads (2002) by Kevin Costner."</item>
		<item>"Studied acting with the late Roy London."</item>
		<item>"Did TV commercial for Toyota (Altis model) that aired only in Asia. The car became very popular and its sales resulted in Toyota getting an almost 32% share of the passenger car market."</item>
		<item>"Has a home at Lake Mohawk in Sparta, New Jersey."</item>
		<item>"Is mentioned by name in the Shania Twain hit song, \"That Don't Impress Me Much\"."</item>
		<item>"He is a member of the Sigma Chi Fraternity. The Xi Xi chapter at The University of Missouri - Columbia."</item>
		<item>"After watching Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels (1998), Pitt asked director Guy Ritchie if he could be in his next film. He couldn't master the English accent, so Ritchie gave him the role of Mickey the One Punch Pikey, an Irish fighter, in Snatch. (2000)"</item>
		<item>"With Brad Grey's departure for Paramount and after the divorce settlement with ex-wife Jennifer Aniston, he now solely owns Plan B Entertainment."</item>
		<item>"Tore his Achilles tendon during the production of Troy (2004), in which he plays, ironically, Achilles. His injury caused the production of Ocean's Twelve (2004) to be pushed back to April 2004. [2003]"</item>
		<item>"Is the first man ever to be named \"Sexiest Man Alive\" twice by \"People Magazine.\" (1994 and 2000)."</item>
		<item>"He and ex-wife Jennifer Aniston campaigned in the United States to save \"EastEnders\" (1985) from being axed there [2003]."</item>
		<item>"Showed his parents the \"Chemical Burn\" scene to convince them not to watch Fight Club (1999)."</item>
		<item>"Got into better shape and eventually gained over 20 pounds of muscle for Troy (2004)."</item>
		<item>"He has appeared in three movies with the number seven in the title (Se7en (1995), Seven Years in Tibet (1997), and Sinbad: Legend of the Seven Seas (2003))."</item>
		<item>"He has also appeared in two movies with the number twelve in the title (Ocean's Twelve (2004) and Twelve Monkeys (1995))."</item>
		<item>"He was ranked #6 on VH1's \"100 Hottest Hotties\"."</item>
		<item>"His high school nickname was Brad the \"Pitt-bull\"."</item>
		<item>"He took Greek language lessons in secret to surprise his then-wife Jennifer Aniston who is of Greek ancestry."</item>
		<item>"Voted #1 in Company magazine's annual \"100 Sexiest Men\" poll, 2004."</item>
		<item>"His favorite movies are Planet of the Apes (1968) and Saturday Night Fever (1977)."</item>
		<item>"Announced on January 7, 2005 that he and Jennifer Aniston are separating after 4 1/2 years of marriage."</item>
		<item>"Was listed as a potential nominee on the 2005 Razzie Award nominating ballot. He was listed as a suggestion in the Worst Actor category for his performance in the film Troy (2004). He did not receive a nomination, however."</item>
		<item>"Dianne Wiest is his favorite actress."</item>
		<item>"Premiere Magazine ranked him as #50 on a list of the Greatest Movie Stars of All Time in their Stars in Our Constellation feature (2005)."</item>
		<item>"A short while after completing A River Runs Through It (1992), he fled to Amsterdam where he briefly lived for three months by himself in a small basement apartment before returning to the USA to film Kalifornia (1993)."</item>
		<item>"He and his ex-wife Jennifer Aniston met on a blind date, which was arranged by their agent"</item>
		<item>"He and his Ocean's Eleven (2001) / Ocean's Twelve (2004) co- stars, Julia Roberts, George Clooney and Elliott Gould, all have guest-starred on the TV show "Friends" (1994), though not in the same episodes."</item>
		<item>"Owns and plays Taylor Guitars."</item>
		<item>"In 2001 renowned architect Frank O. Gehry renovated the wine cellar in the home in which Pitt and wife Jennifer Aniston lived. Pitt subsequently did an informal apprenticeship in Gehry's Los Angeles office."</item>
		<item>"Owns the rights to the Hong Kong thriller Infernal Affairs (2002). He wanted it to be remade with he and Tom Cruise in the leading roles. The movie was eventually remade as The Departed (2006). Pitt served as a producer on the movie."</item>
		<item>"He is a big fan of MTV's \"Jackass\" (2000). He even asked the cast if he could join them during on of their stunt jokes. He eventually made an appearance dressed in an ape outfit, in order not to be recognized, which would have ruined the joke."</item>
		<item>"Raised in Springfield, Missouri, and is an alumni of Kickapoo High School. Other alumni include Adrienne Wilkinson and Jay Kenneth Johnson."</item>
		<item>"Broke his arm during the filming of Se7en (1995). The injury was written into the movie."</item>
		<item>"Adoptive father of Maddox Jolie-Pitt and Zahara Jolie-Pitt with Angelina Jolie."</item>
		<item>"Wanted to play Darcy in Bride and Prejudice (2004), but wasn't able to work out the filming dates."</item>
		<item>"Daughter (with girlfriend Angelina Jolie) Shiloh Jolie-Pitt was born 27 May 2006 in Namibia, Africa."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #15 on Premiere's 2006 "Power 50" list. Had ranked #31 in 2005."</item>
		<item>"Was considered for two roles which went to Johnny Depp: Ichabod Crane in Sleepy Hollow (1999) and Willy Wonka in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (2005). Both were directed by Tim Burton."</item>
		<item>"The first commercial that Brad Pitt ever booked was through Matrix Talent Agency, Los Angeles. His agent was Linda Olhava, sister of film director Jody Lee Olhava."</item>
		<item>"Has Single Engine Land pilot license."</item>
		<item>"Occasionally flies a Cessna 208B Caravan belonging to Chivan Productions."</item>
		<item>"Initially didn't want to appear in Mr. and Mrs. Smith (2005), although it was he who gave the script to director Doug Liman."</item>
		<item>"Originally cast as Colin Sullivan in The Departed (2006), but later dropped out. He continued to produce the film under his (and his then wife Jennifer Aniston's) production company, Plan B."</item>
		<item>"His first job was dancing in a chicken suit to draw in customers at an El Pollo Loco restaurant on Sunset Blvd. in Hollywood."</item>
		<item>"March 2007 - he and girlfriend Angelina Jolie adopted a 3-year-old boy named Pax Thien from Vietnam (born November 29th 2003)."</item>
		<item>"Made a cameo appearance with Matt Damon for free in Confessions of a Dangerous Mind (2002) as a favor to Ocean's Eleven (2001) costar and close friend George Clooney - the film was Clooney's directorial debut."</item>
		<item>"Considered for the role in Crimson Tide (1995) that eventually went to Denzel Washington."</item>
		<item>"Voted #6 in Elle (France) Magazine's \"15 Sexiest Men\" poll (June 2007)."</item>
		<item>"Mentioned in the song High School Never Ends by Bowling for Soup, as \"the quarterback\"."</item>
		<item>"Was trained to handle weapons by renowned Hollywood gun coach Thell Reed, who has also trained such actors as Val Kilmer, Leonardo DiCaprio, Russell Crowe, Sam Elliot, Girard Swan, Ben Foster and Kurt Russell."</item>
		<item>"He and Russell Crowe were director Ridley Scott's first two choices for the lead in American Gangster (2007). Crowe was eventually cast."</item>
		<item>"Used to act at the Vandevort Theater in Springfield, Missouri. He still visits and donates to the theater."</item>
		<item>"Donated 5 million dollars of his own money to rebuild homes in Katrina-ravaged New Orleans."</item>
		<item>"In 2005, he earned $4,500,000 for a Heineken commercial that aired during the 2005 Super Bowl."</item>
		<item>"In 2007, Forbes Magazine estimated his earnings for the year to be $35 million."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #10 in the 2008 Forbes' The Celebrity 100 list. His girlfriend, Angelina Jolie, ranked #3."</item>
		<item>"On July 12th 2008, his longtime girlfriend, Angelina Jolie, gave birth to twins - a boy, Knox Leon, and a girl, Vivienne Marcheline."</item>
		<item>"Was officially in the BAFTA long-list for Best Actor in a Supporting Role for his performance in Babel (2006), however he did not get the nomination."</item>
		<item>"Considers Fitzcarraldo (1982), One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (1975), and The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford (2007) among his personal favorite movies."</item>
		<item>"Domestic Partner: Angelina Jolie (2005 - present)."</item>
		<item>"Auditioned for the role of Mike in Phantasm II (1988) but director Don Coscarelli instead chose James LeGros."</item>
		<item>"Along with Angelina Jolie, he traveled to Syria and Jordan on a United Nations Goodwill visit to displaced Iraqi civilians. [October 2009]"</item>
		<item>"Friends with Clint Eastwood."</item>
		<item>"Met ex-fiancée Gwyneth Paltrow on the set of Se7en (1995)."</item>
		<item>"Was in a relationship with singer Sinitta Renay for two years during the 1980s."</item>
		<item>"Lives in Los Angeles, Malibu, Goleta, California, Benerville, France and New Orleans, Louisiana."</item>
		<item>"Ex-son-in-law of John Aniston and Nancy Dow."</item>
		<item>"Ex-stepson-in-law of Sherry Rooney."</item>
		<item>"He stands 5' 11" (1.80 m)."</item>
		<item>"Enjoys Architecture and Interior Design."</item>
		<item>"Is a vegetarian."</item>
		<item>"Is a member of the Sigma Chi Fraternity. "</item>
		<item>"Has six children with Angelina Jolie."</item>
		<item>"Owns a chatteau in France."</item>
		<item>"Has said he will not marry until same sex marriages are legalized."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
