<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Chris Brown and Rihanna have to be 50 yards from each other after imposed a stay-away order from the judge."</item>
		<item>"Chris avoided prison sentence by pleading guilty for assaulting his former girlfriend, Rihanna. "</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown was replaced by Justin Timberlake and Al Green, due to Chris not able to make 2009 Grammy Awards."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown was released on $50,000 bail the night of the Grammys."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown has hired celebrity lawyer Mark Geragos."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown was arrested after alleged Rihanna assault. "</item>
		<item>"Chris is ranked #67 in AIM's \"100 Celebs Under 25\"."</item>
		<item>"He collaborated with New Era to release his own line of Fitted Caps that he designed himself."</item>
		<item>"When he was 13, Chris moved to Harlem, New York and stayed with a friend's family while working on his career. "</item>
		<item>"Chris has worked with Columbus Short two times. They were both in Stomp the Yard and This Christmas."</item>
		<item>"Chris has performed in Switzerland, Denmark, France, England, and Sweden. "</item>
		<item>"He has a Ford Expedition."</item>
		<item>"He can skateboard."</item>
		<item>"In 2008, Chris was one of the hosts for the Math-A-Thon program."</item>
		<item>"Chris won 4 awards in the 2008 Teen Choice Awards. This includes Choice Hook-Up, Choice Male Artist, Choice RnB Artist, and Choice RnB Track."</item>
		<item>"As of July 2008, Chris is dating musical artist, Rihanna."</item>
		<item>"Chris is featured in the song \"No Air\" with Jordin Sparks."</item>
		<item>"Chris did a song with Lil Mama and T-Pain named \"Shawty Get Loose\"."</item>
		<item>"On June 3, 2008, Chris released his deluxe version of Exclusive, called Exclusive: Forever Edition."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown did a freestyle to the hit Lil Wayne song A Milli, in which he raps."</item>
		<item>"Chris co-wrote Rihanna's song, Disturbia."</item>
		<item>"Chris attended the Kids' Choice Awards 2008 on March 29th, 2008. There, he won Favorite Male Singer."</item>
		<item>"Chris' signature dance move is the moon walk."</item>
		<item>"Chris attended Essex High School in Tappahannock, Virginia."</item>
		<item>"The original title of Exclusive was going to be \"Graduation\", but since Kanye West had all ready had an album with that title, he named it Exclusive."</item>
		<item>"His song With You, on \"Exclusive\", was written by the artist, The-Dream. Swizz Beatz also wrote a song in his album \"Exclusive\". He wrote the song I'll Call Ya. "</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown describes himself as a creative, humble, and talented person."</item>
		<item>"He learned to dance by watching Michael Jackson on TV."</item>
		<item>"He used to be a point guard on his school's basketball team."</item>
		<item>"He likes playing basketball, dancing, and designing his own shirts. "</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown did a song with T-pain called Greatness. However, it is not on the Exclusive CD. "</item>
		<item>"Chris video \"With You\" was a bonus video on Notarized: Top 100 Videos of 2007. "</item>
		<item>"Chris was ranked #62 on Notarized: Top 100 Videos of 2007 for his music video \"Wall to Wall\"."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown and T-Pain have their second number one singles on that chart with the song \"Kiss Kiss\"."</item>
		<item>"The song \"Kiss Kiss\" was number one on The Billboard Hot 100 during the week of November 15, 2007, giving both Chris Brown and T-Pain their second number one singles on that chart."</item>
		<item>"Chris likes down-to-earth girls."</item>
		<item>"Chris was chosen as one of People Magazine's Sexiest Men Alive for 2007."</item>
		<item>"His album, Exclusive, was released on November 6, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Chris guest starred on an episode of Sesame Street on August 13, 2007. In the episode, Chris sang a duet with Elmo entitled \"See the Signs\"."</item>
		<item>"In most of his songs, Chris usually mentions that he is from Virginia."</item>
		<item>"On Chris' \"My Super Sweet 16\" episode, one of his parties was featured at the 40/40 nightclub in New York for friends, family and celebs."</item>
		<item>"Chris went in tour in October and November 2007 with Bow Wow, T-Pain, and Rihanna."</item>
		<item>"Chris left school in 2004 to work on his first album. He was homeschooled."</item>
		<item>"Chris began dancing at the age of 2."</item>
		<item>"Chris won the \"MTV Australia Video Music Award\" category in 2006 for his video, "\Run It!\". "</item>
		<item>"2006. On the tour, he raised over $50,000 for St. Jude's Hospital."</item>
		<item>"On August 17, 2006, Chris started his Up Close and Personal Tour which included artists Ne-Yo, Lil Wayne, Cherish, Juelz Santana, and Dem Franchise Boyz in Cincinatti."</item>
		<item>"On June 13, 2006, Chris Brown's DVD called Chris Brown's Journey was released. It had clips and features of him on his tour in the UK and Japan. It also showed him getting ready for the Grammy Awards."</item>
		<item>"Chris' manager is Tina Davis."</item>
		<item>"Chris was spending time with an aunt in Arkansas when he first took the stage, performing in local talent shows with his cousins. "</item>
		<item>"Chris is part of Jive Records. "</item>
		<item>"Chris came up with the concept for the video, \"Run It\"."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown became the first male solo artist to release a single that went straight to the top of the Billboard singles chart with his smash hit, \"Run It\"."</item>
		<item>"Chris appeared on My Super Sweet 16 (for him it was a super 18) where he had two parties; one for all fans to attend and a private soiree for friends and family."</item>
		<item>"In 2006, Chris won an NAACP Image Award for Oustanding New Artist."</item>
		<item>"Chris Brown appears in the remix of Rihanna and Jay Z's smash hit, \"Umbrella\"."</item>
		<item>"He has one sister."</item>
		<item>"Chris has a pitbull named Diamond."</item>
		<item>"Chris was chosen as one of People Magazine's Annual 100 Most Beautiful People in the World, in May 2007."</item>
		<item>"Chris was nominated for Favorite Male Singer in the Kids Choice Awards 2007."</item>
		<item>"Wins the award for Artist Of The Year, while at the same time also is named New Artist Of The Year and Male Artist Of The Year at the 2006 Billboard Music Awards."</item>
		<item>"His debut album's producers included Scott Storch, R. Kelly, and Jermaine Dupri."</item>
		<item>"He has several nicknames like Sizzle, Charlie Brown, and Booboo."</item>
		<item>"One of his embarassing moments was when on one of his shows and his shirt and hat came off when being pulled by fans into the crowd."</item>
		<item>"If he wasn't a singer he would be a basketball player or a regular kid."</item>
		<item>"Wants to work with Teairra Mari, Beyonce, Ciara, Usher, Michael Jackson, Mario, 50 Cent, Lil Wayne, and T.I."</item>
		<item>"His music influences are Sam Cook, Michael Jackson, Stevie Wonder, Usher, Kim Burrell, Donnie Hathaway, and Marvin Gaye."</item>
		<item>"He has been writing and producing his own songs since he was 14."</item>
		<item>"Chris was nominated for 2 Grammys at the 49th Annual Grammy Awards. There he performed his song \"Run It\"."</item>
		<item>"Chris' first single, Run It, was his most successful song on the Billboard Hot 100 Chart, spending 5 weeks at #1."</item>
		<item>"Chris appeared in Bow Wow's song and video \"Shortie Like Mine\"."</item>
		<item>"Chris' debut album went platinum two times."</item>
		<item>"In the 2006 Teen Choice Awards, Chris was nominated for Choice RnB Artist and Choice Male Hottie. He won Choice Male Breakout artist."</item>
		<item>"Chris first wanted to be a rapper, but noticed his singing talent at age 11 and decided not to."</item>
		<item>"Chris won Best Male Artist, Best Artist, and Best New Artist at the 2006 Billboard Awards."</item>
		<item>"In the BET Awards, his song, 'Yo (Excuse Me Miss)', won Viewer's Choice."</item>
		<item>"He says Lil JJ is a very good dancer. "</item>
		<item>"Chris once hosted Teenick with Megan Good."</item>
		<item>"Chris describes his personality as funny, outgoing, charismatic, and charming."</item>
		<item>"His favorite drink is Gatorade/Powerade."</item>
		<item>"His favorite sports teams are Miami Heat and Atlanta Falcons."</item>
		<item>"His favorite sports are basketball and football."</item>
		<item>"His favorite video game just happens to be Grand Theft Auto(San Andreas)."</item>
		<item>"His favorite clothing brand is Bathing Ape(Bape)."</item>
		<item>"Chris was nominated for Favorite Male Soul/RnB Artist at the 2006 American Music Awards."</item>
		<item>"Chris says he has a crush on singer/actress Vanessa Anne Hudgens."</item>
		<item>"Chris was first discovered at a gas station when he was 11."</item>
		<item>"Chris has 5 tattoos."</item>
		<item>"On his right arm he has Jesus with music notes to symbolize his gratitude towards God for giving him the gift of singing."</item>
		<item>"On his left arm he has his first initial \"C\" with a hand under it and two stars on the sides."</item>
		<item>"On his left arm he has a spray can with a 2 ups and 2 downs sign which stands for \"VA\", which means Virginia, his hometown."</item>
		<item>"He has 3 stars behind his right ear."</item>
		<item>"He has a skull with a halo on his right hand."</item>
		<item>"Chris owns over 500 sneakers."</item>
		<item>"His parents are divorced."</item>
		<item>"His favorite dessert is Strawberry Cheesecake."</item>
		<item>"Chris doesn't want to be one of those guys who has to take off his shirt for girls to like him."</item>
		<item>"His favorite subject in school is math."</item>
		<item>"Chris likes the casual, hip-hop clothing style."</item>
		<item>"His song 'Say Goodbye' is featured on the soundtrack for the 2006 movie Step Up."</item>
		<item>"Chris stands 6'2" (1.88)."</item>
		<item>"His debut single Run It! is produced by Scott Storch, who also wrote, produced and contributed to most of Brown's self titled debut album. Run It was his first #1 hit and was released on November 5, 2005."</item>
        <item>"His favorite food is spaghetti."</item>
        <item>"His favorite dessert is Strawberry Cheesecake."</item>
        <item>"His favorite sweet snack is chocolate."</item>
        <item>"His Favorite candy is Starburst."</item>
        <item>"His favorite books are comic books by Marvel."</item>
				
	</string-array>
</resources>
