<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Lady Gaga cites Queen and David Bowie as creative inspirtaions."</item>
	<item>"Her stage name comes from Queen's hit /"Radio Ga Ga/"."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite fashion designers are Donatella Versace and Peggy Bundy."</item>
	<item>"According to an interview with /"Rolling Stone/", Gaga goes pants-less so that her nearly blind grandmother will be able to see her when she is on TV."</item>
	<item>"Gaga refers to her listeners as her /"little monsters/" and considers them to be a major part of the support network."</item>
	<item>"Gaga once purchased $1,000 worth of Papa John's pizza for her fans that were waiting in line for autographs."</item>
	<item>"Lady Gaga thought herself how to play piano by ear when she was 4 years old."</item>
	<item>"She is a classically trained pianist."</item>
	<item>"/"Haus of Gaga/" is the name she gave to the crew that works with her, which includes stage designers, sound artists, clothes designers, and visual artists."</item>
	<item>"Lady gaga dropped out of NYU."</item>
	<item>"After leaving school, she performed in burlesque shows on the Lower East Side of New York."</item>
	<item>"Gaga also appeared on a 2008 episode of /"The Hills/". Before performance, her broken cat-suit zipper was fixed by Whitney Port and Lauren Conrad."</item>
	<item>"Lady Gaga often carries purple teacup and saucer in public. /"I drank tea with my mom, so teacups make me feel at home/", she said."</item>
	<item>"On June 11th, 2009, Gaga scored the cover of /"Rolling Stone/" magazine's coveted annual /"Hot List/" issue."</item>
	<item>"She was voted the fasion icon of 2009."</item>
	<item>"Lady Gaga was born Joane Steffani Germanotta."</item>
	<item>"She was known for shocking babysitters as a child by showing up to greet them nude."</item>
	<item>"Socialites Paris and Nicky Hilton attended the same school as Gaga, and ended up becoming big fans"</item>
	<item>"Kermit the Frog was on damage control after being caught kissing Gaga at the 2009 MTV Video Music Awards."</item>
	<item>"Gaga attended the Tisch School of the Arts at New York University. She was one of twenty people to gain early admission."</item>
	<item>"She was originally hired by a record label to write songs for other artists. "</item>
	<item>"Even in 2006, Lady Gaga was performing in New York City clubs with the Stefani Germanotta Band, or SGBand. Video footage shows her wearing a normal shirt and pants!"</item>
	<item>"She was born on March 28, 1986."</item>
	<item>"During her early time at Interscope, she worked as a songwriter for fellow label artists and captured the attention of Akon, who recognized her vocal abilities, and signed her to his own label, Kon Live Distribution."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite color is lavender."</item>
	<item>"She has natural brown hair."</item>
	<item>"She has green eyes."</item>
	<item>"She loves to cook."</item>
	<item>"She loves Italian food especially pasta."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite song from The Fame was Paparazzi and her favorite song for The Fame Monster is Speechless."</item>
	<item>"She has 6 tattoos."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: Peace sign on her left wrist."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: Rilke quote on her left inner bicep."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: White daisies on her left shoulder blade."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: /"Tokyo Love/" on her left shoulder blade."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: Small heart with /"Dad/" written in it on her left shoulder."</item>
	<item>"Her Tattoos: Roses and vines on her lower back on the left side (she originally had a small treble cleft there but she got the roses and vines to cover it up)."</item>
	<item>"Never lip-syncs."</item>
	<item>"She grew up in Manhattan."</item>
	<item>"She is a Catholic."</item>
	<item>"She went to a all girls Catholic school, Convent of the Sacred Heart (the same school Paris Hilton went to)."</item>
	<item>"Lady Gagas parents names are Cynthia and Joseph Germanotta and her sister is Natali Germanotta."</item> 
	<item>"Lady Gaga, who made Time magazine’s 100 Most Important People list but failed to show up to the swanky party, is a force to be reckoned with."</item>
	<item>"She is creative, talented, totally hypnotic and sometimes even a wee bit eerie. Oh and did we mention that she isn’t always the confident cat she portrays herself to be?"</item>
	<item>"Just prior to taking to the stage at the Met Costume Institute Gala earlier this week Gaga had a bad case of stage fright and refused to perform. Luckily Oprah Winfrey was there and she managed to coax the singer back on stage."</item>
	<item>"While many of us would love to travel back in time to retake our ghastly school photos, Lady Gaga is among the select few who ended up looking flawless between the pages of her high school yearbook. Can you believe this is the same woman who was covered in blood during the 2009 VMAs?"</item>
	<item>"At 13 she had successfully written her first ballad, and the following year she began to perform during open mike nights at various clubs in New York."</item>
	<item>"Gaga was frequently teased by her classmates due to her highly unconventional style, although the snickering didn’t stop her from doing what she wanted to do."</item>
	<item>"Gaga is the Johnny Depp of the music world (i.e., she treats her fans the way she would want to be treated)."</item>
	<item>"Kermit the Frog later told People that the lip lock was 100 percent innocent and that Gaga /"is a wonderful person/"."</item>
	<item>"/"In private, she is very down to earth ... which is where I spend most of my time,/" Kermie croaked. /“As far as kissing Lady Gaga goes: she is a very good kisser, but it was not a romantic kiss. It was a kiss for good luck. Kissing a frog is good luck for the person giving the kiss – but bad luck for the frog if his pig finds out./""</item>
	<item>"Like True Blood’s Anna Paquin, Lady Gaga has admitted to being bisexual. Her hit tune /"Poker Face/" is about falling for both men and women, a trait which has landed her in hot water with more than a few boyfriends."</item>
	<item>"Gaga’s sexual orientation is neither here nor there however, as she is currently abstaining from all forms of sex. And, she has encouraged her followers to do the same, which has our beloved Mean Betty in quite a tizzy!"</item>
	<item>"What does Gaga possess that Amy Winehouse doesn’t? The ability to abuse dangerous substances, sell millions of albums, and never feel the need to drop a dime on another bag again."</item>
	<item>"Before making it into the big leagues, Gaga spent hours alone in her New York apartment, listening to The Cure and snorting bag after bag of cocaine."</item>
	<item>"In may 2010 the 24-year-old singer surprised a couple of newlyweds by initiating a photo op (the bride even got a kiss on the cheek from Gaga!) after she happened across the reception at the Intercontinental Hotel in Adelaide, Australia."</item>
	<item>"Released on August 19, 2008, her debut album, 'The Fame' reached number one in the UK, Canada, Austria, Germany and Ireland as well as accomplishing positions within the top-ten in numerous countries worldwide; in the United States, it peaked at number two on the 'Billboard 200' Chart."</item>
	<item>"By the fourth quarter of the 2009, she had released her second album, The Fame Monster."</item>
	<item>"She has also stated fashion is a source of inspiration for her songwriting and performances."</item>
	<item>"Gaga was ranked the 73rd Artist of the 2000–10 decade by 'Billboard'."</item>
	<item>"As of August 2010, Gaga has sold more than 15 million albums and 51 million singles worldwide."</item>
	<item>"In May 2010, Time magazine included Gaga in its annual Time 100 list of the most influential people in the world."</item>
	<item>"In June 2010, 'Forbes' listed Gaga fourth on its list of the 100 Most Powerful and Influential celebrities in the world."</item>
	<item>"She is also ranked as the second most powerful musician in the world."</item>
	<item>"Gaga's trademarks are her hair bow, her platinum blond hair, her futuristic outfits."</item>
	<item>"She carries a glow-in-the-dark disco stick during performances."</item>
	<item>"Lady Gaga always features two Great Danes in her music videos."</item>
	<item>"She often portrays herself as a rebel in her videos."</item>
	<item>"She used to be a go-go dancer."</item>
	<item>"She states that she is /"very into fashion/" and that it is /"everything/"."</item>
	<item>"Her song /"Boys, Boys, Boys/" was inspired by Motlue Crue's hit /"Girls, Girls, Girls/"."</item>
	<item>"Her parents are Joseph, an Internet entrepreneur, and Cynthia, a telecommunications assistant."</item>
	<item>"On February 20, 2009, she donated tickets and a meet and greet, for any show on her Fame Ball tour, in the US or Canada, to raise money for Odyssey Charter School and elementary schools in Los Angeles affected by budget cuts."</item>
	<item>"She is a natural brunette, but bleached her hair blonde in light of the fact that she was being mistaken for Amy Winehouse by interviewers while trying to make it big."</item>
	<item>"She has a contralto vocal range."</item>
	<item>"Her song /"Telephone/" was originally written for Britney Spears' sixth album Circus. However, after it failed to make the album's final track listing, Gaga recorded the song as a collaboration with Beyonce Knowles for her second album, The Fame Monster."</item>
	<item>"She is a big fan of Britney Spears."</item>
</string-array>
</resources>
