<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Aubrey has a small role in the movie, Charlie Bartlett alongside Lauren Collins (Paige) and Jake Epstein (Craig)."</item>
		<item>"He's in the Trey Songz video \"Wonder Woman\"."</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's favorite places are Los Angelos and Montreal. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey Graham appeared on Soul Food as Fredrick. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's dream car is a Rolls Royce Phantoms. "</item>
		<item>"The issue Aubrey feels strongly about is the genocide taking place in Darfur. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's celebrity crushes are Meagan Good and Eva Mendes."</item>
		<item>"Aubrey loves shooting scenes with Adamo, Andrea, Lauren and Stacey. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey wasn't playing Jimmy on Degrassi: The Next Generation, he would love to play Hazel, although she is a girl. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey would like to own his own record company. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey would love to work with Aaron Meeks, Vivica A. Fox, Denzel Washington, and Shadia Simmons in the future. "</item>
		<item>"In 2002 and 2003, Aubrey won a Young Artist Award for Best Ensemble in a TV Series (Comedy or Drama) for his role on Degrassi: The Next Generation. "</item>
		<item>"In 2005, Aubrey was nominated for a Young Artist Award for Outstanding Young Performers in a TV Series for Degrassi: The Next Generation. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's favorite band is N.E.R.D. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey is of African American and Caucasian ancestry."</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's nicknames are Aub and Drake. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's astrological sign is a Scorpio."</item>
		<item>"Aubrey is 6'3½". "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey used to go school with Miriam McDonald, who plays Emma, and Cassie Steele, who plays Manny from Degrassi: The Next Generation. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's Idols are Pharell Williams and Denzel Washington. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey once hosted TeeNick with his friend Stacey Farber, who plays Ellie on Degrassi: The Next Generation. "</item>
		<item>"During season 3, Aubrey dated Andrea Lewis (Hazel from Degrassi: The Next Generation). "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey appeared on The-N's reality dating show, Best Friend's Date, with his Degrassi: The Next Generation co-star Stacey Farber and his friend Ali Mukkadam."</item>
		<item>"Aubrey's favorite sport is basketball. He even wants to play 1 on 1 against Bow Wow sometime. "</item>
		<item>"Aubrey is friends with Ali Mukkadam, who plays Ray in Radio Free Roscoe and has made a guest appearance on Degrassi: The Next Generation. "</item>
		<item>"He lives in Toronto, Ontario."</item>
		<item>"Favorite book is the autobiography of Quincy Jones."</item>
		<item>"Favorite movies are Rounders and Two can play that game"</item>
		<item>"Aubrey Graham appeared on Soul Food as Fredrick. "</item>
		<item>"Often considered as the new version of The Fresh Prince a.k.a Will Smith."</item>
		<item>"Won 2002 Young Artist Awards for his role in Canadian TV series \"Degrassi: The Next Generation\"."</item>
		<item>"Is Lil Wayne's protege. "</item>
		<item>"Attended Forest Hill Public School"</item>
		<item>"Attended Forest Hill Collegiate Institute, Toronto, Ontario"</item>
		<item>"Aubrey Drake Graham a.k.a Drake was raised only by his mother in Toronto, Canada since he was just five because his parents got divorced."</item>
		<item>"He had started writing songs since he was ten years old. "</item>
		<item>"He began his career in showbiz industry as a small screen actor."</item>
		<item>"Drake was born on October 24, 1986"</item>
		<item>"Drake got his first role as a junior high schooler named Jimmy Brooks on Canadian teen drama TV series "Degrassi: The Next Generation"."</item>
		<item>"He got more roles in such TV series as \"Soul Food\", \"Conviction\", \"Best Friend's Date\", \"The Borders\", \"Sophie\" and \"Being Erica\"."</item>
		<item>"In February 2006, he released his first indie mixtape titled \"Room for Improvement\". "</item>
		<item>"Drake developed close relationship with Lil Wayne and became his protege after making a collaboration with the rap mogul on a remix of song \"Man of the Year\"."</item>
		<item>"Drake once dated songstress Keshia Chante."</item>
		<item>"Following his break-up with Keshia Chante, he crafted a song called \"Deceiving\", making reference to her mother Tessa. "</item>
		<item>"In 2009, Drake was rumored to embark on a love relationship with Rihanna."</item>
		<item>"Drake is the son of Dennis Graham, a drummer who worked with Jerry Lee Lewis and the nephew of musicians Larry Graham and Teenie Hodges."</item>
		<item>"Drake attended high school at Forest Hill Collegiate Institute, where he began acting, but did not graduate."</item>
		<item>"Drake was inspired to become an actor because of Denzel Washington"</item>
		<item>"Drake was on Degrassi for 8 seasons from 2001-2009."</item>
		<item>"Drake has done commercial work for GMC, Sears, M.A.C. and Toys’R'Us."</item>
		<item>"Drake likes Jay-Z, N.E.R.D, Pharell, Usher, Kanye West, Frank Sinatra and Al Green."</item>
		<item>"Drake is good friends with many of his Degrassi cast-mates, particularly Shane Kippel, who played his best friend Spinner Mason on the show."</item>
		<item>"Drake is a fan of the Kentucky Wildcats and a friend to head coach John Calipari."</item>
		<item>"Drake was nominated for 2 Grammy Awards without an album even being released."</item>
		<item>"The first time Drake realized that his music was getting out was when he saw a bootlegger selling his So Far Gone mixtape in New Orleans. "</item>
		<item>"Drake doesn't understand the retro fashion trend, calling it \"wack\"."</item>
		<item>"He told Seventeen that his dream job is to be a King magazine photographer. "</item>
		<item>"His favorite fast food is McDonald's. "</item>
		<item>"Drake's uncle played bass for Prince. "</item>
		<item>"When Lil Wayne spit one of Drake's verses at the VMAs, Drake wasn't there to actually see the moment. He was stuck outside the VMAs because he'd been given the wrong pass."</item>
		<item>"In the PC vs. Mac wars, Drake is a Mac. "</item>
		<item>"The third single from the album, Miss M”, featuring Lil Wayne, was released on June 1, 2010. It has reached No. 15 on the Hot 100."</item>
		<item>"On June 15, 25,000 fans gathered at New York’s South Street Seaport for a free concert by Drake and Hanson. A near riot ensued after police canceled the show due to over-flowing crowds."</item>
		<item>"The album, Thank Me Later sold 447,000 records in its first week, reaching No. 1 on the Billboard 200"</item>
		<item>"Drake hosted the first annual Ovo (October’s Very Own) Festival. In that festival he brought out the VIP list of rap stars including: Jay-Z, Eminem, Rick Ross, Young Jeezy, Bun B and Fabolous."</item>
		<item>"In February 2006, Drake released his first mixtape Room for Improvement. It was made available via his website and official MySpace page."</item>
		<item>"Graham started gaining popularity when he did his first song with Lil Wayne, a remix of the already popular song “Man of the Year” which Wayne didn’t rap in but had ad-libs in the end of the song."</item>
		<item>"Drake has also written for Jazz Cartier, Bishop Brigante and Dr. Dre."</item>
		<item>"Even after their short-lived Twitter marriage, Nicki Minaj and Drizzy Drake remain great friends. "</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
