<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I got the, the gift of gad, somethin that you wish you had, Don't even get a strap now I'd rather kick a rap."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, free livin', I swear, I be on some hippie shit. But gateway fresher than the hippies did."</item>
		<item>"Oh yeah this life is good, don't let it all go to waste."</item>
		<item>"I don't wanna be inside today, just keep it rollin like we ridin' skates I got a happy of haze. So i'm thinkin we gon' get high today, And let the sun shine all in my face."</item>
		<item>"My life's a topic of a lullabye."</item>
		<item>"I ain't got a damn thing on my mind and baby all we got is time, lets just watch the clouds go by."</item>
		<item>"5-star chefs stay cooking in the kitchen but only making that good shit, see the way im living they like oh my goodness."</item>
		<item>"Tonight might be the night i make it so lets live it up and don't regret it at all."</item>
		<item>"Being broke starts to get a little old. My money had to get some fine tunin."</item>
		<item>"We just some motha fuckin' kids."</item>
		<item>"It's hard to say that I'd rather stay awake when I'm a sleep."</item>
		<item>"I say it feels just like a dream 'bout to wake up from a nap."</item>
		<item>"Yeah they give me money but I gotta go and spend it Man, I been a bad little jew but I gotta pay the bills now so I gotta chill out I ain't walkin round like I'm splurging wit a mil now."</item>
		<item>"Celebrate that we seein' another day, life good."</item>
		<item>"If you ever hated anticipate that I'm famous."</item>
		<item>"Me I'm highly underestimated, so educated that gettin paid quick."</item>
		<item>"Everything is never as it seems."</item>
		<item>"It's hard to say that I'd rather stay awake when I'm a sleep."</item>
		<item>"No disrespect though, I gotta get that cigarette flow for the green pesto, presto."</item>
		<item>"So these funny little girls wanna take a trip. But no, only the M.O.S.T. dope with me other fools home or, boy? and cig free."</item>
		<item>"I'm the youngen hoes tryna make a baby with 'cause it'll make 'em rich."</item>
		<item>"Girl I don't wanna share you. We could be together, but you scared to."</item>
		<item>"I know this girl who want the world to call her own. Goin through these dudes like some minutes on a phone. And once she leave She ain't comin back home."</item>
		<item>"Shorty just attacked me from the blindside. Used to be a player now I'm sidelined. Connect like wi-fi, Mixed like tye-dye."</item>
		<item>"They told me never fall in love, It never works out in your favor. You way too young and right now that's just human nature."</item>
		<item>"Catch me smoking weed where the Wild things are."</item>
		<item>"Shorty just attacked me from the blindside. Used to be a player now I'm sidelined. Connect like wi-fi, Mixed like tye-dye."</item>
		<item>"Can't believe they eyes swear it's just a mirage."</item>
		<item>"Ain't ever seen a young rapper like moi."</item>
		<item>"That was all gravy but I knew I wanted more."</item>
		<item>"Every single summer takin trips to the shore."</item>
		<item>"Used to go to school hang with friends and play sports."</item>
		<item>"Yeah I live a life pretty similar to yours."</item>
		<item>"Weed got me laughin like a damn hyena."</item>
		<item>"Dream of rockin crowds."</item>
		<item>"It's a work of art I ain't talkin mona lisa."</item>
		<item>"Hey kool aid and frozen pizza."</item>
		<item>"The can't understand my concept."</item>
		<item>"Bout to be in music stores everywhere but not yet."</item>
		<item>"Cali for the kush cause boy I know there's plenty there."</item>
		<item>"So I can go anywhere."</item>
		<item>"Well a little more cash and my own fast jet."</item>
		<item>"Could I want that I don't have yet."</item>
		<item>"A couple trophies on my shelf so what else."</item>
		<item>"So far I've done pretty well for myself."</item>
		<item>"I ain't gonna need those I'm a go hard."</item>
		<item>"Still got my training wheels in the garage."</item>
		<item>"I'm feelin like this could be my last shot."</item>
		<item>"I don't even talk about it boy I just do it."</item>
		<item>"I smoke herb and I make music."</item>
		<item>"Everything I drop recorded by big jerm."</item>
		<item>"If you didn't know well I'm from the BURGH."</item>
		<item>"Companies send me clothes so I'm wearin em."</item>
		<item>"Clean conscience good Samaritan."</item>
		<item>"These blogs gotta know I'm on next."</item>
		<item>"Haven't had a fall yet."</item>
		<item>"I been climbin up the great wall."</item>
		<item>"Takin' sips from the fountain of youth, if you ain't heard about the kid then you outta the loop!"</item>
		<item>"Just some mother fuckin' kids!"</item>
		<item>"So take it while you got it try to get a little more they say im gettin better than i ever been before, well thats for sure, tell em what i do rap, keep me fed like a spoon gettin soup."</item>
		<item>"Its all good everybody tryin to eat tonight, tryna go to sleep, have good dreams tonight."</item>
		<item>"So ive been fucking all these hoes, and ive been blowin all this cash and baby this just the beginning, ima make all of it back."</item>
		<item>"Im a fuckin workaholic with a passion in my heart treatin rappin as an art which you have to be a part of. I just copped a new car to hear its all up try to do the right thing, please karma."</item>
		<item>"So i can feel, but i cant touch? You said my love was a bit too much. Broke my heart cant find no crush. So why dont you come on back home?"</item>
		<item>"I aint here, i guess you cant call back sex, drugs and rock and roll, i think ill take all that."</item>
		<item>"Ive been out here on the road, now they missin me at home, all these ex girls that i used to know are hittin up my phone."</item>
		<item>"Im on the road, my girl so sad Im gone. Its hard when I cant even find the time to call my mom."</item>
		<item>"Been working all my life to do some different stuff. For people to say Im young and havent lived enough."</item>
		<item>"Dealing with everybodys opinion. Trying to do me. Only down one, Im in the final Shooting threes."</item>
		<item>"Go ham, like Abraham reading all the signs. Oh yeah, and dont forget to call your moms."</item>
		<item>"The movie never stopped the frank changeover. We add a map to the wolfpack: hangover."</item>
		<item>"So gangsta, like the occupation of Made Men. Creating chaos, my operation is Mayhem."</item>
		<item>"Word. Im so sick with the verbs I use. The words to heal us. They love how I kill it on stage, man. Murder theaters."</item>
		<item>"Now I think Im cool cause I got a pair of shoes. A mug dog, a jacket with a Polo logo. My cup always filled with Henny. So no Four Loko."</item>
		<item>"Drums with a pump like some Reeboks. See me from the treetops. They worry but they need not. Heating like a teapot."</item>
		<item>"Is what Ive become, young and Im dumb Been spending cake to get some bump in the trunk."</item>
		<item>"Take over the world when Im on my Donald Trump shit, look at all this money, aint that some shit."</item>
		<item>"Hit strip clubs find bitches with big butts. I dont give a fuck Im getting drunk, only live once."</item>
		<item>"Marijuana for everybody in yamakas. I dont give a fuck till my homies put some bottles up."</item>
		<item>"Bill Clinton pimping, always with a Monica. Days Inn.. turn that shit to hotel erotica."</item>
		<item>"I aint got time for all the problems, no I never did my trig smile on my face got me feeling like the shit."</item>
		<item>"I aint give a fuck, I hear em talking I dont listen Im up. In the clouds looking down, I aint even in a rush."</item>
		<item>"I been laughed at, hated on, no one would even play my songs. Wouldnt even listen to anything that my name was on."</item>
		<item>"I just wanna ride, ride through the city in a Cutlass. Find a big butt bitch, somewhere get my nuts kissed."</item>
		<item>"You know how much you love it when you get it in abundance. Give a f-ck about a budget when you always be the subject of discussion."</item>
		<item>"Ay yo, the flyest mutha-fcka up in the room. Yeah, you know its me. Bitches hating on him, cause he started out here locally. Hopefully, Ill be at the top soon."</item>
		<item>"Some people just need to stop thinking about everything they do and just do it."</item>
		<item>"People tend to think all the drinks on me. I don't even have no money to spare to buy patron for you and all your friends."</item>
				
	</string-array>
</resources>
