<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="MichaelJackson">
        <item>1|100|And I remember going to the record studio and there was a park across the street and I\'d see all the children playing and I would cry because it would make me sad that I would have to work instead.</item>
        <item>2|100|Because I think every child star suffers through this period because you\'re not the cute and charming child that you were. You start to grow, and they want to keep you little forever.</item>
        <item>3|100|Because I wanted to have a place that I could create everything that I that I never had as a child. So, you see rides. You see animals. There\'s a movie theater.</item>
        <item>4|100|Because parents have power over children. They feel they have to do what their parents say. But the love of money is the root of all evil. And this is a sweet child. And to see him turn like this, this isn\'t him. This is not him.</item>
        <item>5|100|Before I would hurt a child, I would slit my wrists.</item>
        <item>6|100|But I will never stop helping and loving people the way Jesus said to.</item>
        <item>7|100|Children show me in their playful smiles the divine in everyone. This simple goodness shines straight from their hearts and only asks to be lived.</item>
        <item>8|100|Elizabeth Taylor is gorgeous, beautiful, and she still is today, I\'m crazy about her.</item>
        <item>9|100|Everyone who knows me will know the truth, which is that my children come first in my life and that I would never harm any child.</item>
        <item>10|100|Everything that I love is behind those gates. We have elephants, and giraffes, and crocodiles, and every kind of tigers and lions. And - and we have bus loads of kids, who don\'t get to see those things. They come up sick children, and enjoy it.</item>
        <item>11|100|I have a skin disorder that destroys the pigmentation of my skin, it\'s something that I cannot help, OK?</item>
        <item>12|100|I just wish I could understand my father.</item>
        <item>13|100|I love my family very much. I wish I could see them a little more often than I do. But we understand because we\'re a show business family and we all work.</item>
        <item>14|100|I rememeber one time we were getting ready to go to South America and everything was packed up and in the car ready to go and I hid and I was crying because I really did not want to go, I wanted to play. I did not want to go.</item>
        <item>15|100|I was a veteran, before I was a teenager.</item>
        <item>16|100|I will say again that I have never, and would never, harm a child. It sickens me that people have written untrue things about me.</item>
        <item>17|100|I\'m a black American, I am proud of my race. I am proud of who I am. I have a lot of pride and dignity.</item>
        <item>18|100|I\'m happy to be alive, I\'m happy to be who I am.</item>
        <item>19|100|I\'m just like anyone. I cut and I bleed. And I embarass easily.</item>
        <item>20|100|I\'m never pleased with anything, I\'m a perfectionist, it\'s part of who I am.</item>
        <item>21|100|I\'ve helped many, many, many children, thousands of children, cancer kids, leukemia kids.</item>
        <item>22|100|If you enter this world knowing you are loved and you leave this world knowing the same, then everything that happens in between can be dealt with.</item>
        <item>23|100|It\'s a complete lie, why do people buy these papers? It\'s not the truth I\'m here to say. You know, don\'t judge a person, do not pass judgement, unless you have talked to them one on one. I don\'t care what the story is, do not judge them because it is a lie.</item>
        <item>24|100|Just because it\'s in print doesn\'t mean it\'s the gospel.</item>
        <item>25|100|Let us dream of tomorrow where we can truly love from the soul, and know love as the ultimate truth at the heart of all creation.</item>
        <item>26|100|Me and Janet really are two different people.</item>
        <item>27|100|My mother\'s wonderful. To me she\'s perfection.</item>
        <item>28|100|People write negatives things, cause they feel that\'s what sells. Good news to them, doesn\'t sell.</item>
        <item>29|100|Please keep an open mind and let me have my day in court.</item>
        <item>30|100|The Bee Gees who are brilliant, I just love great music.</item>
        <item>31|100|The greatest education in the world is watching the masters at work.</item>
        <item>32|100|The meaning of life is contained in every single expression of life. It is present in the infinity of forms and phenomena that exist in all of creation.</item>
        <item>33|100|There were times when I had great times with my brothers, pillow fights and things, but I was, used to always cry from loneliness.</item>
        <item>34|100|They did it to try and belittle me, to try and to take away my pride. But I went through the whole system with them. And at the end, I - I wanted the public to know that I was okay, even though I was hurting.</item>
        <item>35|100|Well Brooke, I\'ve always liked her, and when I was little I used to stay with Diana Ross, me and my brothers stayed with her for years and I never said, but I always had a crush on her.</item>
        <item>36|100|Well, especially now I come to realize - and then - I would do my schooling which was three hours with a tutor and right after that I would go to the recording studio and record, and I\'d record for hours and hours until it\'s time to go to sleep.</item>
        <item>37|100|Well, you don\'t get to do things that other children get to do, having friends and slumber parties and buddies. There were none of that for me. I didn\'t have friends when I was little. My brothers were my friends.</item>
        <item>38|100|When I see children, I see the face of God. That\'s why I love them so much. That\'s what I see.</item>
        <item>39|100|Why can\'t you share your bed? The most loving thing to do is to share your bed with someone. It\'s very charming. It\'s very sweet. It\'s what the whole world should do.</item>
        <item>40|100|Yeah, Wacko Jacko, where did that come from? Some English tabloid. I have a heart and I have feelings. I feel that when you do that to me. It\'s not nice.</item>
        <item>41|100|Yes, and I had pimples so badly it used to make me so shy. I used not to look at myself. I\'d hide my face in the dark, I wouldn\'t want to look in the mirror and my father teased me and I just hated it and I cried everyday.</item>
        <item>42|100|You know, let\'s put it this way, if all the people in Hollywood who have had plastic surgery, if they went on vacation, there wouldn\'t be a person left in town.</item>
        <item>43|100|In a world filled with hate, we must still dare to hope. In a world filled with anger, we must still dare to comfort. In a world filled with despair, we must still dare to dream. And in a world filled with distrust, we must still dare to believe.</item>
        <item>44|100|The meaning of life is contained in every single expression of life. It is present in the infinity of forms and phenomena that exist in all of creation.</item>
        <item>45|100|I wake up from dreams and go "Wow, put this down on paper." The whole thing is strange. You hear the words, everything is right there in front of your face . . .</item>
        <item>46|100|The greatest education in the world is watching the masters at work.</item>
        <item>47|100|If you enter this world knowing you are loved and you leave this world knowing the same, then everything that happens in between can be dealt with.</item>
        <item>48|100|Lies run sprints, but the truth runs marathons. The truth will win this marathon in court.</item>
        <item>49|100|And my goal in life is to give to the world what I was lucky to receive: the ecstasy of divine union through my music and my dance.</item>
        <item>50|100|Why can\'t you share your bed? The most loving thing to do is to share your bed with someone. It\'s very charming. It\'s very sweet. It\'s what the whole world should do.</item>
        <item>51|100|I changed. People change.</item>
        <item>52|100|Smooth, but not a criminal.</item>
        <item>53|100|People who grew up as child stars have the same thing in common. You\'re cute, they love you - you go through the awkward stage, they don\'t accept you any more. Very few make the transition to adult star.</item>
        <item>54|100|Ground water has always been the property of the landowner, with the idea that water can be used for the benefit of the land.</item>
        <item>55|100|Sorry, guys. I\'m under the gag order.</item>
        <item>56|100|All of Hollywood has plastic surgery. I don\'t know why they point me out. The press exaggerated it. It\'s just my nose, you know. They want it to be everything. Just the nose isn\'t enough.</item>
        <item>57|100|There\'s a Mother\'s Day and there\'s a Father\'s Day, but there\'s no Children\'s Day. It would mean a lot. World peace.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="AbrahamLinkoln">
        <item>101|100|Better to remain silent and be thought a fool than to speak out and remove all doubt.</item>
        <item>102|100|America will never be destroyed from the outside. If we falter and lose our freedoms, it will be because we destroyed ourselves.</item>
        <item>103|100|Labor is prior to, and independent of, capital. Capital is only the fruit of labor, and could never have existed if labor had not first existed. Labor is the superior of capital, and deserves much the higher consideration.</item>
        <item>104|100|Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.</item>
        <item>105|100|A friend is one who has the same enemies as you have.</item>
        <item>106|100|All that I am, or hope to be, I owe to my angel mother.</item>
        <item>107|100|Any people anywhere, being inclined and having the power, have the right to rise up, and shake off the existing government, and form a new one that suits them better. This is a most valuable - a most sacred right - a right, which we hope and believe, is to liberate the world.</item>
        <item>108|100|In the end, it\'s not the years in your life that count. It\'s the life in your years.</item>
        <item>109|100|You can fool all the people some of the time, and some of the people all the time, but you cannot fool all the people all the time.</item>
        <item>110|100|Character is like a tree and reputation like a shadow. The shadow is what we think of it; the tree is the real thing.</item>
        <item>111|100|Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man\'s character, give him power.</item>
        <item>112|100|Government of the people, by the people, for the people, shall not perish from the Earth.</item>
        <item>113|100|This country, with its institutions, belongs to the people who inhabit it. Whenever they shall grow weary of the existing government, they can exercise their constitutional right of amending it, or exercise their revolutionary right to overthrow it.</item>
        <item>114|100|A woman is the only thing I am afraid of that I know will not hurt me.</item>
        <item>115|100|We the people are the rightful masters of both Congress and the courts, not to overthrow the Constitution but to overthrow the men who pervert the Constitution.</item>
        <item>116|100|Sir, my concern is not whether God is on our side; my greatest concern is to be on God\'s side, for God is always right.</item>
        <item>117|100|I remember my mother\'s prayers and they have always followed me. They have clung to me all my life.</item>
        <item>118|100|A house divided against itself cannot stand.</item>
        <item>119|100|Am I not destroying my enemies when I make friends of them?</item>
        <item>120|100|Don\'t interfere with anything in the Constitution. That must be maintained, for it is the only safeguard of our liberties.</item>
        <item>121|100|am not bound to win, but I am bound to be true. I am not bound to succeed, but I am bound to live by the light that I have. I must stand with anybody that stands right, and stand with him while he is right, and part with him when he goes wrong.</item>
        <item>122|100|Be sure you put your feet in the right place, then stand firm.</item>
        <item>123|100|Give me six hours to chop down a tree and I will spend the first four sharpening the axe.</item>
        <item>124|100|Allow the president to invade a neighboring nation, whenever he shall deem it necessary to repel an invasion, and you allow him to do so whenever he may choose to say he deems it necessary for such a purpose - and you allow him to make war at pleasure.</item>
        <item>125|100|I am a firm believer in the people. If given the truth, they can be depended upon to meet any national crisis. The great point is to bring them the real facts.</item>
        <item>126|100|Things may come to those who wait, but only the things left by those who hustle.</item>
        <item>127|100|Most folks are as happy as they make up their minds to be.</item>
        <item>128|100|The dogmas of the quiet past are inadequate to the stormy present. The occasion is piled high with difficulty, and we must rise with the occasion. As our case is new, so we must think anew and act anew.</item>
        <item>129|100|How many legs does a dog have if you call the tail a leg? Four. Calling a tail a leg doesn\'t make it a leg.</item>
        <item>130|100|When I do good, I feel good. When I do bad, I feel bad. That\'s my religion.</item>
        <item>131|100|As I would not be a slave, so I would not be a master. This expresses my idea of democracy.</item>
        <item>132|100|The best thing about the future is that it comes one day at a time.</item>
        <item>133|100|Common looking people are the best in the world: that is the reason the Lord makes so many of them.</item>
        <item>134|100|All my life I have tried to pluck a thistle and plant a flower wherever the flower would grow in thought and mind.</item>
        <item>135|100|You cannot escape the responsibility of tomorrow by evading it today.</item>
        <item>136|100|I don\'t like that man. I must get to know him better.</item>
        <item>137|100|Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves.</item>
        <item>138|100|To sin by silence when they should protest makes cowards of men.</item>
        <item>139|100|I destroy my enemies when I make them my friends.</item>
        <item>140|100|I do the very best I know how - the very best I can; and I mean to keep on doing so until the end.</item>
        <item>141|100|I do not think much of a man who is not wiser today than he was yesterday.</item>
        <item>142|100|Avoid popularity if you would have peace.</item>
        <item>143|100|The things I want to know are in books; my best friend is the man who\'ll get me a book I ain\'t read.</item>
        <item>144|100|With Malice toward none, with charity for all, with firmness in the right, as God gives us to see the right, let us strive on to finish the work we are in, to bind up the nation\'s wounds.</item>
        <item>145|100|Don\'t worry when you are not recognized, but strive to be worthy of recognition.</item>
        <item>146|100|Books serve to show a man that those original thoughts of his aren\'t very new at all.</item>
        <item>147|100|Let not him who is houseless pull down the house of another, but let him work diligently and build one for himself, thus by example assuring that his own shall be safe from violence when built.</item>
        <item>148|100|The philosophy of the school room in one generation will be the philosophy of government in the next.</item>
        <item>149|100|Discourage litigation. Persuade your neighbors to compromise whenever you can. As a peacemaker the lawyer has superior opportunity of being a good man. There will still be business enough.</item>
        <item>150|100|I\'m a slow walker, but I never walk back.</item>
        <item>151|100|Everybody likes a compliment.</item>
        <item>152|100|No man has a good enough memory to be a successful liar.</item>
        <item>153|100|I will prepare and some day my chance will come.</item>
        <item>154|100|I have always found that mercy bears richer fruits than strict justice.</item>
        <item>155|100|That some achieve great success, is proof to all that others can achieve it as well.</item>
        <item>156|100|I never had a policy; I have just tried to do my very best each and every day.</item>
        <item>157|100|My great concern is not whether you have failed, but whether you are content with your failure.</item>
        <item>158|100|I like to see a man proud of the place in which he lives. I like to see a man live so that his place will be proud of him.</item>
        <item>159|100|My dream is of a place and a time where America will once again be seen as the last best hope of earth.</item>
        <item>160|100|Every man is said to have his peculiar ambition. Whether it be true or not, I can say for one that I have no other so great as that of being truly esteemed of my fellow men, by rendering myself worthy of their esteem.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>