<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Has a daughter Lourdes Maria, Rocco, and she adopted two black children: David and Mercy."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Herb Ritts."</item>
		<item>"Attended St. Andrews Patrick Catholic school."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Mary Lambert."</item>
		<item>"Her mother was born on July 11, 1932." </item>
		<item>"One of 7 siblings. Her mother died of breast cancer on December 1st, 1963."</item>
		<item>"1989 album \"Like A Prayer\" ranked #100 on VH1's 100 Greatest Albums."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Jean-Baptiste Mondino."</item>
		<item>"#6 in Life's 100 Greatest Rockers List (March 2002)"</item>
		<item>"Parodied by Amy Poehler on "Saturday Night Live" (1975)"</item>
		<item>"Good friends with David Fincher."</item>
		<item>"Madonna loves David."</item>
		<item>"Madonna is frinds with Versace."</item>
		<item>"Madonna is a matirial girl."</item>
		<item>"Sean Penn was her hubby."</item>
		<item>"Madonna is a blonde."</item>
		<item>"Madonna wears a red string."</item>
		<item>"Madonna studies kabbalah."</item>
		<item>"Madonna is an Icon."</item>
		<item>"Madonna loves sushi."</item>
		<item>"Madonna lived in New York."</item>
		<item>"Madonna is is Italian-french."</item>
		<item>"Her adopted son is David"</item>
		<item>"Her son is Roco."</item>
		<item>"Madonna has a doughter named Lola."</item>
		<item>"Madonna has blue eyes."</item>
		<item>"Her 2008 song "4 Minutes" featuring Justin Timberlake and Tim Mosley made her the female artist with the most Top 10 singles and the most number 1 hits (13) in the UK."</item>
		<item>"Supporter of Hillary Rodham Clinton`s 2008 electoral campaign."</item>
		<item>"Thanked by Alanis Morissette in the liner notes of her album \"Jagged Little Pill\"."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Mary Lambert, Herb Ritts, Jean-Baptiste Mondino and David Fincher."</item>
		<item>"In 2007, Forbes Magazine reported that her 2006 earnings were estimated at $72 million."</item>
		<item>"Four music videos that made it on VH1`s 50 Sexiest Video Moments: \"Justify My Love\" was #1, \"Erotica\" was #16, \"Take a Bow\" was #27, and \"Open Your Heart\" was #37"</item>
		<item>"Her 1989 album \"Like A Prayer\" ranked #100 on VH1`s 100 Greatest Albums."</item>
		<item>"Six music videos that ranked on VH1`s 100 Greatest Videos: \"Like A Prayer\" was #2, \"Justify My Love\" was #7, \"Ray Of Light\" was #40, \"Material Girl\" was #54, \"Like A Virgin\" was #61, and \"Borderline\" was #84."</item>
		<item>"Matthew Vaughn was Best Man at her wedding to Guy Ritchie."</item>
		<item>"Godmother of her son Rocco is Trudie Styler."</item>
		<item>"A fan of the book "Gone with the Wind"."</item>
		<item>"Favourite alcoholic drink is lemon drops."</item>
		<item>"Attended same high school as Karen Moncrieff, and David Geister."</item>
		<item>"Distantly related to Mark Wahlberg."</item>
		<item>"Inducted into the UK Music Hall of Fame for her outstanding contribution to British music and integral part of British music culture. [11 November 2004]"</item>
		<item>"Ranked #86 on VH1`s 100 Greatest Artists of Rock n Roll."</item>
		<item>"14th September 1984: Nominated for MTV Video Music Award for Best New Artist and gives a memorable performance of \"Like A Virgin\" at the ceremony."</item>
		<item>"1982: Signs a deal with Sire Records."</item>
		<item>"14th January 1984: Performs "Holiday" on "Bandstand" (1952) {(1984-01-14)}. It is her first national TV performance."</item>
		<item>"On her 1989 \"Like A Prayer\" album, she wrote a song about her failed marriage to Sean Penn called \"Till Death Do Us Part\"."</item>
		<item>"Andy Warhol was among the guests at her wedding to Sean Penn."</item>
		<item>"Had stated that movie stars such as Carole Lombard, Judy Holliday, Marilyn Monroe, Marlene Dietrich, Bette Davis, Louise Brooks, Rita Hayworth, and Dita Parlo were her idols."</item>
		<item>"Estimated in 2006 to have sold more than 200 million albums worldwide."</item>
		<item>"Appears in the 2006 edition of the Guinness Book of World Records as the female singer with the highest annual earnings."</item>
		<item>"Had stated that Deborah Harry from Blondie and Chrissie Hynde from The Pretenders were her main musical influences."</item>
		<item>"She was ranked #1 on VH1`s 100 Sexiest Artists."</item>
		<item>"1990: Allowed French TV host Michel Drucker to interview her in her L.A. home in 1990."</item>
		<item>"Has childhood friend of Moira McFarland-Messana from Michigan."</item>
		<item>"1986: Wrote the song \"Each Time You Break My Heart\" for Nick Kamen."</item>	
		<item>"Her version of \"American Pie\" was played for the first time at a John Galiano fashion show in 1999."</item>
		<item>"Recipient of the Lifetime Achievement Award at MTV`s 2006 TRL Awards (25 February 2006)."</item>
		<item>"Former sister-in-law of Chris Penn and Michael Penn."</item>
		<item>"Former daughter-in-law of Leo Penn and Eileen Ryan."</item>	
		<item>"Her personal stylist is Shavawn Marie Gordon (2005)."</item>
		<item>"Her father and stepmother, Silvio and Joan Ciccone, own and operate the award- winning Ciccone Vineyard and Winery in Suttons Bay, Michigan, just outside of Traverse City."</item>
		<item>"Was first introduced to her husband Guy Ritchie by Sting and Trudie Styler at their Country Estate. Sting was later made godfather of their first born son Rocco Ritchie."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite flowers are white roses."</item>
		<item>"Owns a house in Miami."</item>
		<item>"Introduced the songs that won Oscars for Broadway \"rivals\" Stephen Sondheim and Andrew Lloyd Webber."</item>
		<item>"Nicknames her daughter Lourdes \"Lola\"."</item>
		<item>"The first song she ever wrote before she became famous was a song called \"Tell the Truth\"."</item>
		<item>"Has two songs with the same title on two different albums: \"Forbidden Love\" which was included in her \"Bedtime Stories\" album; and \"Forbidden Love\" which was a track on her \"Confessions on a Dance Floor\" album."</item>
		<item>"Won two prizes at the 2006 Echo Awards for \"Best Female Artist international\" and \"Hit of the Year\" for \"Hung Up\" (12 March 2006)."</item>
		<item>"Considered for the role of Catwoman in Batman Returns (1992), which eventually went to Michelle Pfeiffer."</item>
		<item>"\"Hung Up\" jumped seven places to No. 7 on the Billboard Hot 100 singles chart in December 2005. Consequently the pop icon matches Elvis Presley`s tally for top 10 hits - 36, the most for any artist in the rock era."</item>
		<item>"Motherhood has inspired her to write a number of critically-acclaimed children`s books: \"The Adventures of Abdi\", \"The English Roses\", \"Lotsa de Casha\", \"Mr. Peabody`s Apples\" and \"Yakov and the Seven Thieves\"."</item>
		<item>"During her career she always had much influence on fashion due to her constant image change. She is considered as a fashion icon by most women in the world."</item>
		<item>"Her role in \"Speed The Plow\" on Broadway was taken over by `Felcity Huffman`"</item>
		<item>"Briefly hospitalized on her 47th birthday after breaking her hand and collar bone, and cracking three ribs after falling off a horse on her country estate."</item>
		<item>"Fell off a horse on her country estate in England, sustaining numerous injuries. [August 16, 2005]"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Designers: Dolce and Gabbana, Jean-Paul Gaultier, Betsy Johnson, Gianni Versace, Stella McCartney, Maripol."</item>
		<item>"Is a distant cousin of Gwen Stefani. Gwen`s great-aunt`s mother-in-law shares the same last name with Madonna."</item>
		<item>"Is a big fan of Kylie Minogue and Dannii Minogue."</item>
		<item>"Is spoofed in Eminem`s music video \"Just lose it\"."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with singer Britney Spears."</item>
		<item>"One of the very few friends she has kept from the old days is her former makeup artist, Debi Mazar, who is now an actress."</item>
		<item>"Voted #35 on Playboy`s \"100 sexiest women\" of the 20th Century (jan/2000)."</item>
		<item>"Nude pictures of her taken years earlier, when she was a starving dancer, ran in Penthouse magazine."</item>
		<item>"She posed nude again in the coffee table book "Sex" which became an instant best seller."</item>
		<item>"Was Prince`s first choice for the role of the Kid`s angelic muse Aura in his movie musical Graffiti Bridge (1990). She turned it down, brazenly telling him \"the screenplay was awful\"."</item>
		<item>"Turned down the role of Selina Kyle/Catwoman in Batman Returns (1992)."</item>
		<item>"Re-Invention Tour was the #1 world tour of 2004 grossing over $125 million. 55 of 56 shows were sold-out. (Billboard Boxscore)."</item>
		<item>"Her son, Rocco Ritchie, with Ritchie, was born by emergency C-section - 3 weeks early. [11 August 2000]"</item>
		<item>"Was born at Bay City Mercy Hospital in Bay City, Michigan."</item>
		<item>"Once had two pets named Chiquita (chichuahua) and Pepito (bull terrier)."</item>
		<item>"Her grandparents are named Elsie Fortin and Willard Fortin (1904-1959)."</item>
		<item>"Has a great-aunt named Bambina De Giulio."</item>
		<item>"Had lived in Pontiac, Michigan before living in Rochester Hills from 6th grade until she moved away to college."</item>
		<item>"A fan of the film Grey Gardens (1975), and \"La Dolce vita (1960))\"."</item>
		<item>"She was voted the 36th Greatest Artist of all time in Rock `n` Roll by Rolling Stone."</item>
		<item>"Her song \"La Isla Bonita\" (1986) was inspired by a visit she made to San Pedro, Ambergris Cay, Belize, with her then-husband Sean Penn."</item>
		<item>"1986: \"Borderline\" re-issued as a single in the UK where it peaked at #2 (54 places higher than its original release) and be certified Silver. It also peaked at #21 on Europe charts for two weeks."</item>
		<item>"1985: \"Holiday\" re-issed in the UK just before the release of \"Angel\" where it peaked at #2 (4 places higher than its original release)."</item>
		<item>"Siblings: Martin (1957), Anthony (1956), Christopher (1960), Paula (1959), Melanie (1962), Mario (1969) and Jennifer (1968)."</item>
		<item>"She has posed nude at least three times in her career: briefly in A Certain Sacrifice (1985), in some nude photos taken before she became famous in the late 1970s."</item>
		<item>"Born on the same day as actress Angela Bassett."</item>
		<item>"She is a fan of Carole Lombard, Betty Grable and Katharine Hepburn."</item>
		<item>"In 2003, three different action figures were made of her likeness based on her character, Susan, from the movie Desperately Seeking Susan (1985)."</item>
		<item>"Parodied by Amy Poehler on \"Saturday Night Live\" (1985)."</item>
		<item>"Is good friends with Björk, who also wrote the song \"Bedtime Story\" for her 1994 album, Bedtime Stories."</item>
		<item>"Won Best Chart Act at the 2004 Dancestar USA Awards, in Bayfront Park, Miami. (9th March 2004)."</item>
		<item>"Her 1985 hit \"Into The Groove\" was ranked #40 on VH1`s 100 Greatest Dance Songs, while \"Vogue\" placed in the top 10 at #4"</item>
		<item>"The Immaculate Collection voted #1 on Blender magazine`s 100 Greatest American Albums of All Time List. (Januray 2002)"</item>
		<item>"Voted #3 on the reader-voted Favorite Female List for Rolling Stone Magazine`s 2001 Music Awards list, following Britney Spears and Jennifer Lopez (January 2002)."</item>
		<item>"Won Best Solo Dance Artist at the 17th International Dance Music Awards held at the Winter Music Conference in Miami. (March 2002)."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #6 in Life`s 100 Greatest Rockers List (March 2002)."</item>
		<item>"\"Madonna - Drowned World Tour 2001\" home video release certified platinum in the U.S. (video sales of over 100,000 copies) (March 2002)"</item>
		<item>"Received a career award at the 2004 French NRJ Awards (January 2004)."</item>
		<item>"Her wedding dress for her 2000 wedding to director Guy Ritchie was designed by her friend Stella McCartney."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #8 on VH1`s 100 Greatest Women of Rock N Roll."</item>
		<item>"Her first children`s book, \"The English Roses\", was published in September, 2003."</item>
		<item>"December 2003 - announced she was starting a merchandising line of dolls, apparel, home decor, etc. as a tie-in to her best-selling children`s book, \"The English Roses\"."</item>
		<item>"Purchased a mini mansion for daughter Lourdes in 2003. Produced by Posh Tots, a mini-mansion ranges in price from US$6,500 to US$125,000, and can even be installed with cable TV and running water."</item>
		<item>"Her mother and her two uncles were buried at Calvary Cemetery in Bay City, Michigan."</item>
		<item>"Her parents were married at Visitation Catholic Church in Bay City, Michigan on July 2, 1955."</item>
		<item>"Attended West Junior High in Rochester Hills, Michigan for the 8th grade."</item>
		<item>"Attended St. Andrew`s Elementary School (now Holy Family Regional)."</item>
		<item>"Mentioned in the lyrics of the song \"You Were Right\" by Damon Gough, aka Badly Drawn Boy."</item>
		<item>"Madonna and Céline Dion share the same French-Canadian heritage through a common ancestor named Zacharie Cloutier."</item>
		<item>"Featured on the sleeve of the album \"Vigil in a Wilderness of Mirrors\" by former Marillion singer Fish. She is also mentioned in his song \"Big Wedge\"."</item>
		<item>"Her song \"Little star\" is dedicated to her daughter Lourdes"</item>
		<item>"Has a personal collection of paintings by Frida Kahlo, Pablo Picasso and Salvador Dalí."</item>
		<item>"In November 2000, she held a live concert at the Brixton Academy in London which was broadcast over the Internet. A record nine million people watched the event, making it the largest live webcast of all time."</item>
		<item>"Measurements: 34C-23-33 (Source: Celebrity Sleuth magazine)"</item>
		<item>"Sister-in-law of Joe Henry who write for \"Don`t Tell Me\" and \"Jump\" from Madonna`s albums \"Music\"(2003) and \"Confessions on a Dance Floor\" (2005) respectively."</item>
		<item>"Her father is Italian, her mother was French-Canadian."</item>
		<item>"Her grandparents are Michelina and Gaetano Ciccone."</item>
		<item>"Gwyneth Paltrow was the Maid of Honor at her wedding to Guy Ritchie."</item>
		<item>"Named one of E!`s \"top 20 entertainers of 2001\"."</item>
		<item>"As of 2001, her albums have sold 153 million copies worldwide."</item>
		<item>"Her first film, A Certain Sacrifice (1985), was released in 1985, after she became a star, but was actually shot in two parts, the first in 1979, and the other, in 1981."</item>
		<item>"Appeared in a stage play in 1986 called \"Goose And Tom-Tom\" with then-husband Sean Penn."</item>
		<item>"Appeared in a filmed stage play in 1980 called \"In Artificial Light\", in which she wrote her own part."</item>
		<item>"Her film Shanghai Surprise (1986) was a box-office disaster, costing $17 million and grossing only $2."</item>
		<item>"Did a Japanese commercial for Panasonic in 1987."</item>
		<item>"Appeared in a 1988 stage play with Ron Silver and Joe Mantegna called \"Speed-The-Plow\"."</item>
		<item>"Named one of People Magazine`s 50 Most Beautiful People of 1991, and 25 Most Intriguing People of 2001."</item>
		<item>"Born at 7:05 AM EDT."</item>
		<item>"Bought mansion in the Hollywood Hills originally built for Rudolph Valentino."</item>
		<item>"Her birthday is also the anniversary of Elvis Presley`s death."</item>
		<item>"Has an IQ of 140."</item>
		<item>"Her infamous 1994 appearance on \"Late Show with David Letterman\" (1993) had her saying the \"f\" word 13 times."</item>
		<item>"Resides in Marylebone, London and a country estate in Tollard Royal, Wiltshire."</item>
		<item>"Graduated from Rochester Adams High School in 1976. Studied at the North Carolina School of the Arts, and won a scholarship to study modern dance and drama for 3 semesters at the University of Michigan."</item>
		<item>"Owner of Maverick Records label (1992-2004)."</item>
		<item>"Was good friends with Gwyneth Paltrow before she declined her invitation to join her Kabbalah study group in London."</item>
		<item>"Turned down the role of Cristal Conners in Showgirls (1995)."</item>
		<item>"Turned down the lead in The Fabulous Baker Boys (1989)."</item>
		<item>"Wanted to play the role of Ginger in Casino (1995), but the role was given to Sharon Stone instead."</item>
		<item>"Her daughter Lourdes was named as a tribute to Madonna`s mother, who wanted to visit Lourdes, France, where the Virgin Mary, the Madonna, appeared in 1858, but died before doing so."</item>
		<item>"She was high school cheerleader."</item>
		<item>"Was supposed to play the lead in Music of the Heart (1999) but dropped out two weeks before filming was set to begin."</item>
		<item>"Unanimously condemned by the Puerto Rican House of Representatives for pulling a Puerto Rican flag between her legs in an October 26, 1993 concert."</item>
		<item>"Studied with the Alvin Ailey dance troupe and Pearl Lang`s Dance Company in Manhattan. [1978]."</item>
		<item>"Gave birth to baby daughter named Lourdes Maria Ciccone Leon (aka Lola Leon). The father is actor/fitness instructor Carlos Leon."</item>
		<item>"Her record company Maverick Records signed a distribution deal with A Band Apart Records, a record company founded by Quentin Tarantino and Lawrence Bender."</item>
		<item>"Her videos \"Justify My Love\" and \"What It Feels Like For A Girl\" were banned from VH1 and MTV. \"Erotica\" (1992), though not banned, was only played after midnight on MTV"</item>
		<item>"Madonna is in the Guinness Book of World Records for being the most successful female solo artist."</item>
		<item>"Madonna has brontophobia - a fear of thunder."</item>
		<item>"She has won numerous MTV Music Awards, five Grammys, and a Golden Globe for her performance in \"Evita\"."</item>
		<item>"In 1992 she signed with Time Warner to create her own record label, Maverick."</item>
		<item>"Madonna was the third of eight children born into a large Italian family in Michigan."</item>
		<item>"She is 5' 4½" (1.64 m) tall."</item>
		<item>"Her birth name is Madonna Louise Veronica Ciccone."</item>
		<item>"She was born on 16 August 1958 in Bay City, Michigan, USA."</item>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
