<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"In a world filled with hate, we must still dare to hope. In a world filled with anger, we must still dare to comfort. In a world filled with despair, we must still dare to dream. And in a world filled with distrust, we must still dare to believe."</item>
		<item>"The meaning of life is contained in every single expression of life. It is present in the infinity of forms and phenomena that exist in all of creation."</item>
		<item>"I wake up from dreams and go "Wow, put this down on paper." The whole thing is strange. You hear the words, everything is right there in front of your face . ."</item>
		<item>"The greatest education in the world is watching the masters at work."</item>
		<item>"If you enter this world knowing you are loved and you leave this world knowing the same, then everything that happens in between can be dealt with." </item>
		<item>"Lies run sprints, but the truth runs marathons. The truth will win this marathon in court."</item>
		<item>"And my goal in life is to give to the world what I was lucky to receive: the ecstasy of divine union through my music and my dance."</item>
		<item>"I was a veteran, before I was a teenager."”</item>
		<item>"Why can't you share your bed? The most loving thing to do is to share your bed with someone. It's very charming. It's very sweet. It's what the whole world should do."</item>
		<item>"I'm just like anyone. I cut and I bleed. And I embarass easily."</item>
		<item>"Children show me in their playful smiles the divine in everyone. This simple goodness shines straight from their hearts and only asks to be lived."</item>
		<item>"the proceedings have been a nightmare for my family"</item>
		<item>"Me and Janet really are two different people."</item>
		<item>"Please keep an open mind and let me have my day in court."</item>
		<item>"My heart and prayers go out to every individual."</item>
		<item>"I changed. People change."</item>
		<item>"Smooth, but not a criminal."</item>
		<item>"I am bewildered at the length to which people will go to portray me so negatively."</item>
		<item>"I will say again that I have never, and would never, harm a child. It sickens me that people have written untrue things about me."</item>
		<item>"Why can't you share your bed? The most loving thing to do is to share your bed with someone, ... You say, 'You can have my bed if you want it. Sleep in it. I'll sleep on the floor. It's yours.' I always give the beds to the company."</item>
		<item>"People who grew up as child stars have the same thing in common. You're cute, they love you; you go through the awkward stage, they don't accept you any more. Very few make the transition to adult star."</item>
		<item>"Ground water has always been the property of the landowner, with the idea that water can be used for the benefit of the land."</item>
		<item>"Sorry, guys. I'm under the gag order."</item>
		<item>"I believe in my heart that the music community will come together as one and rally to the aid of thousands of innocent victims, ... There is a tremendous need for relief dollars right now and through this effort each one of us can play an immediate role in helping comfort so many people."</item>
		<item>"I have always maintained my innocence, and vehemently denied that these events ever took place. I reluctantly chose to settle the false claims only to end the terrible publicity and to continue with my life and career."</item>
		<item>"I respect the obligation of confidentiality imposed on all of the parties to the 1993 proceedings."</item>
		<item>"No action or investigation has been taken to determine who is leaking this information or why they are permitted to violate the law in such a manner. I respectfully request that people see these efforts for what they are."</item>
		<item>"All of Hollywood has plastic surgery. I don't know why they point me out. The press exaggerated it. It's just my nose, you know. They want it to be everything. Just the nose isn't enough."</item>
		<item>"Not sexual. We're going to sleep."</item>
		<item>"She prefers them to be with me than with her"</item>
		<item>"Gross distortion of the truth."</item>
		<item>"I trusted Martin Bashir to come into my life and that of my family because I wanted the truth to be told."</item>
		<item>"Martin Bashir persuaded me to trust him, that his would be an honest and fair portrayal of my life and told me that he was 'the man that turned Diana's life around."</item>
		<item>"Everyone who knows me will know the truth, which is that my children come first in my life and that I would never harm any child."</item>
		<item>"There's a Mother's Day and there's a Father's Day, but there's no Children's Day. It would mean a lot. World peace."</item>
		<item>"Let us dream of tomorrow where we can truly love from the soul, and know love as the ultimate truth at the heart of all creation."</item>
		<item>"And the dream we were conceived in will reveal a joyful face... and the world we once believed in will shine again in grace. Then why do we keep strangling life wound this Earth, crucify its soul. Though it's plain to see, this world is heavenly. We could be God's glow... Heal the world."</item>
		<item>"It pains me to watch the human suffering taking place in the Gulf region of my country."</item>
		<item>"This is America, Charlie Brown."</item>
		<item>"Let a pedophile go."</item>
		<item>"When we gonna leave?"</item>
		<item>"To return to Santa Barbara to immediately confront and prove these charges unfounded."</item>
		<item>"We Are the World."</item>
		<item>"Was the hardest thing I've ever done in my life."</item>
		<item>"People cope in a lot of different ways."</item>
		<item>"We were ready to go (to trial)."</item>
		<item>"He thought better of it when he was looking at the jury."</item>
		<item>"The Jones guy was the main shooter."</item>
		<item>"There's a good chance that most of them will plead guilty."</item>
		<item>"All the refugees and all those who are homeless within Kosovo ... wait a little while until we are ready to take them back to their homes. Their safety and their security are my most serious concerns."</item>
		<item>"And allegedly he was also given Jesus' juice, and it blew the whole deal."</item>
		<item>"Is probably larger than any of us really wanted to believe."</item>
		<item>"He didn't believe that, ... He thought they were good."</item>
		<item>"Rock You Like a Hurricane"</item>
		<item>"I took place in a proceeding where neither my lawyers nor I ever appeared."</item>	
		<item>"I drank a little bit and told him it tasted ugly, ... it will relax you. I know you're all stressed out."</item>
		<item>"Years ago, I settled with certain individuals because I was concerned about my family and the media scrutiny that would have ensued if I fought the matter in court."</item>
		<item>"These people wanted to exploit my concern for children by threatening to destroy what I believe in and what I do. I have been a vulnerable target for those who want money."</item>
		<item>"I have spent my entire life helping millions of children across the world. I would never harm a child."</item>	
		<item>"You can always dream, and your dreams will come true, but you have to make them come true."</item>
		<item>"He's the very best, amazing, so kind."</item>
		<item>"I'm constantly working on it."</item>
		<item>"Given the department's youth and the state of transformation, the overall results were not unexpected."</item>
		<item>"It pains me to watch the human suffering taking place in the Gulf region of my country. My heart and prayers go out to every individual who has had to endure the pain and suffering caused by this tragedy."</item>
		<item>"I will be reaching out to others within the music industry to join me in helping to bring relief and hope to these resilient people who have lost everything."</item>
		<item>"Everything I said, I said with my heart."</item>
		<item>"How the mighty fall. It really is the final straw for this guy. Just when you think things can't get any worse, he holds his baby out of a window. It's actually quite unbelievable. I suppose he'll blame Sony for that, as well."</item>
		<item>"If someone had told me that one day I would be getting, as a musician, the artist of the millennium award, I wouldn't believe it."</item>
		<item>"I sleep with apples."</item>
		<item>"Despite the challenging market environment, the board is confident about the prospects for the current year."</item>
		<item>"Mean, racist, and very, very, very devilish."</item>
		<item>"We resolved the lawsuit over the weekend. We settled it."</item>
		<item>"This is the biggest damn mess I have ever seen."</item>
		<item>"Be Careful Who You Love."</item>
		<item>"It seems every time he has a problem in his life, he blames it on Jews."</item>
		<item>"We're in the planning. Classes will start late this year or early next year. We want to train people with viable marketing skills and rudiments in entrepreneurial skills. You learn and apply it however you best need it."</item>
		<item>"A bunch of guys at work heard me sing and they said I should try this. But I probably wouldn't have done it on my own if they hadn't suggested it."</item>
		<item>"We just hope that... it inadvertently does not affect access consumers would have."</item>
		<item>"We have been screaming for bolder design for years. The consumer has too many choices. The only way to get to No. 1 is bold design."</item>
		<item>"It all starts with defense. With us offense is secondary."</item>
		<item>"It's good to know they're actually looking at it."</item>
		<item>"Nothing in his person or his teaching would indicate that (the charges) would be true... He has strong political views -- I'd say he is a social liberal -- but I've never seen a scintilla of violence in his behavior or in the way he interacts with his students. He is very passive and low-key."</item>
		<item>"I found myself taking a five-hour bus ride to sample the local beers in Whitefish, Montana."</item>
		<item>"We will continue to make sure these gunslingers get a high bond, ... This is Selma, not the 'Rifleman' show."</item>
		<item>"Noncompliance will not be tolerated from whichever quarter it may come."</item>
		<item>"Granada has, by use of voice-overs, editing and the nature of the questions asked, treated me unfairly by giving viewers the impression that I have behaved inappropriately with children."</item>
		<item>"I know the law enforcement community has been very concerned about this case, ... I want to thank Gov. Riley for responding so quickly to my request for some reward money for this case. Hopefully, Lt. Woods' son will be found safe."</item>
		<item>"Clearly, it was an incumbent-protection act, ... Redistricting was indeed a pretty ugly power play."</item>
		<item>"Online banking account hijacking is the fastest-growing form of identity theft we monitor, ... Regulators want to get in front of the problem rather than be reactive."</item>
		<item>"The department and NHTSA are giving this matter full consideration."</item>
		<item>"We think the collectivity of the efforts the secretary has described today will underscore our commitment to implement significant and far-reaching ambitions for changing the dynamic regarding illegal immigration."</item>
		<item>"Nothing in his person or his teaching would indicate that (the charges) would be true. He has strong political views -- I'd say he is a social liberal -- but I've never seen a scintilla of violence in his behavior or in the way he interacts with his students. He is very passive and low-key."</item>
		<item>"We're trying to get them ready for life. It's an anti-gang mentoring program and we look at various ways to train young men 8 to 18."</item>
		<item>"We will continue to make sure these gunslingers get a high bond. This is Selma, not the 'Rifleman' show."</item>
		<item>"Online banking account hijacking is the fastest-growing form of identity theft we monitor. Regulators want to get in front of the problem rather than be reactive."</item>
		<item>"Noncompliance will not be tolerated from whichever quarter it may come."</item>
		<item>"Remember my strong advice, just remember to always think twice."</item>
		<item>"This is an enormously exciting opportunity to grow content businesses that combine the unique capabilities of the internet with the art and science of traditional programming."</item>
		<item>"That can be a 'challenge word,' maybe asking you your birthday, your favorite cake, your favorite dessert."</item>
		<item>"Please, no! You have to give us some privacy. Please, you have to understand his position, he is with his kids... you need to leave us alone."</item>
		<item>"I look at this as a staff award. It's a good indicator that our staff is doing some of the right things and our kids are responding well to what we have asked them to do."</item>
		<item>"Our coaching staff has worked very hard, and so have our players. They dedicated themselves to getting better, and once they developed confidence in themselves and started believing they could win everything just came together."</item>
		<item>"I owe a lot to those three men for helping me become the coach I am today. So much of my coaching philosophy is based on what I learned from all of them. They all played a major role in the things I've been able to accomplish."</item>
		<item>"What we call single-factor authentication is a basic password and ID. Now we're asking banks to use another form of identification."</item>
		<item>"It makes it harder to trust McDonald's if they suddenly have strikingly different (trans fat) numbers."</item>
		<item>"It is almost a routine thing that they come from time to time to visit their regiments. So we are kind of working on those in the longer term."</item>
		<item>"Prince Edward comes to Canada every year. He is president of the Duke of Edinburgh Awards, and so he comes pretty well every year for ... the presentations. And often he'll drop in and do something else while he is travelling, so we are not looking at a kind of highly organized royal visit."</item>
		<item>"(The board) has finally discovered that it's in charge of the Delta."</item>
		<item>"On a list of a hundred environmental problems in my community, this would probably be somewhere around 98."</item>
		<item>"If any checking needs to be done, it needs to be at the point the order is initiated -- not when the order is executed."</item>
		<item>"They [the Jews] suck them like leeches. I'm so tired of it. They start out the most popular person in the world, make a lot of money, big house, cars and everything and end up penniless. It's a conspiracy. The Jews do it on purpose."</item>
		<item>"Many organizations were initially scared of the Internet and email. Now there's hardly a workplace on the planet that doesn't have an Internet connection."</item>
		<item>"I clear $180 a month. It's the highest-paying job in the compound."</item>
		<item>"It's a potential problem when you add any sort of metal to the ground. But I would worry a whole hell of a lot more about agricultural chemicals in Stockton than silver iodine in the Sierra."</item>
		<item>"We saw that the industry was very slow in adopting increased security measures."</item>
		<item>"They have agreed in Hong Kong to tax themselves for the purpose of improving security and we should praise this and partner with these types of opportunities to take this type of system and make it an operationally more aggressive and solid tool."</item>
		<item>"So, for them to publicly display themselves in that manner of the Easter Egg Roll, which is for children like that. It kind of brings about discouragement for me."</item>
		<item>"I am incredibly excited about my new venture, and I am enjoying being back in the studio making music."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
