<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"The only way to have a life is to commit to it like crazy."</item>
		<item>"Oh, God, I struggle with low self-esteem all the time! I think everyone does. I have so much wrong with me, it's unbelievable!"</item>
		<item>"I think all women go through periods where we hate this about ourselves, we don't like that. It's great to get to a place where you dismiss anything you're worried about. I find flaws attractive. I find scars attractive."</item>
		<item>"The truth is I love being alive. And I love feeling free. So if I can't have those things then I feel like a caged animal and I'd rather not be in a cage. I'd rather be dead. And it's real simple. And I think it's not that uncommon."</item>
		<item>"I always play women I would date."</item>
		<item>"All women do have a different sense of sexuality, or sense of fun, or sense of like what's sexy or cool or tough."</item>
		<item>"They're right to think that about me, because I'm the person most likely to sleep with my female fans, I genuinely love other women. And I think they know that."</item>
		<item>"Death is life in reverse."</item>
		<item>"I need someone physically stronger than me... I am always on top. It's really unfortunate. I am begging for the man that can put me on the bottom. Or the woman. Anybody that can take me down."</item>
		<item>"I don't think the money people in Hollywood have ever thought I was normal, but I am dedicated to my work and that's what counts."</item>
		<item>"If being sane is thinking there's something wrong with being different....I'd rather be completely fucking mental."</item>
		<item>"Without pain, there would be no suffering, without suffering we would never learn from our mistakes. To make it right, pain and suffering is the key to all windows, without it, there is no way of life."</item>
		<item>"If I think more about death than some other people, it is probably because I love life more than they do."</item>
		<item>"I don't believe in guilt, I believe in living on impulse as long as you never intentionally hurt another person, and don't judge people in your life. I think you should live completely free."</item>
		<item>"I wish I could find people who just would fight me and break through to me and hold me down and scream their life into my face."</item>
		<item>"I never felt settled or calm. You can't really commit to life when you feel that."</item>
		<item>"There's something about death that is comforting. The thought that you could die tomorrow frees you to appreciate your life now."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I think [my husband] is so amazing that I don't know why he's with me. I don't know whether I'm good enough. But if I make him happy, then I'm everything I want to be."</item>
		<item>"I don't see myself as beautiful, because I can see a lot of flaws. People have really odd opinions. They tell me I'm skinny, as if that's supposed to make me happy."</item>
		<item>"I do have tatoos, and I do wear leather, but there are other sides of me, that my film express."</item>
		<item>"I didn't really want to live, so anything that was an investment in time made me angry... but also I just felt sad. When the hopelessness is hurting you, it's the fixtures and fittings that finish you off."</item>
		<item>"I am odd-looking. I sometimes think I look like a funny Muppet."</item>
		<item>"Honestly, I like everything, boyish girls, girlish boys, the heavy and the skinny."</item>
		<item>"Everyone got kind of crazy with me mentioning I was in love with a woman."</item>
		<item>"And my dad, you're a great actor but you're a better father."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I think my husband is so amazing that I don't know why he's with me. I don't know whether I'm good enough. But if I make him happy, then I'm everything I want to be."</item>
		<item>"If you have enough people sitting around telling you you're wonderful, then you start believing you're fabulous, then someone tells you you stink and you believe that too!"</item>
		<item>"If you ask people what they've always wanted to do, most people haven't done it. That breaks my heart."</item>
		<item>"If I make a fool of myself, who cares? I'm not frightened by anyone's perception of me."</item>
		<item>"If I didn't have my films as an outlet for all the different sides of me, I would probably be locked up."</item>
		<item>"I've told Billy if I ever caught him cheating, I wouldn't kill him because I love his children and they need a dad. But I would beat him up. I know where all of his sports injuries are."</item>
		<item>"I've been reckless, but I'm not a rebel without a cause."</item>
		<item>"I'm odd looking. Sometimes I think I look like a funny muppet."</item>
		<item>"I'm happy being myself, which I've never been before. I always hid in other people, or tried to find myself through the characters, or live out their lives, but I didn't have those things in mine."</item>
		<item>"I'm getting a wrinkle above my eyebrow because I just can't stop lifting it, and I love that you know."</item>
		<item>"I'd go from film to film and almost detach from one world and jump in another. I was living as these people and not having a self. I didn't know who I was. And things just get really dark."</item>
		<item>"I never like being touched, ever. People used to say I held my breath when they were hugging me. I still do."</item>
		<item>"I need more sex, OK? Before I die I wanna taste everyone in the world."</item>
		<item>"I love to put on lotion. Sometimes I'll watch TV and go into a lotion trance for an hour. I try to find brands that don't taste bad in case anyone wants to taste me."</item>
		<item>"I like to hide behind the characters I play. Despite the public perception, I am a very private person who has a hard time with the fame thing."</item>
		<item>"I like someone who is a little crazy but coming from a good place. I think scars are sexy because it means you made a mistake that led to a mess."</item>
		<item>"I like everything. Boyish girls, girlish boys, the heavy and the skinny. Which is a problem when I'm walking down the street."</item>
		<item>"Where ever I am I always find myself looking out the window wishing I was somewhere else."</item>
		<item>"When other little girls wanted to be ballet dancers I kind of wanted to be a vampire."</item>
		<item>"When I get logical, and I don't trust my instincts - that's when I get in trouble."</item>
		<item>"What nourishes me also destroys me."</item>
		<item>"Therapy? I don't need that. The roles that I choose are my therapy."</item>
		<item>"The fact is I am not having sex. But I feel absolutely ripe for the, what would you say? plucking?"</item>
		<item>"I am so in love with my brother right now!"</item>
		<item>"And my dad, you're a great actor but you're a better father."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I think [my husband] is so amazing that I don't know why he's with me. I don't know whether I'm good enough. But if I make him happy, then I'm everything I want to be."</item>
		<item>"I'd go from film to film and almost detach from one world and jump in another. I was living as these people and not having a self. I didn't know who I was. And things just get really dark."</item>
		<item>"If being sane is thinking there's something wrong with being different....I'd rather be completely fucking mental."</item>
		<item>"If I make a fool of myself, who cares? I'm not frightened by anyone's perception of me."</item>
		<item>"I don't believe in guilt, I believe in living on impulse as long as you never intentionally hurt another person, and don't judge people in your life. I think you should live completely free."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
