<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>An actor should never be larger than the film he`s in.</item>
		<item>I started my career without fans.</item>
		<item>It`s the actors who are prepared to make fools of themselves who are usually the ones who come to mean something to the audience.</item>
		<item>I only sound intelligent when there`s a good scriptwriter around.</item>
		<item>I`m English. Our dentistry is not world famous. But I made sure I got moldings of my old teeth beforehand because I miss them.</item>
		<item>I don`t think I`m like any of the characters I`ve played. They`re all really far from who I am.</item>
		<item>I like being kept in the dark myself. You know, like mushrooms: Keep `em in the dark and feed `em shit. See, I think that`s an enjoyable vegetable to be.</item>
		<item>I think there`s a kind of pretentiousness to the idea that serious work is only found in low-budget independent movies--I can`t stand that snobbery.</item>
		<item>Life is not stable. There is a great strength that comes from not being shocked or scared by upheavals.</item>
		<item>I think trying too hard to be sexy is the worst thing in the world a woman can do.</item>
		<item>If everyone really knew what a jerk I am in real life, I wouldn`t be so adored in the slightest.</item>
		<item>I don`t personally look to my own life experiences for answers about how to play a scene.</item>
		<item>I have a fear of being boring.</item>
		<item>When it comes to films, people often don`t differentiate between the message of a bad central character and the message of the film itself. They are two separate things.</item>
		<item>After having done American Psycho and Shaft, I found it a breath of fresh air to play somebody who`s completely human in terms of his emotions.</item>
		<item>It`s not who I am underneath but what I do that defines me.</item>
		<item>I tend to think you`re fearless when you recognize why you should be scared of things, but do them anyway.</item>
		<item>What I love about my wife is that she\'s a really strong-minded, stubborn, fiery woman. I find that sexier than anything else</item>
		<item>My method can be nothing, or the most intense, bizarre preparations you\'ve ever seen</item>
		<item>He\'s not your classical sexy type but he is Batman and you can never underestimate the powers of a superhero!</item>
		<item>Everybody talks about the process too much. The interesting thing about a movie is the movie.</item>
		<item>I have this theory that, depending on your attitude, your life doesn\'t have to become this ridiculous charade that it seems so many people end up living.</item>
		<item>I like the idea of movies having a magic element. How many times have you seen an actor in a movie who you know only as the character? It\'s wonderful, isn\'t it?</item>
		<item>I never want to feel that I\'m playing it safe.</item>
		<item>A movie star is someone people look at and go, \'I want to be like that person\'. There\'s the responsibility of desire. It\'s not something I\'m interested in trying. I would fail miserably at it, so why even bother?</item>
		<item>In everyday life, my wife is the most wonderful. We\'re in love with each other beyond belief.</item>
		<item>In terms of the romantic kind of lead, I just never enjoy those movies very much. Maybe they\'ll come to interest me more as I get older. I doubt it, but maybe. Romantic comedies tend to be, for me, an oxymoron.</item>
		<item>Nuclear apocalypse - who do you need? Actors are probably not top of the list. What can I do for you? I can pretend to be somebody who can grow you some nice crops.</item>
		<item>You\'re creating a different world and the actor\'s job is to be able to convince the audience to enter into that world, whether it be actually something that you recognize from your own life or not.</item>
		<item>What the hell kind of man decides to dress up as a bat and run around the city? There\'s got to be something a little bit loose in there.</item>
		<item> There have been many times when you spend a number of months and the finished product is not what you wanted to see. And Batman Begins was what I wanted to see</item>
		<item>Batman took 10 months to film, and by the time I stopped working on it, it took a long time before my English accent came out again. I was actually having to try for it.</item>
		<item>Essentially, I\'m untrained, so I just go with my imagination and try to put myself as solidly as I can into the shoes of whatever person I\'m going to be playing.</item>
		<item>I\'ve had some painful experiences in my life, but I feel like I\'m trivializing them by using them for a scene in a movie. I don\'t want to do that. It just makes me feel kind of dirty for having done that.</item>
		<item>My hope is that people will be repulsed by the character\'s complete lack of ethics and obsession with consumerism - that\'s what I was saying about the difference between the character\'s message and the film\'s message.</item>
		<item>We are starting off with our own different characters and our own laws and everything, looking at Bruce Wayne and how he came to be the person that he was and how he comes to be this man that jumps around in the Bat suit.</item>
		<item>You\'re creating a different world and the actor\'s job is to be able to convince the audience to enter into that world, whether it be actually something that you recognize from your own life or not.</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
