<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"In her childhood, Amy used to wonder of becoming a roller-skating waitress."</item>
		<item>"At the age of 14, she was expelled from Sylvia Young Theater School for piercing her nose and not applying herself."</item>
		<item>"She got her first guitar at the age of 13, prior to that she used to play with her brother’s guitar."</item>
		<item>"Once Amy was razzed by some of her audience during a concert and some just walked out in protest against her drunken state."</item>
		<item>"Amy made her song \"Rehab\" on her denial of attending an alcohol rehabilitation center."</item>
		<item>"Amy and his boyfriend Blake Fielder-Civil broke up in 2007 but eventually got married the same year in Miami. There were rumors that she married him only to save him not be jailed."</item>
		<item>"After meeting Black Fielder, she hastily tattooed a name of his above her heart."</item>
		<item>"Amy’s favorite artists were Mos Def, Teena Marie, Beastie Boys, Carol King, Nas , Mahalia Jackson and Thelonious Monk."</item>
		<item>"Amy’s album \"Back to Black\" was a big hit and sold more than 3 million copies and was called the bestselling album in the UK in 2007."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse was 5'ft 2' inches tall."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse's distinctive style made her a muse for fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse was born in the Southgate area of north London to a Jewish family, who were influential toward her interest in jazz."</item>
		<item>"Lady Gaga credited Winehouse with paving the way for her rise to the top of the charts."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse won 3 Grammy Awards for  best new album of the year, Song of the year and Record of the year."</item>
		<item>"In 2008 Bryan Adams wrote a song for Amy Winehouse in a bit to help her overcome her drug habit. The song titled Flower Grown Wild, is about the dangers of drug-taking."</item>
		<item>"Singer Tony Bennett recorded a song with Winehouse for his forthcoming album, Duets II, which is scheduled for release on September 20, 2011."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse had strong opinions when it came to cocktails. Her favorite was the Rickstasy: three parts vodka, one part Southern Comfort, one part banana liqueur and one part Bailey's."</item>
		<item>"Her famous beehive was as high as 6 inches."</item>
		<item>"In June 2008, Amy was voted the celebrity most likely to retire early. The poll was conducted by website xRank, with more than 36,000 Britians taking part, with 30% of the vote going to Amy."</item>
		<item>"In early 2008 Amy discovered a painful lump on her cheek. After seeking medical advice she was diagnosed with impetigo, a contagious bacterial skin infection, and treatable by antibiotics."</item>
		<item>"While performing at a concert in Burmingham England in November 2007, Amy was booed by the audience, with others walking out in protest to her drunken state."</item>
		<item>"Amy and her husband were arrested in Norway for marijuana possession (October 2007)."</item>
		<item>"Prior to the 2007 MTV Europe Music Awards, Amy trashed her hotel room in Berlin by throwing furniture and spaghetti at the walls. It was reported that damages cost thousands of dollars worth."</item>
		<item>"In October 2007 it was revealed that Prince had asked Amy to perform a duet with him for his next album."</item>
		<item>"On 17 July 2007, her album Back to Black was announced as one of the 12 albums on the 2007 shortlist of Mercury Prize nominees."</item>
		<item>"In the summer of 2007, her song You Know I'm No Good was incorporated into ads for AMC's T.V. drama, Mad Men."</item>
		<item>"In her song Rehab, she mentions the names Ray and Mr. Hathaway. These are references to the soul singers Ray Charles and Donny Hathaway. "</item>
		<item>"Amy has one brother, named Alex."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse has appeared as an extra in a sketch on The Fast Show."</item>
		<item>"In May 2007, Amy won the 'Best Contemporary Song Award' for her hit Rehab at the 52nd Ivor Novello Awards for British songwriters."</item>
		<item>"In May 2007, Amy married Blake Fielder-Civil in a secret ceremony in Miami."</item>
		<item>"Amy announced she had been approached by one of the producers of the James Bond movies to sing the main theme of Bond 22."</item>
		<item>"Her album Frank went on to sell platinum."</item>
		<item>"Amy was friends with Matt Willis."</item>
		<item>"Her eye color is hazel."</item>
		<item>"When she was 14, she attended the BRIT School in Selhurst, Croydon."</item>
		<item>"She pierced her nose when she was 13."</item>
		<item>"She attended the Ashmole School."</item>
		<item>"Amy has a number of 'old school' tattoos of naked women on her body."</item>
		<item>"Amy grew up in the suburb of Southgate, North London."</item>
		<item>"In February 2007, Amy won the Best British Female Award at the Brit Awards, beating the favourite to win, Lily Allen."</item>
		<item>"Amy's debut album, Frank was released on October 20, 2003."</item>
		<item>"Appeared as a guest on the 'Charlotte Church' Show. They sang Michael Jackson's 'Beat It' together."</item>
		<item>"Had her waxwork unveiled at Madame Tussauds in London on July 23, 2008."</item>
		<item>"Posed naked for the April 2008 issue of British magazine, \"Easy Living,\" in a bid to raise awareness about breast cancer among young women. "</item>
		<item>"Chosen UK Solo Artist of the Year at the 2007 Glamour annual events held on June 5."</item>
		<item>"Ranked 2nd on Mr. Blackwell's 48th Annual Worst Dressed Women List, released on January 8, 2008."</item>
		<item>"Spit at fans after booed for forgetting her own lyrics, slapped herself repeatedly and knocked her head on the mic during a gig in Cornwall, England on July 17, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Was spotted having a number of cuts and scars on her arm while attending the 2007 Elle Style Awards. "</item>
		<item>"Befriended singers Matt Willis and Billie Piper. "</item>
		<item>"Chosen No. 2 in a poll on the World's Unsexiest Women conducted by men's magazine Maxim in October 2007. "</item>
		<item>"Her single \"Rehab\" was turned to several remixes by Steve Mac, Hot Chip and Desert Eagle in 2007. "</item>
		<item>"Broke her big tooth in a drunken fall that forced her to cancel London's Shepherds Bush Empire gigs in March 2007."</item>
		<item>"Ended the January 7, 2007 show at G-A-Y part way through her first song after vomiting, which reportedly was a result of being intoxicated."</item>
		<item>"Ranked the 50th in NME Magazine's annual Cool list in November 2006. "</item>
		<item>"Showed up in an episode of BBC's comedy sketch show \"The Fast Show\" in 1997. "</item>
		<item>"Made a duet with Paul Weller in singing Etta Jones' \"Don't Go To Strangers\" when appeared in his BBC Electric Proms gig. "</item>
		<item>"Went to the same school as Katie Melua did."</item>
		<item>"Suffered from eating disorders."</item>
		<item>"At around age ten, she founded a rap group named Sweet 'n' Sour (she was \"Sour\")."</item>
		<item>"Her mother, Janis, is a pharmacist."</item>
		<item>"Her father, Mitchell Winehouse, is a taxi driver."</item>
		<item>"Due to her bulimia as well as her alcohol problems, she has been a target of the tabloids."</item>
		<item>"Released on bail after being arrested on suspicion of attempting to interfere with a court case involving her husband (18 December 2007)."</item>
		<item>"Friends with singer Remi Wilson (aka Remi Nicole)."</item>
		<item>"Ties with Alicia Keys and Lauryn Hill for the most Grammys (5) won by a woman in a single year."</item>
		<item>"First British artist to win 5 Grammys in a single year (2008)."</item>
		<item>"Found not guilty of assault [July 23, 2009]."</item>
		<item>"Nickname: Wino "</item>
		<item>"Birth Name: Amy Jade Winehouse "</item>
		<item>"She was born Amy Jade Winehouse, on September 14, 1983, in Enfield, London, England, to a Jewish family."</item>
		<item>"Her family shared her love of theater and music."</item>
		<item>"Young Amy Winehouse was a rebellious girl."</item>
		<item>"At age 14, she was expelled from Sylvia Young Theatre School in Marylebone, London. "</item>
		<item>"At age 19, she recorded her debut, Frank (2003)"</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse developed a distinctive style of her own. Her signature beehive hairstyle has become the model for fashion designers."</item>
		<item>"Her fragile personality and self-destructive behavior has been regular tabloid news, and subject of criticism and controversy."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse also performed for Roman Abramovich's party in Moscow; there she earned $2 million for her one-hour gig."</item>
		<item>"Her electic mix of musical genres including RnB, soul and jazz."</item>
		<item>"She is known for her powerful contralto vocals."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse died at the age of 27 on 23 July 2011, at her home in London."</item>
		<item>"Police have said that the cause of her death is \"as yet unexplained\"."</item>
		<item>"On 18 June 2011, Winehouse started her 12-leg 2011 European tour in Belgrade. Local media described her performance as a scandal and disaster, and she was booed off the stage due to her apparently being too drunk to perform."</item>
		<item>"On 21 June it was announced that she had cancelled all shows of her European tour and would be given \"as long as it takes\" to sort herself out."</item>
		<item>"Winehouse's last public appearance took place at Camden's Roundhouse, London on 20 July 2011.when she made a surprise guest appearance on stage to support her goddaughter, Dionne Bromfield who was singing \"Mama Said\" with The Wanted."</item>
		<item>"On 10 July 2008, Winehouse launched her own club night, Snakehips at the Monarch, in the Camden Monarch venue in London."</item>
		<item>"U2 have honoured Amy Winehouse by dedicating a song to the tragic singer."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse predicted she would die at the age of 27."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse's attitude inspired Adele's career."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse's ashes will be mixed with her beloved grandmother's."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse's boyfriend Reg Traviss has been going through \"hell\" since her death."</item>
		<item>"Rapper M.I.A. has unveiled a song in honour of tragic singer Amy Winehouse."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse was reportedly given the all-clear by doctors less than 24 hours before her death."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse \"died alone in bed\" before she was found to be unresponsive by a bodyguard, according to the tragic star's representative."</item>
		<item>"Tragic Amy Winehouse has joined the Forever 27 Club of influential stars who died at 27. Kurt Cobain, Jimi Hendrix, Janis Joplin, Jim Morrison and Rolling Stones star Brian Jones are the most high-profile members of the group."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse was dead by the time emergency services arrived at her home in London on Saturday afternoon."</item>
		<item>"Amy Winehouse is believed to have died from a mix of ecstasy and alcohol. "</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
