<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Em’s in the Guinness Book of World Records for being the fastest selling hip-hop artist."</item>
		<item>"One of the Requirements to be signed to Shady Records is you have to battle Eminem"</item>
		<item>"Em is of Scottish and Welsh decent.".</item>
		<item>"Em has been falsely reported dead by a car crash 4 times and a drug overdose once."</item>
		<item>"Eminem is the oldest member of D12 (b. 1972). Kon Artis is the youngest (b. 1978)."</item>
		<item>"He is a Spiderman fan."</item>
		<item>"Em is a Baptist (just like his mom and the rest of her family). He’s not religious though. Kim’s the one who is Catholic. She’s also not religious."</item>
		<item>"Em wears glasses because he’s near-sighted."</item>
		<item>"Em’s a gadget freak."</item>
		<item>"Em’s favorite porn star is Janet Jacme."</item>
		<item>"Kim and Em’s term of endearment is \"Stinky\"."</item>
		<item>"Despite what was written before, Em did not attempt suicide. He took pills to fight his depression and accidentally OD’d. He was happy to wake up the next day."</item>
		<item>"The platinum bracelet and ring he usually wears both have “DAD” inscribed on them. Both are from Hailie."</item>
		<item>"Despite his chosen profession, Em is still a very quiet individual (much like his character Rabbit) which either surprises or annoys the shit out of people."</item>
		<item>"Em used to have a problem with people staring at him."</item>
		<item>"Em thinks Robin Williams is brilliant and vice versa."</item>
		<item>"Em’s all-time favorite movie is The Matrix."</item>
		<item>"Em thought Luis Resto was Michael Bolton when he first met him"</item>
		<item>"Em had a crush on Madonna when he was 11"</item>
		<item>"The first concert he ever went to is Run DMC, Big Daddy Kane and Queen Latifah in Detroit."</item>
		<item>"Em cuts his own hair"</item>
		<item>"Em’s fave dance song is Busta Rhymes’s \"Put Your Hands Where My Eyes Can See\"."</item>
		<item>"Lose Yourself may have topped the poll on songs that spurs ball players to victory but it also topped the poll on songs most likely to lead to car crashes."</item>
		<item>"Elton John has dedicated his song Rocket Man to Em."</item>
		<item>"Shannon Elizabeth was Em’s first choice to be the girl in \"Superman\"."</item>
		<item>"Neil Tennant (Petshop Boys) has a crush on Em and wishes that the events in their song \"The night I fell in love\" would happen to him."</item>
		<item>"Em and Hailie has a cat named Tigger."</item>
		<item>"For his 8 Mile role, Em dropped from 168 lbs (12 stone or 76.21kg) to 145 lbs (10.35 stone or 65.8kg)."</item>
		<item>"Em wears size XXL clothes."</item>
		<item>"Marshall Jr. and Debbie were in a band called Daddy Warbucks. They played @ Ramada Inns along the Dakota-Montana border."</item>
		<item>"Em prefers Fords. His friends say that he doesn’t like to drive though."</item>
		<item>"Em does not smoke."</item>
		<item>"Em has adopted Dawn’s (Kim’s twin) daughter, Alaina."</item>
		<item>"Dre made Em change (in ‘Love Me’) the line “I’m the equivalent of what will happen if Suge rapped” to \"I’m the equivalent of what will happen if Bush rapped.\"."</item>
		<item>"Em’s other celebrity neighbor in his new Oakland hood is Aretha Franklin."</item>
		<item>"Em received $3 Million for his 8 Mile role."</item>
		<item>"Luis Resto calls Em’s style of production as ‘Classical Hip-Hop’ because of Em’s penchant for using live instruments and minimal sampling."</item>
		<item>"Em did all the three verses of Lose Yourself in one take."</item>
		<item>"Em called on Craig G (of the original Juice Crew) to co-write with him all the rhymes that was recited on 8 Mile."</item>
		<item>"Em’s relatives used to call him Mickey when he was a baby because he had big ears."</item>
		<item>"Dr. Dre and Jimmy Iovine were backstage at the Oscars when Em won. They were there for their boy even if Em wasn’t there."</item>
		<item>"Eminem’s favorite drink is Mountain Dew."</item>
		<item>"It had been Eminem’s dream since he was 16 to sample Aerosmith’s Dream On, his dream came true on the track Sing for the moment."</item>
		<item>"Some of Eminem’s favorite movies are How High?, Orange County, and The Matrix."</item>
		<item>"Eminem’s 99 purple Mustang 2 was sold online for $27,900."</item>
		<item>"Eminem's shoe size is 10 1/2"</item>
		<item>"To record ‘97 Bonnie and Clyde Em told Kim he was taking Hailie to Chuck E. Cheese."</item>
		<item>"The shady one attends public community meetings and even lets kids in the neighborhood play basketball at his house."</item>
		<item>"Eminem’s tattoo artist is Mr. Cartoon, he’s located in California."</item>
		<item>"Em used to spend hours at night studying the dictionary so that he could expand his vocabulary for his ryhmes."</item>
		<item>"Eminem originally wanted to become a comic-book artist."</item>
        <item>"Eminem gave his manager Paul Rosenberg one of the Grammys that he won in 2000"</item>
        <item>"The cast Eminem is wearing in Fight Music is due to an injury Em’s sustained whilst trying to fix his house."</item>
        <item>"The guy dressed as a cactus that in Purple Hills video is also in the beginning of the Without Me video clip."</item>
        <item>"Eminem’s height is 5 foot 8 inches."</item>
        <item>"His full name is Marshall Bruce Mathers III."</item>
        <item>"His birthday is October 17, 1972."</item>
        <item>"Eminem's all time favorite rapper is Tupac Shakur."</item>
        <item>"Eminem dropped out of school after failing 9th grade 3 times, mainly because he skipped school too many times to battle kids on the street corners."</item>
        <item>"Eminem's major influences growing up were his uncle, Ronnie, the Beastie Boys, LL Cool J, 2 Live Crew, Run DMC, and 3rd Bass."</item>
        <item>"Eminem fell in love with rap when she 1st heard Ice-T's \"Reckless\" and started writing rhymes when he was 12 years old."</item>
        <item>"Eminem worked for a factory called Gibbs Machinery when he was 16.  He had a lot of odd jobs (sweeping floors, taking out the trash) and also worked at Little Ceaser's Pizza."</item>
        <item>"Eminem was really quiet at school and had a hard time making friends, but started becoming more social in the 8th grade."</item>
        <item>"Eminem used to spend his free time watching TV and reading comic books."</item>
        <item>"Eminem was 14 when he wrote his first rap song and he wrote it to LL Cool J's \"I'm Bad\"."</item>
        <item>"Eminem started walking at 11 months."</item>
        <item>"His dad left him and his mom when Eminem was only 6 months old."</item>
        <item>"Eminem has two half brothers: Michael and Nathan."</item>
        <item>"Eminem has a half sister named Sarah."</item>
        <item>"Eminem's mother is Scandinavian and his father's family is from the South of Wales."</item>
        <item>"Dre discovered Eminem after finding his demo tape on the floor of his studio."</item>
        <item>"Tom Green and South Park make him laugh like crazy."</item>
        <item>"Eminem like shopping at K-Mart, but is mad because he can't go as much because of his fame."</item>
        <item>"His greatest fear is a crazed fan will kill him at a concert."</item>
        <item>"Although Eminem likes playing basketball, his friends say he can't dribble the ball without traveling."</item>
        <item>"Eminem like to keep in touch with his circle of friends who know him as \"Marshall Mathers\"."</item>
        <item>"Eminem's mom sued Eminem for $12 million for defamation, settled for $25,000."</item>
        <item>"Eminem has a total of 10 tattoos."</item>
        
	</string-array>
</resources>
