<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Barack Obama’s IQ is 143."</item>
		<item>"He and his wife bought a house in Chicago in 2005. Back then it cost $1.65 million. The house has 4 fireplaces."</item>
		<item>"He was born in Honolulu, Hawaii but went to live in Indonesia with his mum when the parents divorced. There he was introduced to dog meat, snake meat, and roasted grasshopper."</item>
		<item>"He doesn’t like ice-cream. He worked in Baskin-Robbins as a teenager. That’s where his distaste for ice-cream comes from."</item>
		<item>"He loves playing Scrabble. He never commented on how good he is, though." </item>
		<item>"According to his wife Michelle he is very romantic. He is not a door opener but he remembers every anniversary and brings her flowers all the time."</item>
		<item>"Every night when he is at home he reads the Harry Potter books to his oldest daughter Malia."</item>
		<item>"He collects Spider-Man and Conan the Barbarian comics."</item>
		<item>"He was known as \"O'Bomber\" at high school for his skill at basketball."</item>
		<item>"His name means \"one who is blessed\" in Swahili."</item>
		<item>"His favourite meal is wife Michelle's shrimp linguini."</item>
		<item>"He won a Grammy in 2006 for the audio version of his memoir, Dreams From My Father."</item>
		<item>"He is left-handed – the sixth post-war president to be left-handed."</item>
		<item>"He has read every Harry Potter book."</item>
		<item>"He owns a set of red boxing gloves autographed by Muhammad Ali."</item>
		<item>"He worked in a Baskin-Robbins ice cream shop as a teenager and now can't stand ice cream."</item>
		<item>"His favourite snacks are chocolate-peanut protein bars."</item>
		<item>"He can speak Spanish."</item>
		<item>"While on the campaign trail he refused to watch CNN and had sports channels on instead."</item>
		<item>"His favourite drink is black forest berry iced tea."</item>
		<item>"He promised Michelle he would quit smoking before running for president – he didn't."</item>
		<item>"He kept a pet ape called Tata while in Indonesia."</item>
		<item>"He can bench press an impressive 200lbs."</item>
		<item>"He was known as Barry until university when he asked to be addressed by his full name."</item>
		<item>"His favourite book is Moby-Dick by Herman Melville."</item>
		<item>"He visited Wokingham, Berks, in 1996 for the stag party of his half-sister's fiancé, but left when a stripper arrived."</item>
		<item>"His desk in his Senate office once belonged to Robert Kennedy."</item>
		<item>"He and Michelle made $4.2 million (£2.7 million) last year, with much coming from sales of his books."</item>
		<item>"His favourite films are Casablanca and One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest."</item>
		<item>"He carries a tiny Madonna and child statue and a bracelet belonging to a soldier in Iraq for good luck."</item>
		<item>"He applied to appear in a black pin-up calendar while at Harvard but was rejected by the all-female committee."</item>
		<item>"His favourite music includes Miles Davis, Bob Dylan, Bach and The Fugees."</item>
		<item>"He took Michelle to see the Spike Lee film Do The Right Thing on their first date."</item>
		<item>"He enjoys playing Scrabble and poker."</item>
		<item>"He doesn't drink coffee and rarely drinks alcohol."</item>
		<item>"He would have liked to have been an architect if he were not a politician."</item>
		<item>"As a teenager he took drugs including marijuana and cocaine."</item>
		<item>"His daughters' ambitions are to go to Yale before becoming an actress (Malia) and to sing and dance (Sasha)."</item>
		<item>"He hates the youth trend for trousers which sag beneath the backside."</item>
		<item>"He repaid his student loan only four years ago after signing his book deal."</item>
		<item>"Daughter Malia's godmother is Jesse Jackson's daughter Santita."</item>
		<item>"He says his worst habit is constantly checking his BlackBerry."</item>
		<item>"He uses an Apple Mac laptop."</item>
		<item>"He drives a Ford Escape Hybrid, having ditched his gas-guzzling Chrysler 300."</item>
		<item>"He wears $1,500 (£952) Hart Schaffner Marx suits."</item>
		<item>"He owns four identical pairs of black size 11 shoes."</item>
		<item>"He has his hair cut once a week by his Chicago barber, Zariff, who charges $21 (£13)."</item>
		<item>"His favourite fictional television programmes are Mash and The Wire."</item>
		<item>"He was given the code name \"Renegade\" by his Secret Service handlers."</item>
		<item>"He was nicknamed \"Bar\" by his late grandmother."</item>
		<item>"He plans to install a basketball court in the White House grounds."</item>
		<item>"His favourite artist is Pablo Picasso."</item>
		<item>"His speciality as a cook is chilli."</item>
		<item>"He has said many of his friends in Indonesia were \"street urchins\"."</item>
		<item>"He keeps on his desk a carving of a wooden hand holding an egg, a Kenyan symbol of the fragility of life."</item>	
		<item>"His late father was a senior economist for the Kenyan government."</item>
		<item>"Obama is a Christian whose religious views developed in his adult life."</item>
		<item>"Obama is a well known supporter of the Chicago White Sox."</item>
		<item>"In his childhood and adolesence was a fan of the Pittsburgh Steelers."</item>	
		<item>"He is also primarily a Chicago Bears fan in the NFL."</item>
		<item>"Obama speaks Indonesian at the conversational level, which he learned during his four childhood years in Jakarta."</item>
		<item>"Obama is the 44th and current President of the United States."</item>
		<item>"Barack Hussein Obama II was on born August 4, 1961"</item>
		<item>"Obama previously served as a United States senator from Illinois, from January 2005 until he resigned following his victory in the 2008 presidential election."</item>
		<item>"A native of Honolulu, Hawaii, Obama is a graduate of Columbia University and Harvard Law School, where he was the president of the Harvard Law Review."</item>
		<item>"He was a community organizer in Chicago before earning his law degree."</item>
		<item>"He worked as a civil rights attorney in Chicago and taught constitutional law at the University of Chicago Law School from 1992 to 2004."</item>
		<item>"He served three terms representing the 13th district in the Illinois Senate from 1997 to 2004."</item>
		<item>"His mother, Stanley Ann Dunham, was born in Wichita, Kansas and was of mostly English descent."</item>
		<item>"His father, Barack Obama, Sr., was a Luo from Nyang'oma Kogelo, Nyanza Province, Kenya."</item>
		<item>"Obama's parents met in 1960 in a Russian language class at the University of Hawaiʻi at Mānoa, where his father was a foreign student on scholarship."</item>
		<item>"Obama's parents married on February 2, 1961, separated when Obama Sr. went to Harvard University on scholarship, and divorced in 1964."</item>
		<item>"Obama Sr. remarried and returned to Kenya, visiting Barack in Hawaii only once, in 1971. He died in an automobile accident in 1982."</item>
		<item>"From ages six to ten, Obama attended local schools in Jakarta, including Besuki Public School and St. Francis of Assisi School"</item>
		<item>"Obama stands 6 ft 1 in (185 cm)."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
