<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"He is the National Spokesperson for the U.S. Department of Transportation's \"Get Big On Safety\" campaign."</item>
<item>"Sold 20 million albums in USA and 35 million worldwide since 1994."</item>
<item>"On March 30, 2010, Usher released his sixth studio album Raymond v. Raymond, which became his third consecutive album to debut at number one on the US Billboard 200 chart."</item>
<item>"He rose to fame in the late 1990s with the release of his second album My Way, which spawned his first Billboard Hot 100 number-one hit, \"Nice and Slow\"."</item>
<item>"His nickname is Big Ush."</item>
<item>"Tameka Johnelle Foster had Usher Jr nov 26, and besides she has three boys from Ryan Foster."</item>
<item>"Usher's mother Jonnetta Patton is also his manager."</item>
<item>"His favorite pro team is The Atlanta Hawks."</item>
<item>"His favorite women perfume is Spring Fever Perfume. (Use This Perfume If You Want To Impress Usher)"</item>
<item>"Usher once toured with Janet Jackson (in 1998 for his My Way album)."</item>
<item>"His favorite flower is Orchid."</item>
<item>"His favorite snacks are Strawberries, Whip cream, and Chocolate."</item>
<item>"Raymond v. Raymond album has been certified platinum by the RIAA and spawned another Billboard Hot 100 number-one hit \"OMG\"."</item>
<item>"His favorite cologne is Amen."</item>
<item>"Usher was born on 14.10.1978."</item>
<item>"Usher's 2008 album Here I Stand sold over 5 million copies worldwide, and its lead single \"Love In This Club\" peaked at number-one on the Billboard Hot 100."</item>
<item>"His favorite singers are Danny Hathaway, R. Kelly, Stevie Wonder , and Michael Jackson."</item>
<item>"Usher practices Kendo and Karate"</item>
<item>"\"OMG\" song became his ninth number one in the United States, making him the first 2010s artist to collect number one singles in three consecutive decades, and only the fourth artist of all-time to achieve the feat."</item>
<item>"Usher's first acting debut: UPN TV series \"Mesha\"."</item>
<item>"His favorite movie is \"The five Heartbits\"."</item>
<item>"When he was seven he was singing in his mom's choir at St. Elmo Missionary Baptist Church in Tennesse."</item>
<item>"His favorite song is \"As We Lay\" by Shirley Murdock."</item>
<item>"Usher has been on the music scene for 15+ years! His first album \"Usher\" debuted in 1994."</item>
<item>"Usher was on the hit tv show Star Search and won several times."</item>
<item>"Usher is married to Tameka Johnelle Foster."</item>
<item>"When Usher was spotted by LaFace Records on Star Search he was only 13."</item>
<item>"His favorite food is Seafood and \"Soul food\"."</item>
<item>"Usher has a Harley Davidson motorcycle."</item>
<item>"Usher created his own record label, US Records, in 1998."</item>
<item>"A historic record - Usher is the third leading pop artist in history and the very first solo artist to have 3 singles in the Hot 100's TOP 10 list."</item>
<item>"His third album 8701 (2001) produced the Billboard Hot 100 number-one hits \"U Remind Me\" and \"U Got It Bad\"."</item>
<item>"Confessions has the highest first week sales for an R&amp;B artist in history, and sold over 20 million copies worldwide."</item>
<item>"Usher's favorite flowers are orchids and his favorite book is Conversations With God."</item>
<item>"He was born in Dallas, Texas."</item>
<item>"Usher has 1 sibling - a brother named James Lackey."</item>
<item>"His height is 5'9."</item>
<item>"His favorite rapper The Notorious B.I.G.."</item>
<item>"Usher's success continued with his 2004 album Confessions, which has sold over ten million copies in the United States, and been certified diamond by the RIAA."</item>
<item>"His first starring film role was in \"Light It Up\"."</item>
<item>"Usher has starred in movies &amp; tv shows (Moesha, The Parenthood, The Faculty, She's All That, Texas Rangers, Light It Up, Disney's Gepetto and more)."</item>
<item>"When Usher lived in Chattanooga, TN he was in a singing group."</item>
<item>"His favorite color is Yellow."</item>
<item>"Two Dogs Named Star and Sugar are Usher's pets."</item>
<item>"Usher lived with Sean \"P.Diddy\" Combs during the production of his first album \"Usher\"."</item>
<item>"He was raised in Chattanooga, Tennessee until age 12."</item>
<item>"Confessions album spawned a record breaking four consecutive Billboard Hot 100 number-one hits \"Yeah!\", \"Burn\", \"Confessions Part II\", and \"My Boo\"."</item>
<item>"Usher's full name is Usher Raymond IV."</item>
<item>"Usher has done duets with Monica &amp; Mariah Carey."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
