<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Better late than never, but never late is better."</item>
		<item>"Shout out to the home owners, the girls that got diplomas and enough money to loan us."</item>
		<item>"All the girls that played me eat yo mutha heart out it's Drizzzyyyy"</item>
		<item>"Still spending every dollar they encourage me to save but I'm gooood"</item>
		<item>"Look at where I landed, you would think I planned it. I'm just doin me and you can never understand it."</item>
		<item>"It takes a certain type of man to teach, to be far from hood but understand the streets."</item>
		<item>"Wayne if your on Mars can you pick me up from Jupiter."</item>
		<item>"My reality is brighter than your dreams are."</item>
		<item>"I'm still myself, suicide bars I kill myself, charge it to the game I bill myself, and I don't feel yall but I feel myself."</item>
		<item>"I tell patron truths, I tell you Henny lies."</item>
		<item>"Drake just stands for Do Right And Kill Everything."</item>
		<item>"I meet quotas while you rappers having sleep overs, spending nights in the studio tryna beat Hova."</item>
		<item>"You accomplish in a week what I'm daily required."</item>
		<item>"If amazing was a young bitch, I'd be going to jail cuz I'm fucking amazing."</item>
		<item>"They say real girls ain't never perfect, perfect girls ain't never real."</item>
		<item>"Cause you know life is what we make it and a chance is like a picture, it'd be nice if you'd just take it."</item>
		<item>"I need you to rescue me from my destiny. I'm tryna live right and give you whatever's left of me."</item>
		<item>"I be up all night, whole crew's in here, 'cause I don't really know who I'ma lose this year."</item>
		<item>"Famous like a drug that I've taken too much of. But I never ever trip, just peace, happiness, and love."</item>
		<item>"And if you dolled up, I got the voodoo for you b-tches."</item>
		<item>"Bracelet sayin' you should quit. Cars sayin' f-ck ya life."</item>
		<item>"I'm havin' a good time, they just tryin' to ruin it. Shout out to the fact that I'm the youngest n---a doin' it."</item>
		<item>"N---as with no money act like money isn't everything."</item>
		<item>"Kush rolled, glass full, I prefer the better things."</item>
		<item>"Okay, we outta here, toodles to you b-tches."</item>
		<item>"And life ain't a rehearsal the cameras always rollin."</item>
		<item>"Like I catch em stealing flows cause I swear I never loaned it."</item>
		<item>"Every time you see me I look like I hit the lotto twice."</item>
		<item>"World Series attitude, champagne bottle life. Nothing ever changes so tonight is like tomorrow night."</item>
		<item>"Im bout my paper like a muthf---ing scratch and win."</item>
		<item>"If you think I'ma quit before I die - dream on."</item>
		<item>"I did it overnight, it couldn't happen any quicker."</item>
		<item>"I can teach you how to speak my language - Rosetta Stone."</item>
		<item>"Bout to set it off in this bitch - Jada Pinkett."</item>
		<item>"I have these n----s trippin', no luggage."</item>
		<item>"Just holla if you got me and f--k you if you had me."</item>
		<item>"And whoever got the torch just can't seem to hold it steady cause I see the flame flickerin'."</item>
		<item>"Please startin doin' you, I been doin' me."</item>
		<item>"And I got love for everybody, even if you suein' me."</item>
		<item>"Coldest thing droppin' and these b-tches wanna snow blow. And they just give me head while the haters give me promo."</item>
		<item>"I'm still fly, I'm sky high, and I dare anybody to try and cut my wings."</item>
		<item>"Startin' poppin bottles cause it's ATL tradition to."</item>
		<item>"I am on a 24 hour champagne diet."</item>
		<item>"So can you do me a favor? If i pull it together, make it sooner than later."</item>
		<item>"I want it all, thats why I strive for it. I know that it's coming - I just hope that i'm alive for it."</item>
		<item>"This lost boy got fly without Peter Pan."</item>
		<item>"I think better when I'm not sober."</item>
		<item>"I may not mean nothing to y'all but understand nothin was done for me so i dont plan on stoppin' at all."</item>
		<item>"Everybody talk and everybody listen, but somehow it's always the truth that comes up missing."</item>
		<item>"We all got dreams and we all star reaching."</item>
		<item>"Sweat pants, hair tied, chillin with no make-up on. That's when you're the prettiest, I hope that you don't take it wrong."</item>
		<item>"She just stuck in houstatlantavegas."</item>
		<item>"Life change for us every single week so it's good but I know this ain't the peak yet."</item>
		<item>"Last name ever first name ever greatest."</item>
		<item>"24 hours from greatness, I'm that close. Don't ever forget the moment you began to doubt."</item>
		<item>"I just want to be successful."</item>
		<item>"And you ain't even gotta ask twice. You can have my heart or we can share it like the last slice."</item>
		<item>"And I can hear the critics talking over the applause."</item>
		<item>"The girl or the world. You see someone gotta lose. I thought i could have it all, do I really gotta choose?"</item>
		<item>"Tellin every girl she the one for me and I ain't even plannin to call."</item>
		<item>"Everyone who doubted me is askin' for forgiveness."</item>
		<item>"Inside I'm treadin water steady trying to swim ashore."</item>
		<item>"We don't have Resolutions we've just got Reservations. I try to live my life right every day."</item>
		<item>"Seven days without love makes one weak."</item>
		<item>"Cause you know life is what we make it and a chance is like a picture, it'd be nice if you'd just take it."</item>
		<item>"I need you to rescue me from my destiny. I'm tryna live right and give you whatever's left of me."</item>
		<item>"I be up all night, whole crew's in here, 'cause I don't really know who I'ma lose this year."</item>
		<item>"Famous like a drug that I've taken too much of. But I never ever trip, just peace, happiness, and love."</item>
		<item>"And if you dolled up, I got the voodoo for you b-tches."</item>
		<item>"Bracelet sayin' you should quit. Cars sayin' f-ck ya life."</item>
		<item>"I'm havin' a good time, they just tryin' to ruin it. Shout out to the fact that I'm the youngest nigga doin' it."</item>
		<item>"Niggas with no money act like money isn't everything."</item>
		<item>"Kush rolled, glass full, I prefer the better things."</item>
		<item>"Okay, we outta here, toodles to you bitches."</item>
		<item>"And life ain't a rehearsal the cameras always rollin."</item>
		<item>"Every time you see me I look like I hit the lotto twice."</item>
		<item>"Im bout my paper like a muthfucking scratch and win."</item>
		<item>"If you think I'ma quit before I die - dream on."</item>
		<item>"I did it overnight, it couldn't happen any quicker."</item>
		<item>"I have these niggas trippin', no luggage."</item>
		<item>"Just holla if you got me and fuck you if you had me."</item>
		<item>"And I got love for everybody, even if you suein' me."</item>
		<item>"Please startin doin' you, I been doin' me."</item>
		<item>"Coldest thing droppin' and these b-tches wanna snow blow. And they just give me head while the haters give me promo."</item>
		<item>"And whoever got the torch just can't seem to hold it steady cause I see the flame flickerin'"</item>
		<item>"Startin' poppin bottles cause it's ATL tradition to."</item>
		<item>"I'm still fly, I'm sky high, and I dare anybody to try and cut my wings."</item>
		<item>"I want it all, thats why I strive for it. I know that it's coming - I just hope that i'm alive for it."</item>
		<item>"So can you do me a favor? If i pull it together, make it sooner than later."</item>
		<item>"Everybody talk and everybody listen, but somehow it's always the truth that comes up missing."</item>
		<item>"Sweat pants, hair tied, chillin with no make-up on. That's when you're the prettiest, I hope that you don't take it wrong."</item>
		<item>"Life change for us every single week so it's good but I know this ain't the peak yet."</item>
		<item>"Last name ever first name ever greatest."</item>
		<item>"24 hours from greatness, I'm that close. Don't ever forget the moment you began to doubt."</item>
		<item>"I may not mean nothing to y'all but understand nothin was done for me so i dont plan on stoppin' at all."</item>
		<item>"I think better when I'm not sober."</item>
		<item>"Everyone who doubted me is askin' for forgiveness."</item>
		<item>"Tellin every girl she the one for me and I ain't even plannin to call."</item>
		<item>"And you ain't even gotta ask twice. You can have my heart or we can share it like the last slice."</item>
		<item>"I always fall your type."</item>
		<item>"Everybody dies but not everybody lives."</item>
		<item>"Inside I'm treadin water steady trying to swim ashore."</item>
		<item>"Talking to myself but I never listen."</item>
		<item>"The hardest part about the fucking business is minding your own."</item>
		<item>"I wonder why I never learned my lesson."</item>
		<item>"I've been down this road before and yeah I skidded but forget it."</item>
		<item>"Doin' target practice; all these bitches just aiming to please."</item>
		<item>"Niggas wanna be friends how coincidental."</item>
		<item>"A young King, pay me in gold."</item>
		<item>"You a star in my eyes."</item>
		<item>"I swear this shit is as fun as it looks."</item>
		<item>"I'm really tryna make it more than what it is, cause everybody dies but not everybody lives."</item>
		<item>"I heard you good with them soft lips."</item>
		<item>"I come alive in the night time."</item>
		<item>"Say my name, say my name, wear it out."</item>
		<item>"I might just put up with the arguing and stay for real."</item>
		<item>"You with all those curves and me without no breaks."</item>
		<item>"Tell them bitches that you'll always be my misses."</item>
		<item>"The hardest part about the fucking business is minding your own."</item>
		<item>"Even when I throw them deuces you just send it back around."</item>
		<item>"Life's story is as quick as the wink of an eye...love's story is merely hello and goodbye...until we meet again..."</item>
		<item>"Time flies like an arrow; fruit flies like a banana."</item>
		<item>"Even though it seems you're losing me...and things ain't what they used to be...dont worry."</item>
		<item>"Niggas with no money act like money isn't everything."</item>
		<item>"I'm busy getting rich, I don't want trouble."</item>
		<item>"I got money in these jeans, so they fit me kinda snug."</item>
		<item>"It's feeling like the second chance and its the first impression."</item>
		<item>"I prefer the better things."</item>
		<item>"I'm busy getting rich, I don't want trouble."</item>
		<item>"I got money in these jeans, so they fit me kinda snug."</item>
		<item>"All up in yo face man I hate to put you through it."</item>
		<item>"I love my team, I would die for them niggas."</item>
		<item>"I'm having a good time, they just trying to ruin it. Shoutout to the fact that I'm the youngest nigga doing it."</item>
		<item>"Whole crew's in here 'cause I don't really know who I'ma lose this year."</item>
		<item>"Show me a good time."</item>
		<item>"I live for the nights that I can't remember with the people that I won't forget."</item>
		<item>"Let's get right, now that I'm here show me a good time."</item>
		<item>"How did I end up right here with you after all the things that I been through? It's been one of those days you try to forget about it, take a shot and let it out."</item>
		<item>"Presidential suite girl - Barack Hussein."</item>
		<item>"Young and rich and out of control."</item>
		<item>"Call me overrated, or created or two jaded, because anyway you put it bitch I made it!"</item>
		<item>"Ain't no turning back for me; I'm in it til it's over."</item>
		<item>"You can't have my heart, the doctor told me I'd be dead without it."</item>
		<item>"You let me go, little did you know I could've made it all on my own."</item>
		<item>"You have to risk going too far to discover just how far you can really go."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather be an optimist who is sometimes wrong than a pessimist who is always right."</item>
		<item>"They stay kicking it with me like a field goal."</item>
		<item>"And the way that I jack son you think that Drake new Samuel."</item>
		<item>"So they don't like me and pop parties and yet they never invite me."</item>
		<item>"Nosey niggas speaking in my window."</item>
		<item>"Took a lot of patience and action, I grind so I'm anticipating relaxin."</item>
		<item>"I provide protection if you open up the door for me."</item>
		<item>"Dedicating time when I really can't afford to be."</item>
		<item>"Who killed Chivalry? They need to get their sentencing, meanwhile we argue and I can't get a sentence in."</item>
		<item>"You be the baddest girl around round round and they notice, they notice."</item>
		<item>"Them other niggas just wanna hit it, but if they had it they wouldn't know what to do with it!"</item>
		<item>"I'm addicted to fresh, so you could either get with the real or stick with the rest."</item>
		<item>"Get it, got it, good, gotta get it going 'cause I don't want you confused it's always better knowing."</item>
		<item>"It's only right I make you aware I am the only rapper taking you there."</item>
		<item>"Put on some P. Reign, thats somethin hood girl. We all know that RnB is for the good girls."</item>
		<item>"They tend to call me a college cat, I ball hard and Toronto please acknowldge that."</item>
		<item>"I'm more than just an option; refuse or be forgotten."</item>
		<item>"We all fall... so may I send you four blessings... Older Wine, Younger Lovers, Faster Cars, and a Slow Descent."</item>
		<item>"Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Just walk beside me and be my friend."</item>
		<item>"When a young man complains that a young lady has no heart, it's pretty certain that she has his."</item>
		<item>"I better find your loving...I better find your heart."</item>
		<item>"Today you are you, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is You'er than You."</item>
		<item>"Being real is like being a lady... if you have to tell people you are... you aren't."</item>
		<item>"I won't judge her, and I could never love her. But to her I'm just a Baller and she could find another..."</item>
		<item>"Just smile and smell good."</item>
		<item>"Life ain't no rehearsal, the cameras always rolling."</item>
		<item>"Life is like a confused teacher...first she gives the test and then teaches the lesson."</item>
		<item>"Cooler than Mick Jagger with the stones, stop jacking my swagger cause my swagger is my own."</item>
		<item>"Don't go through life...grow through life."</item>
		<item>"Now that it's over. I should have known better than to think this is real and you could be mine."</item>
		<item>"Nothing ever changing so tonight is like tomorrow night."</item>
		<item>"May all your joys be pure joys, and all your pain champagne."</item>
		<item>"I hope this isn't one of those forever things, its funny how money can change everything."</item>
		<item>"I sit and drink wine and watch californiacation of life!"</item>
		<item>"Point the biggest skeptic out, I'll make him a believer."</item>
		<item>"I want it all that's why I strive for it. Diss me and never get a reply for it."</item>
		<item>"Life is moving fast where the fuck do all these minutes go?!"</item>
		<item>"If they love u to death, never die on them."</item>
		<item>"The pressure's on both hearts beat like a metronome both in sync like a justin song, feel so right but it's just so wrong."</item>
		<item>"So we don't confirm the fling keep avoiding all the questions you can teach me many things i'm just scared to learn a lesson."</item>
		<item>"No strings attached your love is so wifi."</item>
		<item>"She just too far away for affection, so I pray that we never lose the connection..."</item>
		<item>"Today I bent the truth to be kind, and I have no regret, for I am far surer of what is kind than I am of what is true."</item>
		<item>"As far as recession goes I know it's a difficult time out here for people, but me, myself I honestly have to say I've been put in a blessed position."</item>
		<item>"Shows are great, internet is great, but at the end of the day you got to sell records."</item>
		<item>"Nigga, I'm the man, I sent your girl message; Said I see you when I can She send me one back but I ain't never read it. 'Cause pussy's only pussy and I get it when I need it."</item>
		<item>"Don't know why it happens every time we alone. But here we are again and I swear I'm in my zone."</item>
		<item>"So I'ma sip this drink till that motherfucker gone. Than you go get undressed and we gon' get it on."</item>
		<item>"It's funny how someone else's success brings pain."</item>
		<item>"When you're no longer involved that person has it all, and you're just stuck standing there."</item>
		<item>"I'm gonna' need you to say something baby."</item>
		<item>"Uhh, I am the topic of conversation this a celebration."</item>
		<item>"As far as liquor goes, I'm a hennessy man."</item>
		<item>"Nicki Minaj is a very tempting individual, she's very attractive; we're close."</item>
		<item>"In order to gain loyal fans, I had to give away a lot of music."</item>
		<item>"I wanna do it all tonight I got plans, I have a certain lust for life and as it stands."</item>
		<item>"Let's toast to the fact that I moved out my momma's basement."</item>
		<item>"Killing shit the ever so talented Mr. Ripley."</item>
		<item>"What's a star when its most important fan is missing?"</item>
		<item>"Other niggas' situations, they are all depressin'."</item>
		<item>"I drive two black cars, I named them Malcolm X and Martin Luther."</item>
		<item>"I am more than what you bargained for and nothing less than real."</item>
		<item>"Never drop the ball, fuck are y'all thinkin'?"</item>
		<item>"Making sure the Young Money ship is never sinkin."</item>
		<item>"I could teach you how to speak my language, Rosetta Stone."</item>
		<item>"Finally here, I'm a star with the timing, my swagga is chill, and my flow is reclining."</item>
		<item>"Universe is just a verse of me, I keep it generic and the niggas take it personally."</item>
		<item>"Livin life from a whole different angle, only see the road through the wings of an angel!"</item>
		<item>"It's a shame, she had me convinced that she could've been a dime. I guess, I lost another one to the wintertime."</item>
		<item>"If amazing was a young girl I would be in jail because I'm fuckin' amazing."</item>
		<item>"Either or my nigga, make sure you don't get shelved. Make sure your money's right and they do a promotion well, so you could get checks cut like Benedict in Ocean's 12."</item>
		<item>"Fuck you, pussy ass haters you should do you."</item>
		<item>"You ain't heard of me, then you should go and get a blues clue; oops I mean a red clue, Wayne's here; Suwoo."</item>
		<item>"To have known me would mean there was a knew me."</item>
		<item>"When raindrops hit the tin roof its crazy. Thats a metaphor, did I lose ya baby?"</item>
		<item>"And I belong right where you see me. Ain't on the fence about it, I ain't Mr. Feeny."</item>
		<item>"I can paint what's goin through my mind, racing against myself but I'm a couple steps behind."</item>
		<item>"Why do i feel so alone? Like everybody passing through the studio is in character as if we acting out a movie role."</item>
		<item>"I'm still fly, I'm sky high; and I dare anybody to try and cut my wings."</item>
		<item>"I'm addicted to this life, its gonna be hard to quit."</item>
		<item>"I be at the parties where you stuck outside and cant come in."</item>
		<item>"I got a sex pistol pointed right at you."</item>
		<item>"Nothing ever changes so tonight is like tomorrow night."</item>
		<item>"Say baby, Ive got to mention that if i you were a star youd be the one I'm searching for."</item>
		<item>"Hate is so familiar to me, Im slowly embracing it. Doesnt come natural...bear with me it could take a bit."</item>
		<item>"I know what to do with it."</item>
		<item>"Go Cinderella. Go Cinderella. Orgasm blush. Lipstick n conceiler. Devil in a tight dress. Girl you a killer and aint nobody realer."</item>
		<item>"We walk the same path, but got on different shoes."</item>
		<item>"Until you find yourself, its impossible to lose you. Because I never had you, although I would be glad to."</item>
		<item>"People I dont have the time to hang with always look at me and say the same shit. You promised me you would never change."</item>
		<item>"Many fine things can be done in a day if you dont always make that day tomorrow."</item>
		<item>"I pick and choose. I dont get shit confused. I got a small circle, Im not with different crews."</item>
		<item>"Kush got the room smelling like teen spirit."</item>
		<item>"You never see it coming. You just get to see it go."</item>
		<item>"Im sitting in a chair but in the future its a throne."</item>
		<item>"I dont judge her but I could never love her."</item>
		<item>"I be gettin' high, just to balance out the lows."</item>
		<item>"They be staring at the money like its unfamiliar."</item>
		<item>"Life aint no rehearsal: the cameras always rollin."</item>
		<item>"Who do you look up to when youre better than your idols?"</item>
		<item>"R.I.P. to the girl you used to see. Her days are over, baby shes over. Ive decided to give you all of me."</item>
		<item>"Lifes story is as quick as the wink of an eye¦loves story is merely hello and goodbye¦until we meet again."</item>
		<item>"You promised me you would never change."</item>
		<item>"She doesnt ever worry, if she wants it shell get it on her own, she knows theres more to life, and shes scared of ending up alone."</item>
		<item>"Fame is like a drug that Ive taken too much of...but I never ever trip, just peace, happiness, and love."</item>
		<item>"I'm really tryna make it more than what it is, cuz everybody dies but not everybody lives!"</item>
		<item>"I pop bottles cause I bottle my emotions, at least I put it out in the open."</item>
		<item>"Hope you forgive me.....never meant wrong. Tried to be patient but waited too long...."</item>
		<item>"Live without pretending, Love without depending, Listen without defending, Speak without offending."</item>
		<item>"Better late than never, but never late is better."</item>
		<item>"They say real girls ain't never perfect, perfect girls ain't never real."</item>
		<item>"I'm really tryna make it more than what it is, cause everybody dies but not everybody lives."</item>
		<item>"We always ignore the ones who adore us, and adore the ones who ignore us."</item>
		<item>"I know they say that first love is the sweetest, but that first cut is the deepest."</item>
		<item>"You gotta own it if you want it. Kisses all on her body, she tells me live in the moment. And baby, Ill never forget none of that. Girl I told you I was coming back"</item>
		<item>"La Familia, Ive been inducted and instructed to stunt on these niggas we dont really fuck wit"</item>
		<item>"In one nigga, amazing shit I got that Courtney Love for you, that crazy shit"</item>
		<item>"I dont drink every bottle I own, I be aging shit. And I got them wedding ring flows, that engaging shit"</item>
		<item>"Girls countin on me to be there like missing rubbers, I'm on some Marvin Gaye shit a bunch of distant lovers."</item>
		<item>"Hope you forgive me, I never meant wrong. Tried to be patient... but waited too long. But I would of came back."</item>
		<item>"I'm urging all daughters to kiss they mothers, with those lips that all the lipstick covers. You're never too grown up to miss and hug her."</item>
		<item>"I hate callin women bitches but bitches love it."</item>
		<item>"Dedicating time when I really can't afford to be, I'll provide protection if you open the door for me."</item>
		<item>"They always say the hottest love has the coldest end."</item>
		<item>"Don't get impatient when it takes to long and drink it all even when it taste too strong."</item>
		<item>"I gotta feel alive, even if it kills me. Promise to always give you me, the real me."</item>
		<item>"The always tell me no one is working as hard as you, and even though I laugh it off man its probably true."</item>
		<item>"I keep thinking how young can you die from old age."</item>
		<item>"Ice cream conversations, they all want the scoop."</item>
		<item>"Oh well I guess you win some and lose some, long as the outcome is income."</item>
		<item>"I think I'm scared of what the future holds. I was wishing for some things and now I'm use to those."</item>
		<item>"Every girl I meet thinks I'm fucking groupie hoes. The honesty of my music has left me too exposed."</item>
		<item>"Now security follow me everywhere so I'm never actually am alone, I just always feel alone."</item>
		<item>"Yall the reason for a lot of my devotion, you know I spend money because spending time is hopeless."</item>
		<item>"Staring at the members of my team who get questioned about they profit from this million dollar scheme. Just know that I'm in debt for you defending all our dreams."</item>
		<item>"I could use a writer to balance my flows. But I never share my thoughts, This is all a nigga knows."</item>
		<item>"I be getting high just to balance out the lows."</item>
		<item>"You always be callin her, she ain't never answerin, you ain't figured out I am the reason she's cancelin."</item>
		<item>"The game ain't always fair and that's the thing though, you can play ya heart but everyone don't get a ring though."</item>
		<item>"Can I hit it in the morning? The sun rise while your moanin."</item>
		<item>"I use to to go to the stables and get the kids to bet me, and I would always ride the stallions whenever she let me."</item>
		<item>"Baby you winter time cold, the night is still young drink that dinner wine slow."</item>
		<item>"Stunt so hard I make these niggas hate summer, and pray for winter. But when it's winter time I'm still waiting on these niggas at the finish line."</item>
		<item>"I let the beat bang I don't claim colors, honestly the honesty is why the game loves us."</item>
		<item>"I'm the one to blame, now that I'm around shit will never be the same."</item>
		<item>"I'm tryna bring it home even if I gotta do it on my own, I'm a mufukkin killlaaaa"</item>
		<item>"Even when I'm not functioning in tip top shape, I can bench as much as hip hop weighs."</item>
		<item>"You would swear we planted trees the way the money's grown. We been busy like some bees no honeycomb, and you can prolly feel the breeze when the money's blown."</item>
		<item>"From the begining to the end know I'm into making history not into making friends."</item>
		<item>"I infiltrated the game, I was hesitant at first then feared what it would change. Now I'm high off the success and faded off of the fame."</item>
		<item>"Man I love my team.. I would die for them n-ggas.."</item>
		<item>"I be up all night.. whole crews in here, cause I don't really know who I'mma lose this year."</item>
		<item>"I'm about whatever man.. F-ck what they be talking about, they opinon doesn't count, we the only thing that matters."</item>
		<item>"Fame is like a drug that I've taken too much of but I never ever trip just peace happiness and love."</item>
		<item>"I'm busy getting rich, I don't want trouble. I made enough for two niggas boy stunt double."</item>
		<item>"I tried to told you, Drizzy still aint nothing nice. Bracelet saying you should quit, cars saying f-ck ya life."</item>
		<item>"Kush rolled, glass full, I prefer the better things. Niggas with no money act like money isn't everything."</item>
		<item>"Before these haters kill me in my sleep, I'd like to say its been a pleasure."</item>
		<item>"Ducking your questions, f-ck your suggestions, money gets all of my love and affection."</item>
		<item>"Im nervous but im about to kill it cause they about to let the realist team in."</item>
		<item>"Girls fall through like coins in a couch, now we just f-ckin all the b-tches they warned us about."</item>
		<item>"This one is for all my niggas from my city tryin to diss. Without a response from me you really fail to exist, and I love to see you fail that feelin' there is the shit."</item>
		<item>"Weezy im just out here reppin' us, till I get to shake the hand of the man that's blessin' us."</item>
		<item>"People ask how music is goin' I heard it pays, I just came off makin' 2 million in 30 days."</item>
		<item>"Take a look at yourself the mirror's revealin'. If you aint got it you ain't got it the theory is brilliant."</item>
		<item>"Im in the crib stackin' money from here to the ceilin'. Whatever it is I got is clearly appealin'."</item>
		<item>"Look how the champagne diamonds flow. Find dining, pour another another glass when the wine is low."</item>
		<item>"Discussin' life and all our common goals, smart kids that smoke weed, honor roll."</item>
		<item>"Don't ask permisson, just ask forgiveness."</item>
		<item>"If you pillow talking with the women that are screwin' you just know that she gon' tell another nigga when she through wit you."</item>
		<item>"I'm just filling up this daily planner, gettin' busy 'cause I'm a star, no spangled banner."</item>
		<item>"I'm a ma'fuckin' missed target. But a target nonetheless and I just started."</item>
		<item>"I just want to tell the truth Before one of the haters load up a couple shells and shoot"</item>
		<item>"I grow tired of these fuckin' grown man liars storytellers, they ain't even need a campfire."</item>
		<item>"They always tell me nobody's workin' as hard as you. And even though I laugh it off, man, it's probably true."</item>
		<item>"Rolexes, chauffeurs, and low fades. I keep thinking, how young can you die from old age?"</item>
		<item>"I been up for four days gettin' money both ways. Dirty and clean, I could use a glass of cold Spades."</item>
		<item>"Yes I make mistakes that I don't ever make excuses for, like leaving girls that love me and constantly seducing hoes."</item>
		<item>"What am I doing? Oh yeah, that's right, I'm doing me, I'm doing me. I'm living life right now, man, and this what I'mma do 'til it's over."</item>
		<item>"All the care that we take...all the love that we make..."</item>
		<item>"I'm urgin' all daughters to kiss they mothers, with those lips that all that lipstick covers. You're never too grown up to miss and hug her."</item>
		<item>"Wassup with these new niggas? And why they think it all comes so easy."</item>
		<item>"All I care about is money and city that I'm from, I'm a sip until I feel it I'm a smoke until it's done. I don't really give a fuck my excuse is that I'm young, and I'm only gettin older somebody should of told you I'm one."</item>
		<item>"The mother of your child always tell you I'm her favorite. She call me her baby, not the one she was in labor with."</item>
		<item>"Making all the same mistakes and I'm just trying to correct it and I fall."</item>
		<item>"It's been one of those days, you try and forget about. Take a shot and let it out."</item>
		<item>"Still ain't tryna die to get to heaven."</item>
		<item>"They tryna bring us down me, Weezy and Stunna We stayed up, Christmas lights in the middle of summer."</item>
		<item>"I feel like lately I went from top 5 to remaining 5. My favourite rappers either lost it or they aint alive."</item>
		<item>"Ohh, I never seen the car you claim to drive. Shit I seen it, you just aint inside."</item>
		<item>"Cant tell you how much I love when niggas think they got it and I love the fact that line made em think about it."</item>
		<item>"I aint lying, yeah and comfortable I sit. That manual Ferrari Italian, some fly shit . Its sittin at the house like I bought it in 9-6. Cause honestly Im too f-cking busy to drive stick."</item>
		<item>"We go on dates I send the Maybach out the neighbourhoods, they never seen it. That shit is dangerous but it so convenient."</item>
		<item>"Yeh, and lately I do bitches the meanest. Tell em I love em and dont ever mean it."</item>
		<item>"I want women to cry and pour out their heart for me and tell me how much they hate it when they apart from me."</item>
		<item>"I got car money, fresh start money. I want Saudi money, I want art money."</item>
		<item>"Ahh, this is perfect for the women that I love before. I love them all, I just love me more."</item>
		<item>"Okay...live my life in hotels. Bitch better have my room right. If they kill me, bury me a legend. Bitch better have my tomb right."</item>
		<item>"They watch us make that shit into a song. Ya aint livin that boy stop stealin that life. Anything could happen when I do see ya. Guess it all depends on how Im feelin that night."</item>
		<item>"Thats that fake shit, thats that fake shit. That that top row of veneers. Just when they getting impatient. When I make a World premiere."</item>
		<item>"Wassup, real nigga doing real stuff. Get a lot of money, you could never get enough and you know the new shit sounds so tough. So and so just walked on, so what?"</item>
		<item>"Dreams money can buy. They told me its like a high, it wasnt a lie."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, I throw my dollars up high and they land on the stage you dance on. We got company coming over. Would it kill you to put some pants on?"</item>
		<item>"If the girl standing next to me got a fat ass. Then Ill probably give her my number."</item>
		<item>"The game needed life, I put my heart in it."</item>
		<item>"Send the haters all my love, xoxo."</item>
		<item>"I am murdering it's so amusing, if their a site to see I am a illusion."</item>
		<item>"Even though I want it too this shit don't last forever, but better late than never."</item>
		<item>"That's why I never follow y'all suggestions, I just always did my own thing now I run the game, you stupid muddasuckassss"</item>
		<item>"I'm on one. Yeah, fuck it, I'm on one."</item>
		<item>"Im like a waiter and you something like a hater with trays in both hands, place an order I can cater."</item>
		<item>"F-ck you, p-ssy ass haters you should do you."</item>
		<item>"F-ck it me and Nicki Nick gettin married today. And all you b-tches that be hating can catch a bouquet."</item>
		<item>"Take photos with hater n-ggas and crop them. I am not them. I photoshop them out cause they dont understand what Im about."</item>
		<item>"My song is your girlfriends waking up ringer...or alarm or whatever."</item>
		<item>"These women living like they tryna write a book after. But I'm just trying to keep it G for my chapter."</item>
		<item>"Cups of the rozay, bitches in my old phone. I should call one and go home, I been in this club way too long."</item>
		<item>"I've had sex four times this week I'll explain, having a hard time adjusting to fame."</item>
		<item>"I need you right now are you down to listen to me. I got some women that's livin off me, pay for their flights and hotels I'm ashamed."</item>
		<item>"I don't think I'm conscious of makin monsters out of the women that I sponsor til it all goes bad."</item>
		<item>"I think I'm addicted to naked pictures and sittin talkin bout bitches that we almost had."</item>
		<item>"Fuck that nigga that you think you found, and since you pick up I know that he's not around."</item>
		<item>"I'm just sayin that you can better, tell me have you heard that lately."</item>
		<item>"Fuck that nigga that you love so bad, I know you still think about the times we had."</item>
		<item>"The woman that I would try, is happy with a good guy. But I've been drinking so much Imma call her anyway."</item>
		<item>"Empty home...pretty things...tryna write the songs that my city sings..."</item>
		<item>"I promise I've been thinking before yall, I barely get tired Im rarely inspired."</item>
		<item>"I love you as much as you love me...so if you hate me it works out perfectly."</item>
		<item>"What I tend to do is think of today as the past. It's funny when you're coming in first, but you hope that you're last, you just hope... that it lasts."</item>
		<item>"Always make it work but I live like I'm retired."</item>
		<item>"I don't trust these bitches, they might catch me slippin and put in something different."</item>
		<item>"I'm scared to put the time in, women wanna f-ck like they're me and I'm them."</item>
		<item>"You can look me in my eyes and see I ain't myself, cause if yall what I created then I hate myself."</item>
		<item>"I can tell certain people don't like me no more, new shit don't excite me no more, guess that they don't really make them like me no more."</item>
		<item>"I got new girls but none of their love is for certain, I call old girls but none their numbers are workin"</item>
		<item>"Women dont get saved around me, even on a Sunday."</item>
		<item>"Don't ever forget the moment you began to doubt. Transitioning from fitting into standing out."</item>
		<item>"Hate the rumours, hate the bullshit. Hate these fucking allegations, I'm just feeling like the throne is for the taking. Watch me take it!"</item>
		<item>"I can tell her things and treat her right, you can get whatever baby remember you're with me tonight."</item>
		<item>"Young women are lost these days but older women dig me."</item>
		<item>"I don't judge her but I could never love her cause to her I'm just a rapper and soon she'll have met another."</item>
		<item>"You niggas make it so hard to be friendly when I know part of it's envy."</item>
		<item>"I might be too strung out on compliments, overdosed on confidence. Started not to give a fuck and stop fearing the consequence."</item>
		<item>"I be yelling out money over everything, money on my mind."</item>
		<item>"That the real is on the rise, fuck them other guys."</item>
		<item>"Drizzy got the money, so Drizzy gonna pay it. Those my brothers, I ain't even gotta say it."</item>
		<item>"I know I exaggerated things, now I got it like that. Stuff my napkin in my shirt cause I'm just mobbin like that."</item>
		<item>"I had someone tell me I fell off, ooh I needed that.And they want to see me pick back up, well where'd I leave it at?"</item>
		<item>"They sayin' I'm back, I agree with that. I just take my time with all this shit, I still believe in that."</item>
		<item>"The real is on the rise."</item>
		<item>"I got a black box where suggestions go, but I don't really give a fuck it's probably best you know."</item>
		<item>"Drinking every night because we drink to my accomplishments. Faded way too long, I'm floatin' in and out of consciousness."</item>
		<item>"I had someone tell me I fell off, ooh I needed that and they want to see me pick back up, well where'd I leave it at?"</item>
		<item>"They sayin' I'm back, I agree with that. I just take my time with all this shit, I still believe in that."</item>
		<item>"I had someone tell me I fell off, ooh I needed that and they want to see me pick back up, well where'd I leave it at?"</item>
		<item>"Soap opera rappers, all these niggas sound like "All My Children."</item>
		<item>"I be yelling out money over everything, money on my mind. Then she wanna ask when it got so empty. Tell her I apologize, happened over time. She says they miss the old Drake, girl don't tempt me."</item>
		<item>"I'm looking for somebody who's gonna be somebody."</item>
		<item>"Maybe she won't...but shit then again maybe she will."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
