<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
<item>"R. Kelly was very close to his mother."</item>
<item>"In 2003, R.Kelly became one of the rare artists to have two different albums hitting the #1 spot on the Billboard Charts within the same year. He produced on of the album (Body Kiss by The Isley Brothers) and the other one was his own (The Chocolate Factory)."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly is facing 14 counts of child pornography. He was indicted in 2002 after a videotape surfaced that allegedly showed him having sex with a 13-year-old girl. He denies the claim and was due to attend a court date when he was taken to hospital for an emergency appendectomy."</item>
<item>"In early February 2007, R. Kelly underwent an emergency appendectomy. His appendix burst after he performed at a Super Bowl party and he was rushed to Jackson Memorial Hospital in Miami for the operation."</item>
<item>"He is signed to Jive Records/Zomba Label Group."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly wrote Michael Jackson's hit \"You Are Not Alone\"."</item>
<item>"His trademark is he frequently wears a \"Zorro\" mask."</item>
<item>"His album \"Chocolate Factory\" sold over 500,000 copies in its first week of release. It has so far sold in excess of 2,000,000 in the USA alone."</item>
<item>"His trademark is French braids."</item>
<item>"He wrote Toni Braxton's hit ""I don't want to""."</item>
<item>"Lena McLin inspired Kelly to become a singer. She was his high school music teacher."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly was lampooned by the animated adult series The Boondocks. The entire episode, entitled \"Trial for R. Kelly\", was a parody of Kelly's alleged crimes."</item>
<item>"Kelly often works with the legendary R'n'B group The Isley Brothers featuring Ronald Isley. They did numerous hits together such as ""Down Low (Nobody Has to Know)"" and ""Contagious""."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly collaborated with numerous artist such as Celine Dion, Jay-Z, Ja Rule, The Game, Aaliyah, Nas, Diddy and Snoop Dogg."</item>
<item>"In 2005, MADtv produced a music video called ""Trapped in the Cupboard"" which was a parody of Kelly's urban opera ""Trapped in the Closet""."</item>
<item>"In 2003, Dave Chappelle made a music video called ""Piss On You"" which was a parody of Kelly's sex scandal. Chappelle's video contains samples of Kelly's \"Ignition (Remix)\"."</item>
<item>"He is 6'1\" (1.85 m) tall."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly has had the most Top 10 singles in America during the 1990s, making him the most successful R&amp;B male artist of the decade. He has sold more than 31 million copies in the US alone and over 50 million copies worldwide."</item>
<item>"In 1998, \"I Believe I Can Fly\" made him won 3 Grammy Awards. One for Best R&amp;B Song, one for Best R&amp;B Male Vocal Performance and the last one for Best Original Song from A Soundtrack. The single was a massive hit and Kelly's most famous song to this day."</item>
<item>"Kelly's \"I Believe I Can Fly\" was ranked among Rolling Stone Magazine's Top 500 Songs Of All Time."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly began his music career as the founder and lead singer of r&amp;b singing group Public Announcement."</item>
<item>"Kelly married Andrea Lee in 1996 and they had three children together, a son named Robert Jr., and two daughters Jaya and Joann. The couple filled for divorce in 2005."</item>
<item>"Being a songwriter, a producer and a singer, Kelly mostly writes, arranges, and produces all of his own songs."</item>
<item>"Kelly used to attend Kenwood Academy High School in Chicago, Illinois."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly shares his birthday with Sean Paul, David Bowie, and Chris Masters."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly married R&amp;B Singer Aaliyah on August 30, 1994. The marriage was canceled due to Aaliyah's status as a minor. She only was 15 years old while he was in his mid 20s."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly joined the long list of celebrities lampooned by South Park. It happened in South Park episode 137 entitled \"Trapped in the Closet\"."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly: (on his counts of child pornography) All of a sudden you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one that knows what I'm going through."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly: I'm the Ali of today. I'm the Marvin Gaye of today. I'm the Bob Marley of today. I'm the Martin Luther King, or all the other greats that have come before us. And a lot of people are starting to realise that now."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly: I want America to know that you can't believe everything you hear, and nowadays, you can't believe everything you see."</item>
<item>"His full name is Robert Sylvester Kelly."</item>
<item>"He was born January 8, 1967 in Chicago, Illinois."</item>
<item>"Kelly's single mother, Joanne, was a singer and a Baptist."</item>
<item>"Kelly's father was absent throughout most of his life."</item>
<item>"In Chicago, Kelly's family lived on 63rd Street before relocating to a small house at 107th and Parnell Streets."</item>
<item>"Kelly began singing in the church at the age of eight."</item>
<item>"As a teenager, he began street performing under the Chicago 'L' trains before he eventually formed a group with his friend Marc McWilliams called MGM (Musically Gifted Men)."</item>
<item>"Along with Vincent Corey Walker and Shawnth Brooks, MGM performed on the TV talent show Big Break, hosted by Natalie Cole, and went on to win the $100,000 grand prize. Soon after, R. Kelly and MGM released their first single, \"Why You Wanna Play Me,\" on Tavdash Records."</item>
<item>"Kelly signed to Jive Records in 1991, and Kelly formed another R&amp;B group with friends called Public Announcement."</item>
<item>"In 1997, Kelly fulfilled a longtime dream of his and signed a contract to play professional basketball with the Atlantic City Seagulls of the USBL."</item>
<item>"Kelly is believed to be the first music artist to play professional basketball."</item>
<item>"Kelly's debut solo album, 12 Play, was released in the fall of 1993 and yielded the singer's first number-one hit, \"Bump n' Grind\", which spent a record-breaking 12 weeks at number one on the Hot R&amp;B Singles chart."</item>
<item>"R. Kelly is the self-titled second studio album by R&amp;B singer R. Kelly. It was released on November 14, 1995."</item>
<item>"R. is the third studio album and his first double album. It was released in the United States on November 10, 1998."</item>
<item>"His 4th album was released in 2000. called TP-2.com as the \"sequel\" to 12 Play."</item>
<item>"Chocolate Factory is his fifth studio album, released February 18, 2003 on Jive Records."</item>
<item>"Happy People/U Saved Me is his sixth studio album and the second double album, where he mixed feel-good danceable soul records (Happy People) with gospel anthems (U Saved Me). It was released in 2004."</item>
<item>"TP.3 Reloaded is his seventh studio album. The album is the third entry in the 12 Play series."</item>
<item>"Double Up is his eighth studio album, released on May 29, 2007."</item>
<item>"Untitled is his ninth studio album, released November 30, 2009 in the United Kingdom and December 1, 2009 in the United States, through Jive Records and Sony Music."</item>
<item>"Love Letter is his tenth studio album, released December 14, 2010 on Jive Records. It was written and produced entirely by Kelly."</item>

</string-array>
</resources>
