<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Bone Thugs N Harmony and Wu Tang were a couple of musical inspirations for him as a teen."</item>
		<item>"Wiz’s real name is Cameron Jibril Thomaz."</item>
		<item>"Wiz Khalifa was born in North Dakota."</item>
		<item>"He was called ‘the wiz’ as a nickname growing up because he was such a ‘wiz’ at everything he attempted."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa is an Arabic name which signifies leadership."</item>
		<item>"He was just eight years old when he decided he wanted to become a rapper."</item>
		<item>"Music isn’t the only thing the breakthrough MC is not just working to build upon. He also is working on covering his whole body in tattoos."</item>
		<item>"He came in first in a poll on MTVNews.com as the “hottest breakthrough MC of 2010″ beating out other newcomers such as Nicki Minaj."</item>
		<item>"He likes to drink Bombay Sapphire gin."</item>
		<item>"He turned down a chance to open up for Drake on tour before he was signed by a record label!"</item>
		<item>"Declared as Rolling Stone's 'Artist to Watch' in 2006."</item>
		<item>"Named MTV's Hottest Breakthrough MC of 2010. "</item>
		<item>"He was born on September 8, 1987. in Minot, North Dakota, United States."</item>
		<item>"He released his debut album, Show and Prove, in 2006, and signed to Warner Bros. Records in 2007."</item>
		<item>"His eurodance-influenced single, \"Say Yeah\", received urban radio airplay, charting on the Rhythmic Top 40 and Hot Rap Tracks charts in 2008."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa parted with Warner Bros. and released his second album, Deal or No Deal, in November 2009."</item>
		<item>"He released the mixtape Kush and Orange Juice as a free download in April 2010; he then signed with Atlantic Records."</item>
		<item>"He is also well-known for his debut single for Atlantic, "Black and Yellow", which peaked at number 1 on the Billboard Hot 100."</item>
		<item>"His debut album for the label, Rolling Papers, was released on March 29, 2011."</item>
		<item>"His parents divorced when Khalifa was about three years old."</item>
		<item>"His parents' military service caused him to move on a regular basis. Khalifa lived in Germany, England, and Japan before settling in Pittsburgh where he attended Taylor Allderdice High School."</item>
		<item>"His stage name is derived from khalifa, an Arabic word meaning \"successor\", and wisdom, which was shortened to Wiz when Khalifa was fifteen."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa stated that the name also came from being called \"young Wiz 'cause I was good at everything I did, and my granddad is Muslim, so he gave me that name; he felt like that's what I was doing with my music\"."</item>
		<item>"He got his stage name tattooed on his 17th birthday."</item>
		<item>"He includes Camp Lo, The Notorious B.I.G. and Bone Thugs-n-Harmony among his influences."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa released his first mixtape, Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania, in 2005."</item>
		<item>"Thomaz is dating Amber Rose, the former girlfriend of Thomaz's fellow hip-hop star Kanye West."</item>
		<item>"He is also personal friends with rapper Yelawolf, and fellow Pittsburgh rapper, Mac Miller."</item>
		<item>"In October of 1990, Wiz was separated from his mother, who left him in the hands of her sister while she served in Operation Desert Storm."</item>
		<item>"During his travels, Wiz was forced to mature quicker than his peers. He was constantly faced with new surroundings, schools, and friends, making it difficult to become attached to anyone outside family."</item>
		<item>"Nomadic life, though, gave Wiz an opportunity to broaden his mind and offered many experiences from which to draw inspiration."</item>
		<item>"Wiz Khalifa was arrested on various marijuana charges after performing at one of his shows on his Waken Baken Tour. Wiz was allegedly found with over 2 ounces of marijuana."</item>
		<item>"Wiz Khalifa's song Black and Yellow, a known Steelers Anthem, which was also made into a Lakers Anthem Purp and Yellow, went viral a few weeks ago, with over 24 million views on Youtube."</item>
		<item>"He has been hailed by the award winning Pittsburgh Post-Gazette pop music critic, Ed Masley, as having \"the skills, the looks, the confidence, the drive, and the charisma for the job\"."</item>
		<item>"In September his first single the label, the Pittsburgh Steelers tribute “Black and Yellow,” appeared. As the NFL team progressed toward the playoffs, Khalifa’s track became their unofficial anthem."</item>
		<item>"Wiz Khalifa height is 6’4”(195cm)"</item>
		<item>"His sign is Virgo"</item>
		<item>"Wiz Khalifa weight is 84 kg – 184 lb"</item>
		<item>"His debut Warner Bros. single "Say Yeah" reached number 25 on the Billboard Rhythmic Top 40 music chart and number 20 on Billboard's Hot Rap Tracks."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa appeared at the Soundset 2010 festival in May 2010 in Minneapolis, Minnesota, alongside Method Man and Redman, Del the Funky Homosapien and Hieroglyphics, Atmosphere, Murs, Cage, and others."</item>
		<item>"He also performed at the 2010 Rock the Bells festival, along with hip hop veterans Wu-Tang Clan, Snoop Dogg, Lauryn Hill, A Tribe Called Quest, Rakim, KRS-One, Jedi Mind Tricks and Slick Rick."</item>
		<item>"Khalifa's fanbase is known as the Taylor Gang, named after his love of Chuck Taylor All-Stars shoes."</item>
		<item>"Rolling Papers album debuted at number two on the US Billboard 200 chart, with first-week sales of 197,000 copies in the United States."</item>
		<item>"On June 26, 2011, Khalifa was nominated and won Best New Artist at the BET Awards of 2011."</item>
		<item>"Studio albums: Show and Prove (2006), Deal or No Deal (2009), Rolling Papers (2011)"</item>
		<item>"Mixtapes: Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania (2005), Grow Season (2007), Prince of the City 2 (2007), Star Power (2008), Flight School (2009), How Fly (2009), Burn After Rolling (2009), Kush and Orange Juice (2010), Cabin Fever (2011)"</item>
		<item>"Singles: \"Black and Yellow\", \"Roll Up\", \"On My Level\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Gang is Wiz Khalifa's clique/crew that he runs with."</item>
		<item>"Now-a-days, Taylor Gang is more then just a crew. Its a lifestyle, aka Taylor Gang Life$tyle. If you're a fan of Wiz Khalifa.. then you're Taylor Gang!"</item>
		<item>"He has two brothers, Jude and Terrell and one sister Vaness."</item>
		<item>"Wiz favorite colors are black and yellow."</item>
		<item>"His first tattoo was \"Wiz Khalifa\" on his upper left arm."</item>
		<item>"He has more than 17 tattoos."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
