<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Michael Jackson's favourite animated character was Pinocchio "</item>
		<item>"When he was a child his favourite books included Rip Van Winkle and The Old Man and the Sea."</item>
		<item>"Michael Jackson was very ticklish."</item>
		<item>"Saint Vincent, an island in the Caribbean, once issued Michael Jackson stamps."</item>
		<item>"The singer once owned a boa constrictor called \"Muscles\"." </item>
		<item>"As a youngster he used to put spiders in sister La Toyah’s bed."</item>
		<item>"He played a scarecrow in The Wiz, a movie version of the Wizard of Oz."</item>
		<item>"He has two stars on the Hollywood Walk of Fame (one for himself and one as part of the Jackson Five)"”</item>
		<item>"Quincy Jones nicknamed him \"smelly\" – a slang term similar to \"funky\"."</item>
		<item>"Jackson described his own voice on early Jackson 5 records as \"like Minnie Mouse\"."</item>
		<item>"He was a big fan of The Three Stooges."</item>
		<item>"He is an Exeter City fan "</item>
		<item>"He had two llamas called Louis and Lola"</item>
		<item>"Thriller spent 37 weeks at number one in the US Billboard chart."</item>
		<item>"In 1984 he won eight Grammy’s – the joint highest amount ever won by one person in a single year."</item>
		<item>"He gave his first public performance at the age of 5 singing Climb Every Mountain."</item>
		<item>"He had eight brothers and sisters."</item>
		<item>"His marriage to Lisa-Marie Presley lasted only 19 months."</item>
		<item>"Jackson paid $47 million for the publishing rights to the Beatles back catalogue in 1985 and sold a share of to Sony in 1995 for $95 million."</item>
		<item>"His middle name was Joseph."</item>
		<item>"He was born on Aug 29, 1958."</item>
		<item>"At the Brit Awards in 1996 Pulp frontman Jarvis Cocker took exception to his bombastic performance of Earth Song and ran on to the stage."</item>
		<item>"Jackson was very fond of Mexican food."</item>
		<item>"In 1993 Jackson’s dermatologist said he had a rare skin disease called vitiligo, which causes sufferers to lose pigmentation in their skin."</item>
		<item>"Thriller is the world’s best-selling record of all time with an estimated 50 million copies sold worldwide."</item>
		<item>"Two of his other albums – Bad and Dangerous – are also among the world’s best-selling records."</item>
		<item>"He popularised dance moves including the robot and the moonwalk."</item>
		<item>"He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame twice."</item>
		<item>"He won 13 Grammy Awards."</item>
		<item>"Billie Jean was the first video by a black artist to air on MTV."</item>
		<item>"Jackson owns the rights to the South Carolina State Anthem, South Carolina on My Mind."</item>
		<item>"He has waxworks in five Madame Tussauds museums across the world. Only Elvis Presley and Madonna have more."</item>
		<item>"He has sold more than 300 million records worldwide."</item>
		<item>"His favourite superhero is Morph from X-Men."</item>
		<item>"He had a pet ram called Mr Tibbs."</item>
		<item>"His total lifetime earnings from music are estimated at $500 million"</item>
		<item>"Jackson regularly wore a black armband to remind people of children suffering around the world."</item>
		<item>"The moonwalk was picked up from street dancers."</item>
		<item>"Little Richard wanted to be played by Jackson in a biopic."</item>
		<item>"Jackson had a pet python called Crusher."</item>
		<item>"In 1984 a French fan committed suicide because he couldn’t have surgery to look like Jackson."</item>
		<item>"The video for Scream was the most expensive ever at £3.8 million."</item>
		<item>"A library once accused the singer of owing $1 million in overdue book fines."</item>
		<item>"Jackson was a vegetarian."</item>
		<item>"He won an MTV award for Best Movie Song in 1994. It was for Will You Be There from the movie Free Willy."</item>
		<item>"HIStory was the biggest selling double album ever released in the United States."</item>
		<item>"Jackson was given a royal title in the Ivory Coast in 1992."</item>
		<item>"Before concerts he would drink Ricola candy dissolved in hot water."</item>
		<item>"His birthplace Gary, Indiana, is planning a museum in his honour."</item>
		<item>"The singer patented a shoe device that allowed dancers to lean forward at gravity defying angles."</item>
		<item>"He was a best man at Liza Minnelli’s wedding to David Gest."</item>
		<item>"The largest television audience in US history watched him perform at half time during the 1993 Super Bowl."</item>
		<item>"Martin Scorcese once directed a Jackson video."</item>
		<item>"A survey in 1997 declared him the Most Famous Person in the World."</item>
		<item>"He paid $1.5 million in 1999 to buy for the 1939 Oscar for best film won by Gone With The Wind."</item>	
		<item>"Jackson once described Elizabeth Taylor as \"a warm cuddly blanket that I love to snuggle up to"."</item>
		<item>"He recorded a voice-over on The Simpsons."</item>
		<item>"Macauley Culkin is godfather to two of Jackson’s children."</item>
		<item>"Jackson co-wrote We Are The World with Lionel Richie."</item>	
		<item>"He is godfather to Nicole Richie."</item>
		<item>"He is also godfather to Bee Gees singer Barry Gibb’s son Michael."</item>
		<item>"Jackson shares a birthday with Sir Richard Attenborough and actress Rebecca DeMornay."</item>
		<item>"At the time of his death Jackson was rehearsing for his greatest comeback, with 50 shows scheduled in London."</item>
		<item>"He was four years old when he began singing with his brothers Marlon, Jermaine, Jackie and Tito in the Jackson 5."</item>
		<item>"The Jackson 5’s number one hits included “I Want You Back,” “ABC” and \"I’ll Be There\"."</item>
		<item>"In 2002 Jackson caused controversy when he playfully dangled his infant son, Prince Michael II, over a hotel balcony in Berlin in front of fans."</item>
		<item>"MC Hammer once challenged Jackson to a dance off."</item>
		<item>"In a TV documentary he acknowledged sharing his bed with children but described the practice as sweet, and not sexual."</item>
		<item>"During production of a 1984 Pepsi advertisement Jackson sustained burns when an explosion set his hair on fire."</item>
		<item>"Jackson’s 13 number one hits on the US Billboard charts put him behind only Elvis Presley, the Beatles and Mariah Carey."</item>
		<item>"Jackson’s father Joseph worked in a steel mill."</item>
		<item>"Joseph Jackson and his brother Luther were in an RnB band called The Falcons."</item>
		<item>"Michael was raised as a Jehovah’s Witness by his mother."</item>
		<item>"In a 1993 interview with Oprah Winfrey the singer spoke of a traumatic childhood including suffering from loneliness."</item>
		<item>"Jackson showed his singing talent at the age of five when he performed at a Christmas recital."</item>
		<item>"The family band was originally called the Jackson Brothers."</item>
		<item>"Michael was promoted to joint lead vocals at the age of eight and the band became the Jackson 5."</item>
		<item>"They toured extensively in the US Midwest from 1966 to 1968."</item>
		<item>"He initially used his eccentricities to promote his music but strongly disliked the “Wacko Jacko” nickname."</item>
		<item>"Wild stories about him included that he slept in an oxygen chamber and that he bought the bones of The Elephant Man."</item>
		<item>"During the world tour for Bad he performed to 4.4 million people."</item>
		<item>"His first autobiography, Moon Walk, took four years to complete."</item>
		<item>"The book reached the top of The New York Times best sellers’ list."</item>
		<item>"Jackson admitted to having had two nose jobs."</item>
		<item>"He suggested weight loss and a strict vegetarian diet had contributed to the change in his appearance."</item>
		<item>"He paid $17 million in 1988 for the land in California that became the Neverland Ranch."</item>
		<item>"The 2,700-acre property had a theme park, a menagerie, and a movie theatre."</item>
		<item>"Its grounds were protected by a security staff of 40."</item>
		<item>"Neverland was valued at $100 million in 2003."</item>
		<item>"The profits from his single “Man in the Mirror” went to charity."</item>
		<item>"In 1991 he signed a contract with Sony worth $65 million."</item>
		<item>"In 1992 he founded the Heal the World Foundation which brought underprivileged children to Neverland and made donations worldwide."</item>
		<item>"When he visited the African country of Gabon 100,000 people turned out to see him."</item>
		<item>"Jackson’s most famous pet was Bubbles the chimpanzee."</item>
		<item>"Bubbles was adopted at the age of three from a cancer research clinic in Texas."</item>
		<item>"Bubbles sat in on recording sessions for the Bad album and accompanied Jackson to Tokyo."</item>
		<item>"The artist Jeff Koons made a series of sculptures of Jackson and Bubbles"</item>
		<item>"Jackson fathered two children with Deborah Jeanne Rowe – Michael Joseph Jackson Junior (also known as \"Prince\") and a daughter, Paris Michael Katherine Jackson."</item>
		<item>"The couple divorced in 1999 and Rowe gave full custody rights to Jackson."</item>
		<item>"Vitiligo, the skin disease from which he suffered, affects 1 to 2 per cent to 2 per cent of the population."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
