<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I love you like a fat kid loves cake."</item>
		<item>"Hate it or love it, the underdogs come out on top."</item>
		<item>"You shouldn't throw stones if you live in a glass house and if you got a glass jaw, you should watch yo mouth: cause I'll break yo face."</item>
		<item>"Im a trackstar running thru life, chasing my dream."</item>
		<item>"Everyone else is just mad 'cause I came from the bottom wthout them."</item>
		<item>"Don't much good come from me, but my music. Is a gift given from God so I'm gonna use it."</item>
		<item>"I'm the type to swallow my blood 'fore I swallow my pride."</item>
		<item>"Rappers are like fighters. They condition themselves to be the best."</item>
		<item>"I, when I was just a kid, savored my skittles to ensure the luscious flavor."</item>
		<item>"I had sex for the first time when I was 12-years-old with a grown-ass woman. Like, 22. She wasn't really attractive. I was a big 12-year-old though. I had no idea what I was doing, but I was ready! "</item>
		<item>"A lot of kids join the Army to get a college education. That's why they do it, and they get sent into these horrible situations."</item>
		<item>"A man becomes as attractive as an attractive woman when he becomes successful and is publicly noted. Power's an aphrodisiac."</item>
		<item>"I think it's easier for the general public to embrace me in a negative way. You have people who already have a perception of me that says I'm a bad person."</item>
		<item>"If they keep comin' at me, I'll just keep responding back until they don't exist anymore. I got the time and energy to ruin what is left of their careers, if they want to do that."</item>
		<item>"I don't display emotions. I have every feeling that everyone else has but I've developed ways to suppress them. Anger is one of my most comfortable feelings."</item>
		<item>"In my neighborhood if you're too aggressive, you intimidate someone, they kill you. Or if you decide to be emotional and you start crying, you're a victim."</item>
		<item>"You know, the kid in the schoolyard that doesn't want to fight always leaves with a black eye."</item>
		<item>"You have to find a way to stay in the middle, somewhere where people just don't mess with you because they know that you don't have a problem with it if it goes there."</item>
		<item>"In Hollywood they say there's no business like show business in the hood they say there's no business like ho business."</item>
		<item>"You shouldn't throw stones if you live in a glass house and if you got a glass jaw, you should watch yo mouth: cause I'll break yo face."</item>
		<item>"I'm the type to swallow my blood 'fore I swallow my pride."</item>
		<item>"Everyone else is just mad 'cause I came from the bottom wthout them."</item>
		<item>"I'm a trackstar running thru life, chasing my dream."</item>
		<item>"The only thing that I'm scared of is not livin' up to the expectations of Dr. Dre and Eminem."</item>
		<item>"Don't much good come from me, but my music is a gift given from God so I'm gonna use it."</item>
		<item>"Eminem is so talented it becomes annoying. Everytime we go to the studio, he's got something new to play and it's like \"Oh man, I gotta have something new to play, too\"."</item>
		<item>"I don't get worked up or excited about situations I can't control because it's not in my power, so I might appear crazy to some people."</item>
		<item>"To me, rappers are liars until I see that their actions coincide with what they said through the music. Me, I put my situations down and I make fun of them."</item>
		<item>"I'm not in control of these situations and I feel like to be upset or down about something I can't control is just being weak and wasting energy."</item>
		<item>"When I have conversations with people, for some strange reason they think I'm gonna die and they're not. But you know what? Death means nothing to me."</item>
		<item>"Your first reaction is to move and then the shots is going off and you jumping around the backseat. I was scared the whole time. You supposed to die in that situation. They're not playing."</item>
		<item>"I'm not in control of these situations and I feel like to be upset or down about something I can't control is just being weak and wasting energy."</item>
		<item>"To me, rappers are liars until I see that their actions coincide with what they said through the music. Me, I put my situations down and I make fun of them."</item>
		<item>"I don't get worked up or excited about situations I can't control because it's not in my power, so I might appear crazy to some people."</item>
		<item>"Eminem is the rapper's rapper. He listens to everything. Every word, every slang, if you change something he's going to hear it all. "</item>
		<item>"I was thinking of releasing the next album in November, but I'm gonna wait."</item>
		<item>"Growing up, I was confused, my momma kissing a girl Confusion occurs, growing up in a cold world. "</item>
		<item>"This is God's plan, homey, not mine... I am what I am. You can like it or love it."</item>
		<item>"If you die in an elevator make sure you press the UP button."</item>
		<item>"Show No Love , Cus Love Can Get U killed."</item>
		<item>"What comes around goes around."</item>
		<item>"Get rich are die trying."</item>
		<item>"You shouldn't throw stones if you live in a glass house and if you got a glass jaw, you should watch yo mouth: cause I'll break yo face."</item>
		<item>"Its not about the dog in the fight, its about the fight in the dog!"</item>
		<item>"I've made so many mistakes, so many corrections. I'm so far from perfect so many imperfections. But I'm a go getta I get up and go get it, so if you preaching prosperity, i wanna hit it..."</item>
		<item>"I spit sh*t, slick sh*t, so quick you miss it."</item>
		<item>"All bulls**t aside, now it’s time to be honest. I fear no man, for death is all that’s promised."</item>
		<item>"Here’s a jewel: Love your enemies and hate your friends. Your enemies remain the same — friends always change."</item>
		<item>"Hate a liar more than I hate thief. A thief is only after my salary a liar is after my reality."</item>
		<item>"I don’t think it makes me a role model. I think it makes me inspiring. Cause I’m from the bottom I think they look at me and go \"well, if he made it, I can make it\"."</item>
		<item>"I’m not sensitive, I give people things exactly the way they are, and if they’re ready to absorb it, they will, and if they aren’t, they won’t."</item>
		<item>"Love at first sight saves a lot of time."</item>
		<item>"Lil bow wow the size of a mini teck, we ridin around with guns the size of 50 cent."</item>
		<item>"Sunny days wouldnt be so special, if it wasnt for rain and joy wouldnt feel so good, if it wasnt for pain."</item>
		<item>"If niggas so hot, why they aint got what i go.t My Maybach, my watch, my Hublo."</item>
		<item>"I now know I'm here for a real reason. Cuz he got hit like I got hit and he ain't fuckin' breathin'"</item>
		<item>"My fat knots, my swag is top notch. My crack spots bring in cash in non stop."</item>
		<item>"Got shit locked, i stunt non stop I get it and i blow it how i want , why not?"</item>
		<item>"9 millimeter, 9 shots, big rock 9 carat stones, im in my own zone."</item>
		<item>"Outlaw yea yea we lawless. We ballin out yea regardless. VVS yea yea we flawless."</item>
		<item>"You wanna get shot, go ahead run up on my spot. My lawyers will have me out by 1 oclock."</item>
		<item>"My gun pop, tell me why would you try that. Porsche turbo, cayenne , ill buy that."</item>
		<item>"G5 jet , pilot, i fly that. Burn good shit, get as high as i get."</item>
		<item>"Groupie love bitch, your left breast ill sign that. Im CEO , Hoe you aint know?"</item>
		<item>"New york party of the year, my spot. These bitches look so good, oh my god."</item>
		<item>"Looking at the man in the mirror im so hot.Shorty wanna cut, cool make sure the door lock."</item>
		<item>"Like pornstar took ya to my spot. My bed rock back and forth when im on top."</item>
		<item>"My backshots they are sorta like crack rocks. I give it all i got, nonstop till sweat drop."</item>
		<item>"I damage i wreck shop, i come thru correct i , I give her what she need, till its hard to breathe."</item>
		<item>"When you come from where Im from, you come from the bottom, you aint supposed to get this rich!"</item>
		<item>"What cha saying boy, you think Im playing boy, watch ya mouth girl, its a mans world."</item>
		<item>"Listen, n-gga you play me, and Im gon go crazy, you push me Imma muthaf-cking trip."</item>
		<item>"N-gga from JFK to Lax, im back through the sets again, gangsta life thats right, crazy ass mexicans."</item>
		<item>"Next thing you know, they up in your crib, saying where is the stash at, you move they gon blast that."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
