<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Beautiful girls all over the world, I could be chasing. But my time would be wasted, they got nothing on you, baby. Nothing on you, baby."</item>
		<item>"If perfect is what you're searching for then just stay the same."</item>
		<item>"Her eyes, her eyes Make the stars look like they're not shining Her hair, her hair Falls perfectly without her trying."</item>
		<item>"They say lifes a dream, call this in insomnia cuz this ain't wonderland damn sure ain't narnia and once you cross the line you can't change your mind and yeah I'm a monster but I'm no Frankenstein."</item>
		<item>"I was perfect for the circus. If she dared me, I'd do it. love makes you stupid."</item>
		<item>"Or am I a fool who sits alone talking to the moon? She set the bar just above the stars."</item>
		<item>"So whatchya wanna do let's just run girl, if we wake up and you wanna break up thats cool no I won't blame you, it was fun girl."</item>
		<item>"It's a beautiful night were looking for something dumb to do hey baby I think I wanna marry you."</item>
		<item>"So many eager young bunnies that id love to pursue. Now even though they eaten out the palm eaten out the palm of my hand, there's only one carrot and they all gotta share it."</item>
		<item>"Run run runaway baby before I put my spell on you."</item>
		<item>"Gave ya all I had and ya tossed it in the trash tossed it in the trash."</item>
		<item>"I would go through all the pain take a bullet straight through my brain, yes I would die for ya baby but you won't do the same."</item>
		<item>"Easy come easy go that's just how you live oh take take take it all but you never give shoulda known you was trouble from the first kiss."</item>
		<item>"Little miss perfect sitting at the train stop red Nike high tops listening to hip hop."</item>
		<item>"When everything in life gets so complicated it only takes a day to change it."</item>
		<item>"So easy to forget our love the little things we do like calling for no reason just to say the words I love you."</item>
		<item>"The truth of the matter is I'm complicated, your as straight as they come you go about your day baby while I hide from the sun."</item>
		<item>"I'll be lounging on the couch just chillen in my snuggie click to MTV so they can teach me how to dougie cuz I'm my castle I'm the fricken man."</item>
		<item>"You're Amazing, Just The Way You Are."</item>
		<item>"I could be chasin but my time would be wasted."</item>
		<item>"Beautiful girls, all over the world."</item>
		<item>"For when I'm a billionaire."</item>
		<item>"Oh I swear the world better prepare..."</item>
		<item>"A different city every night."</item>
		<item>"Oh every time I close my eyes."</item>
		<item>"Smiling next to Oprah and the Queen."</item>
		<item>"Uh, I wanna be on the cover of Forbes magazine."</item>
		<item>"Buy all of the things I never had."</item>
		<item>"I wanna be a billionaire so fucking bad."</item>
		<item>"You know I'd do anything for you."</item>
		<item>"I'd jump in front of a train for you."</item>
		<item>"Throw my hand on a blade for you."</item>
		<item>"I'd catch a grenade for you."</item>
		<item>"Is all I ever asked cause what you don't understand is..."</item>
		<item>"You tossed it in the trash, you did to give me all your love."</item>
		<item>"Gave you all I had and you tossed it in the trash."</item>
		<item>"But you shouldn't worry, about what they say."</item>
		<item>"They might say hi, and I might say hey."</item>
		<item>"They got nothin on YOOOOOOOOOU, baby."</item>
		<item>"Shes so beautiful and I tell her every day."</item>
		<item>"Her laugh, her laugh She hates but I think its so sexy."</item>
		<item>"Her lips, her lips I could kiss them all day if shed let me."</item>
		<item>"If perfect is what youre searching for then just stay the same."</item>
		<item>"Oh you know, you know, you know Id never ask you to change."</item>
		<item>"When you smile, the whole world stops and stares for a while."</item>
		<item>"'Cause you're amazing. Just the way you are."</item>
		<item>"When I see your face, there's not a thing that I would change."</item>
		<item>"Yes, I would die for you, baby but you won't do the same."</item>
		<item>"I would go through all this pain. Take a bullet straight through my brain."</item>
		<item>"Should've known you was trouble from the first kiss. Had your eyes wide open, why were they open?"</item>
		<item>"I missed the first train, stood out in the rain, all day. But little did I know, when I caught the next train. There you were to sweep me away."</item>
		<item>"Lift my arms out wide I open my eyes and now all I wanna see. Is a sky full of lighters. A sky full of lighters."</item>
		<item>"This ones for you and me, living out our dreams. Were all right where we should be."</item>
		<item>"I'll just strut in my birthday suit and let everything hang loose."</item>
		<item>"I might mess around, get my college degree. I bet my old man will be so proud of me but sorry pops, you'll just have to wait."</item>
		<item>"Tomorrow I'll wake up, do some P90X. Meet a really nice girl, have some really nice sex and she's gonna scream out: 'This is Great'"</item>
		<item>"I'll be lounging on the couch, Just chillin' in my snuggie. Click to MTV, so they can teach me how to dougie. 'Cause in my castle I'm the freaking man..."</item>
		<item>"I'm gonna kick my feet up. Then stare at the fan. Turn the TV on, throw my hand in my pants. Nobody's gonna tell me I can't..."</item>
		<item>"Don't feel like picking up my phone. So leave a message at the tone. 'Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything."</item>
		<item>"Today I don't feel like doing anything. I just wanna lay in my bed."</item>
		<item>"You and I know what its like to be kicked down. Forced to fight but tonight were alright. So hold up your light. Let it shine..."</item>
		<item>"My fragile heart's been done so wrong. I wondered if I'd ever heal again."</item>
		<item>"Take my hand, close your eyes With you right here, I'm a rocketeer! Let's fly..."</item>
		<item>"Here we go, come with me. There's a world out there that we should see."</item>
		<item>"Cause '68 Citrus ain't gonna pay the rent, so I'll be out here til they call the cops."</item>
		<item>"Me and my guitar tonight, singing to the city lights, tryna live on more than what I got."</item>
		<item>"One shot for my pain, one drag for my sorrow. Get messed up today, I'll be ok tomorrow."</item>
		<item>"I'll take one shot for my pain, one drag for my sorrow. Get messed up today, I'll be ok tomorrow."</item>
		<item>"Because my job got me going nowhere, so I ain't got a thing to lose. Take me to a place where I don't care, this is me and my liquor store blues."</item>
		<item>"Lotto tickets and cheap beer. That's why you can catch me here, tryna scratch my way up to the top."</item>
		<item>"Standing at this liquor store, whiskey coming through my pores, feeling like I run this whole block."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
