<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Keyshia says she would never kiss a guy she doesn't know for a video."</item>
		<item>"Her song, \"Let It Go\" Features Missy Elliot and Lil' Kim. It also features a sample of Mtume's \"Juicy Fruit\". This same sample was used in The Notorious B.I.G.'s \"Juicy\"."</item>
		<item>"She moved to Los Angeles at the age of 16."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia was named the face of Akademiks Ladies for the Fall 2006 Advertising Campaign."</item>
		<item>"The Cole's adopted her after her mother Frankie, an addict at the time, could no longer take care of her."</item>
		<item>"She appears on R. Kelly's single \"Best Friend\" alongside Polow Da Don."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia Cole is still trying to put all of the pieces of the puzzle we call life together discovering long lost siblings, mending the relationship with her mother who was recently released from jail and supporting her sister, Neffe, and her four children."</item>
		<item>"Her video \"Love\", retired on 106 &amp; Park on April 19 2006."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia has two dogs, Lyric and Lola."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia's height is 5'2\" (1.57 m)."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia sang backup for M.C. Hammer when she was 12 years old."</item>
		<item>"Within minutes of catching her boyfriend cheating, Keyshia was in her car driving to Los Angeles in the middle of the night to start a brand-new life."</item>
		<item>"Her album \"The Way It Is\" has been certified gold and platinum."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia's talent, personality, and faith have won her fans and supporters within the music industry since she was a young girl."</item>
		<item>"Her full name is Keyshia Myeshia Cole."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia: There's a lot of trials and tribulations you have to go through to get what you want, especially if you feel like it belongs to you."</item>
		<item>"She appears on Diddy's single \"Last Night\"."</item>
		<item>"She appears on Young Jeezy's song and music video \"Dreamin\"."</item>
		<item>"Has said that people should listen to her music to get over a broken heart."</item>
		<item>"She performed at the BET Awards '07 on June 27, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia's biological mother is named Frankie Lons. Her adoptive mother's name is Yvonne Cole."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia is passionate about providing inspiration to young girls, and young people in general, who come from troubled backgrounds."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia: I want to be an example for young people, especially growing up in the 'hood, because it's already hard enough to not be focused, not to be trying, to be doing something. It's really possible."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia knew from childhood that she wanted to become a musician."</item>
		<item>"One of the first songs she sang as a little girl was \"As We Lay\" by Shirley Murdock."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia: Being young, you have to be really dedicated to doing it for yourself. There's a lot of trials and tribulations you have to go through to get what you want, especially if you feel like it belongs to you."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia, who was devoted to her boyfriend, realized after he cheated on her that he was devoted to himself."</item>
		<item>"She was on the cover of VIBE magazine."</item>
		<item>"She was born on October 15, 1981 in Oakland, California."</item>
		<item>"She was good friends with the late Tupac Shakur. She was staying at 'Marion 'Suge' Knight''s Las Vegas home on the evening Tupac was shot."</item>
		<item>"She was featured in Keak da Sneak's hit video \"Super Hyphy\"."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia started singing when she was around 6 years old."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia appeared on the track \"Never\" from the Barbershop 2 soundtrack with Eve. The song also appeared on her debut album \"The Way It Is\"."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia tied with Young Jeezy for the win of The \"Next\" VIBE award."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia was recently featured on Access Granted of the making of her music video \"Let It Go\" alongside Lil' Kim and Missy Elliot."</item>
		<item>"She has said that her brother, Sean Cole, and Tupac Shakur were close friends and that he was like an older brother to her."</item>
		<item>"The first song she recorded for her debut album was \"Love\"."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia (talking about her single \"Love\"): After I wrote the song, I went to the studio about 4 in the morning, and by 5 or 6 I was done with the song and that's what you hear."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia uses Mary J. Blige and Brandy as inspirations."</item>
		<item>"Her vocal range is soprano with a 2.5/3 octave."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia has brown eyes."</item>
		<item>"The tattoo on her right shoulder -- a cross, a heart, and a star -- truly reflects her belief that goals can be realized, despite the circumstances. Keyshia also has a tattoo of a teddy bear on her right ankle."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia's song, \"Talk To Me,\" co-written by singer Mya, Keyshia lets a guy know that his seeming disinterest is just a front."</item>
		<item>"She describes herself as a \"hard worker\", \"goofy\", and \"fun\"."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia: It's just different things that we see in the 'hood that we never see in Hollywood. I liked the contents of the song, because I felt like no girls talked about it."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia has admitted that ballads are not her favorite style."</item>
		<item>"She signed her best friend Amina to her recording label."</item>
		<item>"She once said she wouldn't sing, if the songs weren't straight from the heart."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia's album, Just Like You came on November 25, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia says that adding hope and faith and holding on to a dream can carry anyone far."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia Cole sung the national anthem twice for a football game and boxing game."</item>
		<item>"Keyshia also scored sessions singing hooks with other Bay Area artists, including Messy Marv's \"Nubian Queen\" remix, which was a regional hit for the rapper, and with Tony Toni Tone's Dwayne Wiggins, who featured her on his soundtrack for the indie film Mr &amp; Mrs. Jones."</item>
		<item>"Her single \"Let It Go\" reached #19 on the U.S. Chart and #3 on the U.S. R&amp;B Chart."</item>

			
	</string-array>
</resources>
	