<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"And tomorrow's just a mystery, oh, yeah, but that's okay. I'm alone, on my own and I'm starting off. I'll be strong, I'll be wrong, oh, but life goes on. Oh, I'm just a girl trying to find a place in this world."</item>
		<item>"He's the song in the car I keep singing. Dont know why i do."</item>
		<item>"And we know its never simple, never easy. Never a clean break, no one here to save me."</item>
		<item>"So watch me strike a match on all my wasted time. As far as I'm concerned, you're just another picture to burn."</item>
		<item>"I'm only me when i'm with you."</item>
		<item>"And all I think about is how to make you think of me, and everything that we could be"</item>
		<item>"I'm only up when you're not down. Don't wanna fly if you're still on the ground."</item>
		<item>"Feels like I'm falling and i am lost in your eyes. You make me crazier, crazier, crazier."</item>
		<item>"I'm intimidated by the fear of being average."</item>
		<item>"I'm not that complicated. My complications come out in my songs. All you need to do to be my friend is like me."</item>
		<item>"What I've learned is not to change who you are, because eventually you're going to run out of new things to become."</item>
		<item>"Talk to the man with the reasons why."</item>
		<item>"You don't even know where I start."</item>
		<item>"Everybody has that point in their life where you hit a crossroads and you've had a bunch of bad days and there's different ways you can deal with it and the way I dealt with it was I just turned completely to music."</item>
		<item>"I never want to change so much that people can't recognize me."</item>
		<item>"I suffer from girlnextdooritis where the guy is friends with you and that's it."</item>
		<item>"This is a new year. A new beginning. And things will change."</item>
		<item>"To me, Fearless is living in spite of those things that scare you to death."</item>
		<item>"People haven't always been there for me but music always has."</item>
		<item>"I suffer from girlnextdooritis where the guy is friends with you and that's it."</item>
		<item>"I never want to change so much that people can't recognize me."</item>
		<item>"Now its too late for you and your White Horse to come around."</item>
		<item>"You don't even know where I start."</item>
		<item>"What I've learned is not to change who you are, because eventually you're going to run out of new things to become."</item>
		<item>"I'm not that complicated. My complications come out in my songs. All you need to do to be my friend is like me."</item>
		<item>"I'm intimidated by the fear of being average."</item>
		<item>"Feels like I'm falling and i am lost in your eyes. You make me crazier, crazier, crazier."</item>
		<item>"I'm only up when you're not down. Don't wanna fly if you're still on the ground."</item>
		<item>"And all I think about is how to make you think of me, and everything that we could be."</item>
		<item>"I'm only me when i'm with you"</item>
		<item>"So watch me strike a match on all my wasted time. As far as I'm concerned, you're just another picture to burn."</item>
		<item>"He's the song in the car I keep singing. Dont know why i do."</item>
		<item>"And tomorrow's just a mystery, oh, yeah, but that's okay. I'm alone, on my own and I'm starting off. I'll be strong, I'll be wrong, oh, but life goes on. Oh, I'm just a girl trying to find a place in this world."</item>
		<item>"People haven't always been there for me but music always has."</item>
		<item>"I miss your tanned skin, your sweet smile, so good to me, so right."</item>
		<item>"I'd go back to December, turn around and change my own mind."</item>
		<item>"It turns out freedom ain't nothing but missing you, Wishing I'd realized what I had when you were mine."</item>
		<item>"And then the cold came, the dark days when fear crept into my mind. You gave me all your love and all I gave you was goodbye..."</item>
		<item>"These days I haven't been sleeping. Staying up playing back myself leavin."</item>
		<item>"And I go back to December all the time."</item>
		<item>"So this is me swallowing my pride Standing in front of you saying, \"I'm sorry for that night\"."</item>
		<item>"You gave me roses and I left them there to die."</item>
		<item>"Your guard is up and I know why, because the last time you saw me is still burned in the back of your mind."</item>
		<item>"I'm so glad you made time to see me. How's life? Tell me how's your family?"</item>
		<item>"Oh, I remember you were driving to my house In the middle of the night. I'm the one who makes you laugh When you know you're about to cry."</item>
		<item>"Standing by you Waiting at your backdoor. All this time How could you not know, baby."</item>
		<item>"Been here all along So why can't you see You belong with me?"</item>
		<item>"Can't you see That I'm the one Who understands you?"</item>
		<item>"Dreaming about the day when you wake up and find that what you're looking for has been here the whole time."</item>
		<item>"She wears high heels, I wear sneakers. She's cheer captain, And I'm on the bleachers."</item>
		<item>"It turns out freedom ain't nothing but missing you, Wishing I'd realize what I had when you were mine."</item>
		<item>"I'd go back in time and change it but I can't. So if the chain is on your door I understand."</item>
		<item>"Maybe this is wishful thinking, Probably mindless dreaming but if we loved again, I swear I'd love you right."</item>
		<item>"And how you held me in your arms that September night. The first time you ever saw me cry."</item>
		<item>"And I don't know why but with you I'd dance in a storm in my best dress...Fearless."</item>
		<item>"And I don't know how it gets better than this. You take my hand and drag me head first...Fearless"</item>
		<item>"And you know I wanna ask you to dance right there. In the middle of the parking lot...Yeah"</item>
		<item>"Well count to ten, take it in. This is life before you know who you're gonna be."</item>
		<item>"Cause when you're fifteen and somebody tells you they love you. You're gonna believe them."</item>
		<item>"Romeo save me, they're trying to tell me how to feel. This love is difficult, but it's real."</item>
		<item>"You'll be the prince and I'll be the princess, It's a love story, baby, just say yes."</item>
		<item>"That you were Romeo, you were throwing pebbles and my daddy said \"stay away from Juliet\"."</item>
		<item>"We were both young, when I first saw you. I close my eyes and the flashback starts- I'm standing there, on a balcony in summer air."</item>
		<item>"Romeo take me somewhere, we can be alone. I'll be waiting; all there's left to do is run."</item>
		<item>"He's just another picture to burn!"</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
