<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"All the hatin just fuels to my fire."</item>
		<item>"I dont care what you do fo you respect, but I would die for mine."</item>
		<item>"Let the losers worry about losin."</item>
		<item>"I aint dead, I aint done, I ain't scared, I aint run, no matter what, no matter what, still I stand."</item>
		<item>"Fear aint in the heart of me, I learned just do it, you get courage from your fears right after you go through it."</item>
		<item>"God will take you through hell, just to get you to heaven."</item>
		<item>"I give the niggas what they came to see, a reflection of one self where they aim to be."</item>
		<item>"People hate it when you're better than them they ain't hating, start worrying then."</item>
		<item>"Nigga, lyrically I'll murk you, Physically I'll hurt you, you ain't never ran the streets, you had a curfew."</item>
		<item>"At 14, man, thought I knew everything - I'm slangin slabs, trappin hard, movin heavy Cain - I bought an '85 cutlass on some dane-a-danes - Now I'm the shit, huh, the motor blew in 30 days."</item>
		<item>"To play me, ba-by, hey he gone need a track from God featuring Jesus or Jay-Z."</item>
		<item>"Im either running from life or im just waiting to die im the supplier or fire if you chasing a high."</item>
		<item>"If you dont respect nothin else, you will respect this hustle."</item>
		<item>"I promote peace and positivity."</item>
		<item>"Nevermind what haters say, ignore them til they fade away."</item>
		<item>"You dont have to be a dopeboy to have money."</item>
		<item>"It's easy to be on the straight and narrow when you in the joint because it ain't no temptation. You don't really got too much room to roam. Now, once you leave up out of them gates, walk back out there in that free world, breathe that air, your mentality then, that's what counts."</item>
		<item>"People hate it when you're better than them they ain't hating, start worrying then."</item>
		<item>"At 14, man, thought I knew everything - I'm slangin slabs, trappin hard, movin heavy Cain - I bought an '85 cutlass on some dane-a-danes - Now I'm the shit, huh, the motor blew in 30 days."</item>
		<item>"I give the niggaz what they came to see, a reflection of one self where they aim to be."</item>
		<item>"Nigga, lyrically I'll murk you, Physically I'll hurt you, - you ain't never ran the streets, you had a curfew."</item>
		<item>"Sooner or later the dawgh gonna get tired from barking at the moon and walk away, so let the moon shine dawgh, let the moon shine dawgh"</item>
		<item>"If GOD wit me who can be against me?"</item>
		<item>"In order to understand my train of thoughts you'll have to put yo self in my position you can't expect me to think like you cuz my life ain't like yours"</item>
		<item>"Never been fucked in the game I'm celibate"</item>
		<item>"I aint dead, I aint done, I ain't scared, I aint run, no matter what, no matter what, Still I stand"</item>
		<item>"All the hatin just fuels to my fire."</item>
		<item>"I aint dead, I aint done, I ain't scared, I aint run, no matter what, no matter what, still I stand."</item>
		<item>"My life yo entertainment you watch while I live it."</item>
		<item>"You kick like me, no exaggeration necessary Living revolutionary, nothin' less than legendary Gangsta shit heredity, got it from my dad Flow colder than February wit extraordinary swag"</item>
		<item>"Even when winning is illogical, losing still far form optional."</item>
		<item>"Just don't let your emotions overpower your intelligence."</item>
		<item>"If your heart fill with faith then you cant fear."</item>
		<item>"Life can change of direction even when u aint plan it."</item>
		<item>"My nigga get a Benz, I'll value yo opinion then."</item>
		<item>"5'9 with the soul of a 6'4 nigga!"</item>
		<item>"I got the mind of a hustler, Hellacious grind and I hold my city down, like an anchor iron."</item>
		<item>"You can have what ever you like."</item>
		<item>"Ay man real talk..in order to understand my train of thought you'd have to put yourself in position, you cant expect me to think like you cuz my life aint like yours you know what im sayin?"</item>
		<item>"Winning in ya Blood Yous was born wit wut it take. Ok."</item>
		<item>"Some move away to make a way not move a way cuz they afraid."</item>
		<item>"If ur heart filled with faith, then u can't fear."</item>
		<item>"Feed the ho snacks, everything you get you get to go, We ain't on no date what you eatin' drinkin' sittin' fo'."</item>
		<item>"Niggas hate on me because they know I can fuck their bitch."</item>
		<item>"K-I-N-G that's not gon' change I'm rich bitch, I don't care about no fame, Cuz If all else fails I got cocaine."</item>
		<item>"So you cant deny I'm patient but I aint gona try if you dont come I aint gonna die."</item>
		<item>"Ain't I let the haters trynna take a shot at me,they dun know wich way to go,I make it easy...follow Me!"</item>
		<item>"The spirit of a hustler and the swagger of a college kid."</item>
		<item>"Yea you know they call me T.I., but you dont know me."</item>
		<item>"Stop lookin at what you ain't got and start being thankful for what you do got."</item>
		<item>"I made it from the bottom to the top where I ought to be."</item>
		<item>"Nigga, lyrically I'll murk you. Physically I'll hurt you. You ain't never ran the streets, you had a curfew."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
