<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Marilyn Monroewas was an American actress, singer and model."</item>
		<item>"Date of Birth: 1 June 1926, Los Angeles, California, USA "</item>
		<item>"Date of Death: 5 August 1962, Los Angeles, California, USA (drug overdose)"</item>
		<item>"Birth Name: Norma Jeane Mortenson "</item>
		<item>"Nicknames: The Blonde Bombshell, MM "</item>
		<item>"Height: 5' 5½" (1.66 m)"</item>
		<item>"Her mother was a film-cutter at RKO Studios who, widowed and mentally ill, abandoned her to sequence of foster homes."</item>
		<item>"She was almost smothered to death at two, nearly raped at six."</item>
		<item>"At nine the LA Orphans' Home paid her a nickel a month for kitchen work while taking back a penny every Sunday for church. "</item>
		<item>"At sixteen she worked in an aircraft plant and married a man she called Daddy; he went into the military, she modeled, they divorced in 1946. "</item>
		<item>"She owned 200 books (including Tolstoy, Whitman, Milton), listened to Beethoven records, studied acting at the Actors' lab in Hollywood, and took literature courses at UCLA downtown."</item>
		<item>"Her first film was in 1947 with a bit part in The Shocking Miss Pilgrim (1947)."</item>
		<item>"Voted 'Sexiest Woman of the Century' by People Magazine. [1999]"</item>
		<item>"Was 1947's Miss California Artichoke Queen."</item>
		<item>"In her autobiography, \"My Story\", she recounted her guardian told her she was a direct descendant of James Monroe. Her mother's maiden name was Monroe, but there is no evidence she was a descendant of the US President."</item>
		<item>"Was roommates with Shelley Winters when they were both starting out in Hollywood."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #8 in Empire (UK) magazine's \"The Top 100 Movie Stars of All Time\" list. [October 1997]"</item>
		<item>"Voted Empire's (UK) \"sexiest female movie star of all time\" in 1995."</item>
		<item>"She was Playboy's first \"Sweetheart of the Month\", in December of 1953."</item>
		<item>"When she died in 1962 at age 36, she left an estate valued at $1.6 million. In her will, Monroe bequeathed 75 percent of that estate to Lee Strasberg, her acting coach, and 25 percent to Dr. Marianne Kris, her psychoanalyst."</item>
		<item>"The licensing of Marilyn's name and likeness, handled world-wide by Curtis Management Group, reportedly nets the Monroe estate about $2 million a year."</item>
		<item>"Was named the Number One Sex Star of the 20th Century by Playboy magazine in 1999."</item>
		<item>"Started using the name Marilyn Monroe in 1946, but did not legally change it until 1956."</item>
		<item>"Appeared on the first cover of Playboy in 1953."</item>
		<item>"Given a dog she named Tippy by foster father Albert Bolender. Her final, unfinished film, Something's Got to Give (1962), the dog was also named Tippy."</item>
		<item>"Interred at Westwood Memorial Park, Los Angeles, California, USA, in the Corridor of Memories, crypt #24."</item>
		<item>"Hundreds of items of memorabilia auctioned off in late October, 1999 by Christie's, with her infamous 'JFK' birthday-gown fetching over $1 million."</item>
		<item>"Childhood photos show she was born blonde, but her hair turned \"mousy\" as she grew older."</item>
		<item>"Chosen by Empire magazine as one of the 100 Sexiest Stars in film history (#2). [1995]"</item>
		<item>"Hugh M. Hefner owns the burial vault next to hers."</item>
		<item>"She was discovered dead at her home at 12305 Fifth Helena Drive, Brentwood, California. She had a phone in one of her hands, her body was completely nude and face down, on her bed."</item>
		<item>"Ex-husband Joe DiMaggio put fresh roses at her memorial site, for numerous years after her death."</item>
		<item>"Red-headed actress, Tina Louise portrayed the character of \"Ginger Grant\", on TV's \"Gilligan's Island\" (1964) was loosely based on her personality, but a different hair color."</item>
		<item>"Her first modeling job paid only five dollars."</item>
		<item>"Frequently used Nivea moisturizer."</item>
		<item>"During the filming of Niagara (1953), she was still under contract as a stock actor, thus, she received less salary than her make-up man. This was also the only film in which her character died. The film was reworked to highlight her after Anne Bancroft withdrew."</item>
		<item>"Often carried around the book, \"The Biography of Abraham Lincoln\"."</item>
		<item>"Was an outstanding player on the Hollygrove Orphanage softball team."</item>
		<item>"Because the bathing suit she wore in the movie Love Nest (1951) was so risque (for the time period) and caused such a commotion on the set, director Joseph M. Newman had to make it a closed set when she was filming."</item>
		<item>"Fearing blemishes and sweat, she washed her face fifteen times a day."</item>
		<item>"She was suggested as a possible wife for Prince Rainier of Monaco. But he picked actress, Grace Kelly, to be his wife."</item>
		<item>"Thought the right side of her face was her \"best\" side."</item>
		<item>"The first time she signed an autograph as Marilyn Monroe, she had to ask how to spell it. She didn't know where to put the \"i\" in \"Marilyn\"."</item>
		<item>"Born at 9:30 AM, Pacific Standard Time, which is Los Angeles, California's time zone."</item>
		<item>"Suffered from endometriosis, a condition in which tissues of the uterus lining (endometrium) leave the uterus, attach themselves to other areas of the body, and grow, causing pain, irregular bleeding, and, in severe cases, infertility."</item>
		<item>"Divorced first husband, James Dougherty, in Las Vegas, Nevada."</item>
		<item>"Divorced last husband, Arthur Miller, in Juarez, Mexico."</item>
		<item>"Wore glasses."</item>
		<item>"On Thursday, February 23rd, 1956, she obtained order from the City Court of the State of New York to legally change her name from Norma Jeane Mortenson to Marilyn Monroe."</item>
		<item>"Married Arthur Miller twice: the 1st time in a civil ceremony, then in a Jewish (to which she had converted) ceremony 2 days later."</item>
		<item>"Won an interlocutory decree from Joe DiMaggio on Wednesday, October 27th, 1954, but, under California law, the divorce was not finalized until exactly 1 year later."</item>
		<item>"Although it's believed that her mother, Gladys Baker, named her after Norma Talmadge, Gladys reportedly told her daughter, Bernice (Marilyn's half-sister), that she named Marilyn after Norma Jeane Cohen, a woman Gladys knew while she lived in Kentucky with Bernice's father."</item>
		<item>"The first stamp released in the USPS's Legends of Hollywood series, issued on Friday, June 1st, 1995."</item>
		<item>"Went to Van Nuys High School (Los Angeles) in the early 1940s but never graduated."</item>
		<item>"Elton John and Bernie Taupin wrote a tribute to her entitled "Candle in the Wind". In 1997 it was re-recorded with updated lyrics in memory of Princess Diana."</item>
		<item>"Her behavior on the unfinished Something's Got to Give (1962) dimmed her reputation in the industry, but she was still big box office at the time of her death. What a Way to Go! (1964) and The Stripper (1963) were being developed for her."</item>
		<item>"When told she was not the star in Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (1953) Marilyn was quoted \"Well whatever I am, I'm still the blonde\"."</item>
		<item>"Formed her own production company, Marilyn Monroe Productions, with Milton H. Greene, on December 31, 1955."</item>
		<item>"Appears on sleeve of The Beatles' \"Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band\" album."</item>
		<item>"Batman writer/artist Bob Kane used Marilyn's likeness as a reference when he drew Vicki Vale."</item>
		<item>"She is mentioned in the song \"Lady Nina\" by rock band Marillion."</item>
		<item>"Her USO Entertainer Identification Card (#129778) listed her name as \"Norma Jeane DiMaggio\"."</item>
		<item>"She was \"discovered\" by press photographers during a WWII photo shoot at the Radioplane plant in California owned by actor Reginald Denny. She was one of the plant's employees. She left her job and signed with Emmeline Snively's modeling agency."</item>
		<item>"Was referenced in the dialogue of La Dolce Vita (1960), in the context of dieting."</item>
		<item>"Measurements: 37C-24-35 (definitive measurements for the majority of her career) / (Source: Celebrity Sleuth magazine)"</item>
		<item>"The Emily Ann Faulkner/Rita Shawn character (played by Kim Stanley) in the John Cromwell film The Goddess (1958) was based on her."</item>
		<item>"The first Playboy magazine cover, featuring her, is pictured on one of six stamps issued in a souvenir sheet, issued by Grenada and the Grenadines on Saturday, December 1st, 2003 to celebrate Playboy's 50th and golden anniversary."</item>
		<item>"When she wasn't acting, she preferred to wear nothing but a bathrobe and occasionally a bikini."</item>
		<item>"Def Leppard's 1983 #1 hit single \"Photograph\" from their Pyromania album was written about her."</item>
		<item>"\"Candle in the Wind\", Elton John's song, was originally written about her, and was lyrically re-changed to fit Princess Diana upon her death, in 1997. Coincidentally, both legends died at age 36."</item>
		<item>"Named 2nd Greatest Movie Star of all time by Premier Magazine, behind #1 Cary Grant and after #3 Tom Cruise."</item>
		<item>"The punk band, 'The Misfits' created or picked their name from last movie title she acted in, The Misfits (1961)."</item>
		<item>"The punk band 'The Misfits' recorded a song called \"Who Killed Marilyn?\" inspired by lead singer Glenn Danzig's belief that she had been murdered."</item>
		<item>"Featured on a 1.11 euro postage stamp issued by French Post Office on Saturday, November 8th, 2003."</item>
		<item>"The very popular version of "Santa Baby" (also found in the film, Party Monster (2003)) thought to be sung by her was instead recorded by Cynthia Basinet for Jack Nicholson as a Christmas gift."</item>
		<item>"Ten days in advance, on Saturday, May 19th, 1962 she performed for U. S. President John F. Kennedy at his 45th birthday tribute in his honor at Madison Square Garden. She sang \"Happy Birthday\". (Kennedy's real birthday was May 29th)."</item>
		<item>"After discovering her dress was torn, at the 1950 Academy Awards, she burst into tears."</item>
		<item>"Was named #6 Actress on The American Film Institute's 50 Greatest Screen Legends."</item>
		<item>"Is one of the many movie stars mentioned in Madonna's song \"Vogue\"."</item>
		<item>"The dress Marilyn Monroe wore to serenade John F. Kennedy, on May 19, 1962 at his birthday celebration was so tight, that it had to be sewn onto her. She had to sit still for approximately an hour."</item>
		<item>"In 1999, a make-up kit that she personally owned, sold for $266,500."</item>
		<item>"One of the first Los Angeles natives to become a major movie star."</item>
		<item>"She took acting lessons from Michael Chekhov."</item>
		<item>"Sergei Parajanov made collages of Monroe, Charles Chaplin, Mona Lisa, and other famous personages and many were featured in Mikhail Vartanov's Parajanov: The Last Spring (1992)."</item>
		<item>"The ADR stage at Twentieth Century Fox is named after her."</item>
		<item>"Was good friends with Dorothy Dandridge and Ava Gardner when they were all young, struggling actresses in Hollywood."</item>
		<item>"In How to Marry a Millionaire (1953), her character Pola is reading a book called "Murder By Strangulation" on the plane. Coincidentally, this is how her character was murdered in Niagara (1953)."</item>
		<item>"Friend of James Haspiel."</item>
		<item>"What a Way to Go! (1964) initially intended as a vehicle for her, Shirley MacLaine played Louisa May Foster instead. Producer Arthur P. Jacobs was her publicist and J. Lee Thompson was on her list of approved directors"</item>
		<item>"She resided at the Hollywood Rossevelt while she was breaking into the acting business."</item>
		<item>"Her \"Happy Birthday Mr. President\" dress sold for $1,267,500.00, a world record for the most expensive piece of clothing ever sold, and is in the Guinness Book of World Records."</item>
		<item>"She left Hollywood to pursue serious acting by studying under Lee Strasberg at his Actors' Studio in New York City."</item>
		<item>"In 1946, she signed her first studio contract with 20th Century Fox and dyed her hair."</item>
		<item>"Producer Keya Morgan owns her Bible."</item>
		<item>"When she married Joe DiMaggio, the couple moved into a home at 508 N. Palm Drive in Beverly Hills, that was next door to Jean Harlow's last home."</item>
		<item>"She tried 9 different shades of blonde hair color before settling on platinum blonde."</item>
		<item>"Her personal library contained over 400 books on topics ranging from art to history, psychology, philosophy, literature, religion, poetry, and gardening. Many of the volumes, auctioned in 1999, bore her pencil notations in the margins."</item>
		<item>"There are over 600 books written about her."</item>
		<item>"At 168, Marilyn's IQ was significantly higher than John F. Kennedy's 129. (A score of 100 is considered average and 150 to be highly gifted)."</item>
		<item>"In 1961, after her divorce from Arthur Miller, she purchased a 2900 square foot hacienda style house in Brentwood, for $77,500."</item>
		<item>"Featured in "Femme Noir: Bad Girls of Film" by Karen Burroughs Hannsberry (McFarland, 1998)."</item>
		<item>"Champagne was her drink of choice and Dom Perignon was her personal favorite."</item>
		<item>"Her last film. Something's Got to Give (1962), was finally released in 2003. In the swimming pool scene, Marilyn reveals much more to the camera than she did in her then controversial calendar photo from the early '50s."</item>
		<item>"Was in consideration for the part of Adelaide in Guys and Dolls (1955/I), but Vivian Blaine was cast instead."</item>
		<item>"Although she was perhaps the most famous actress of the 1950's decade, she never made more than $100,000 per picture upfront. Actresses such as Elizabeth Taylor and Barbara Stanwyck were earning significantly more"</item>
		<item>"Former stepmother of Robert A. Miller."</item>
		<item>"She was sister of Berniece and Robert Kermitt Baker (but she never knew him, because he died at 14) by her mother's side. Sister-in-law of Paris Miracle, aunt of Mona Rae Miracle."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
