<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="facts">
        <item>Minaj noted Jay-Z as her favorite rapper, likening his lyrics to religious doctrine</item>
        <item>She is thought to weigh 140lbs or 63.5kg.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s measurements are 34C#8211;26#8211;45.</item>
        <item>Nicki stands 5\' 3</item>
        <item>Nicknames: Nicki Lewinski, Nicki The Harujuku Barbie, Nicki The Ninja, Nicki The Harajuku Barbie&#8230;</item>
        <item>Nicki uses her money to keep her family from struggling. These lines are from the song "I'm the Best".</item>
        <item>Nicki is a very talented artist. Her mixtapes are what attracted a lot of people to her music. She released mixtapes in 2007, 2008, and 2009.</item>
        <item>Was the first artist to ever have seven songs on billboard charts at the same time.</item>
        <item>Nicki has "God you are always with me" tattooed in traditional Chinese letters on her left arm.</item>
        <item>Graduated from LaGuardia High School, where she participated in the drama program. She had planned to sing at LaGuardia but lost her voice on the day of the audition.</item>
        <item>Nicki Currently Lives in Atlanta, Georgia</item>
        <item>She likes to Shop in Costume Stores</item>
        <item>Nicki is Afraid of heights.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s favorite movies are Gladiator and Set it Off</item>
        <item>Nicki loves to write.</item>
        <item>Her favorite actress is Jada Pinkett.</item>
        <item>Nicki graduated from LaGuardia High School Manhattan. There, she studied singing and acting.</item>
        <item>Nicki hates cats.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj dislikes people that burp.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj is a morning person.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s favorite color is pink.</item>
        <item>Nicki likes Kit-Kats.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s appearance on SNL gave the show their second highest ratings in the season.</item>
        <item>Nicki used to play the clarinet.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s favorite video shoot was "Check it Out" with will.i.am.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s favorite love song is Just the Way You Are by Bruno Mars.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s favorite party anthem is Firework by Katy Perry.</item>
        <item>Some of Nicki\'s favorite comedians include: Martin Lawrence, Chris Rock and Larry David.</item>
        <item>Nicki eats rap bitches for dinner.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj became the first artist ever to have seven songs within the Billboard Hot 100 at the same time.</item>
        <item>Nicki says that "Queen's girls are more girly than most girls".</item>
        <item>Nicki thinks a good wifey is naughty or nice. She says "Too nice is not good".</item>
        <item>Nicki started rapping by just being funny and messing around and eventually joined a small rap group.</item>
        <item>Nicki claims that she had the most fun recording "Roman's Revenge" out of all songs on Pink Friday.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s first kiss was in elementary school with a boy named Derrick or a boy named Travis. She can\'t quite remember.</item>
        <item>Nicki says that Wayne is little but he has a nice body.</item>
        <item>Nicki loves tattoos.</item>
        <item>Nicki says that her song "Save Me" is a more "Onika" type of song.</item>
        <item>Nicki says that in her next album she might do some Trini accent.</item>
        <item>In high school, Nicki put a b in front of people\'s names.</item>
        <item>Nicki was asked if she was a dancer and she replied "hell to the no".</item>
        <item>Nicki says that she is a perfectionist.</item>
        <item>Nicki says she loves white boys.</item>
        <item>Nicki doesn\'t get drunk.</item>
        <item>Nicki doesn\'t like saying "men" or "women". She likes to say "boys" and "girls".</item>
        <item>Nicki loves intelligent men.</item>
        <item>Nicki used to be a waitress.</item>
        <item>Nicki plans on making a perfume.</item>
        <item>Nicki was fired from about 4 red lobsters because they said she "had attitude".</item>
        <item>Nicki loves her barbs and kens.</item>
        <item>Pink Friday is PLATINUM.</item>
        <item>Nicki started making "weird raps" when she was 11 years old.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s father dealt with alcohol and drugs as Nicki grew up.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s mom means the world to her.</item>
        <item>Nicki has been writing and recording raps for over 7 years.</item>
        <item>Nicki remembers listening to George Michael as she grew up.</item>
        <item>Nicki wears Chloe perfume.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s mom once had a dream that her dad would set the house on fire. The next day, her dad actually set the house on fire.</item>
        <item>Minaj is openly bi-sexual.</item>
        <item>Nicki is shittin\' on all the other rap bitches.</item>
        <item>Nicki sites beloved rap figure Lauryn Hill as one of her major influences and says that she wants fans to focus on her music and not her sexy image.</item>
        <item>She is the first female rap act signed to rapper Lil Wayne\'s Young Money Records and is the labels first lady.</item>
        <item>In 2008 she won the Female Artist Of The Year at the Underground Music Awards.</item>
        <item>She studied singing and acting at LaGaurdia High School in NY where she graduated.</item>
        <item>Before rapping she sang background vocals and hooks for local rap acts from around her way.</item>
        <item>Nicki is the survivor of a broken home. The product of a drug addicted father and a struggling single-mom.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj has also referred to herself as "Cookie","Harajuku Barbie" and "Roman Zolanski".</item>
        <item>She worked at a Red Lobster restaurant in the Bronx.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj\'s fast food of choice is Popeyes Chicken.</item>
        <item>She has a sister and two brothers.</item>
        <item>She\'s a Saggitarius.</item>
        <item>She\'s a native New Yorker hailing from Jamaica, Queens, NY.</item>
        <item>Minaj is of mixed descent with African, Trinidadian and Indo-Asian roots.</item>
        <item>The tattoo on her left arm is Chinese script for "God is with me always".</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s real name is Onika Maraj.</item>
        <item>Her birthday is December 8, 1984.</item>
        <item>The outfit that Nicki wore to The Grammy\'s was by Givenchy.</item>
        <item>Nicki claims that she would do a song with Taylor Swift.</item>
        <item>Nicki thinks that Lady GaGa is "badass" and she would not mind doing a song with GaGa.</item>
        <item>Nicki\'s dream role is to play someone in a Tim Burton movie, where she would get dressed up and painted and crazy.</item>
        <item>Nicki would also enjoy playing a role in an action movie, like Angelina Jolie.</item>
        <item>Nicki loves Judge Judy and she even calls her a "comedian".</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>Tell them hoes stoppington; they know they want everything that we be coppington.</item>
        <item>You like me, you don\'t like me, you love me, you hate me. I\'m gonna be me, but one thing I have to back it up is skills.</item>
        <item>When you was on stage with ya brain on drugs, Nick Nack Carry Crack what my nickname was.</item>
        <item>That\'s when I hopped out da pink on pink; hate it when a bitch act like her shit don\'t stink.</item>
        <item>And when he spank this I make that pussy fart. I\'m such an actress, Melissa Joan Hart.</item>
        <item>It\'s been a long time coming, but I came now everybody in the rap game know my name, but honey ain\'t a damn thang;&#8230;</item>
        <item>Out weights ya change, out weights ya change.</item>
        <item>Similes, metaphors and we pop pills. Sick flow inundated with the doc bills. Work hard, now we know how to top bills; in the middle of the street doing cartwheels.</item>
        <item>RIP to Anna Nicole Smith. Yes my dear, you\'re so explosive. Say Hi to Mary Mary and Joseph, now bottoms up and double my dosage</item>
        <item>If I wasn\'t a rapper, then I could have got a pop deal.</item>
        <item>And free my Lil Weezy and lets just get right. Young Money Cash Money in the building, lets go the world ends tonights.</item>
        <item>I Am Zolanski, I\'m Roman.</item>
        <item>I think big, get cash, make \'em blink fast.</item>
        <item>And I\'ll say boy the Chucky is Child\'s play. Just killed another career it\'s a mild day.</item>
        <item>We can do debit, I don\'t need no credit. Yes I\'m epic, look how I rep it. It\'s been eight years but I broke the record.</item>
        <item>On a diet but my pockets eating cheesecake.</item>
        <item>Hotter than a middle eastern climate.</item>
        <item>Yeah my money\'s so tall that my Barbies gotta climb it.</item>
        <item>And if I\'m fake I aint notice cause my money aint.</item>
        <item>And I\'m all up all up all up in the bank with the funny face And if I\'m fake I aint notice cause my money aint.</item>
        <item>Young money is the roster and the monster crew.</item>
        <item>Ok first things first I\'ll eat your brains Then I\'ma start rocking gold teeth and fangs.</item>
        <item>You could be the King, but watch the Queen conquer.</item>
        <item>Yeah I\'m in that Tonka, color of Willy Wonka.</item>
        <item>Before I play it yo know my hand. You can turn a freethrow to a goal. Nigga got the peep hole to my soul.</item>
        <item>Pull up in the monster; Automobile gangster with a bad b-tch that came from Sri Lanka.</item>
        <item>\'Cause you cab do it two, and you can do it too. I just happen to be the girl that they through it to.</item>
        <item>Don\'t be mad when you see me transending GUCC!</item>
        <item>Better Strap Up Ya Boots, Before They start to shoot, don\'t know. It\'s Young Money Salute.</item>
        <item>Before I played it, you knew my hand.</item>
        <item>I\'ma need my badges and my ribbons, maybe it\'ll make up for everything I wasn\'t given.</item>
        <item>Forget the haters, just get ya money, just get ya weight up.</item>
        <item>I am not Jasmine, I\'m Aladdin.</item>
        <item>The good advice, I always hated. But looking back, it made me greater.</item>
        <item>I\'m still hood, Hollywood couldn\'t change me</item>
        <item>I will retire with the crown, Yes No I\'m not lucky I\'m blessed, Yes</item>
        <item>We done did everything they could think of</item>
        <item>You see right through me. How do you do that shit?</item>
        <item>You see right through me</item>
        <item>I call the play, now do you see why? These bitches callin\' me Manning, Eli</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj is who you ain\'t fuckin\' with</item>
        <item>I\'m startin\' to feel like a dungeon dragon. Raah, raah, like a dungeon dragon</item>
        <item>See me in that new thing, bums is gaggin\'</item>
        <item>I wish that I could have this moment for life</item>
        <item>Greatness is what we on the brink of</item>
        <item>It\'s a celebration every time we link up</item>
        <item>I get what I desire - it\'s my empire</item>
        <item>I call the shots, I am the umpire</item>
        <item>In this very moment I\'m king In this very moment I slayed Goliath with a sling.</item>
        <item>Clap for the heavy weight champ; me!</item>
        <item>I fly with the stars and the skies. I am no longer trying to survive.</item>
        <item>Greatness is what we on the brink of.</item>
        <item>I am not Jazmin, I am Aladdin.</item>
        <item>No I\'m not lucky, I\'m blessed.</item>
        <item>I believe that life is a prize, but to live doesn\'t mean you\'re alive.</item>
        <item>I wish that I could have this moment for life.</item>
        <item>Don\'t worry about me and who I fire, I get what I desire..it\'s my empire.</item>
        <item>Before I got signed, I was doing a lot of DVD\'s, and a lot of freestyles.</item>
        <item>My haters are my motivators</item>
        <item>Flow tighter than a d*** in the butt.</item>
        <item>I\'m mean muggin\' like Lil Mama on Jay\'s Set.</item>
        <item>May the Lord protect me as the world gets hectic.</item>
        <item>I\'m the baddest in the school, the baddest in the game.</item>
        <item>Yo, now all these b*****s wanna try and be my bestie, but I take a left and leave them hanging like a testie. Trash talk to \'em, then I put \'em in a Hefty.</item>
        <item>I am so territorial, that [from the start] I just felt like whatever I was gonna do I was gonna write it myself, its my personal preference to always be in control of everything I do in life.</item>
        <item>White girls tell me hey, Nicki your camp rules. Is that why you get more head than shampoos.</item>
        <item>Bad b****es do not have promiscuous sex.</item>
        <item>Please you can never compare to me, all these b****es is scared of me. I am who they couldn\'t even dare to be.</item>
        <item>Step yo d*** down, to like basement status.</item>
        <item>I don\'t give a f*** about you or your bum crew.</item>
        <item>Ask Lil Wayne who the 5-star b**** is.</item>
        <item>Switch my hair, they gon\' copy her. Switch my gear, they gon\' copy her. Look at how they stare, just a copier. Roger that. Did you copy that? Copycat.</item>
        <item>If every n**** can say he had it, you\'re not exclusive. You\'re not a bad b****.</item>
        <item>I\'m gettin\' the munchies, I think I\'ll have a rap b**** for my entree.</item>
        <item>Cause it\'s Barbie b****, you can join the wave. I done penny, nickel, dime, I done coined the phrase.</item>
        <item>Which bitch you know made a million off a mixtape</item>
        <item>Fuck I look like hoe? I look like yes and you look like no!</item>
        <item>My flow hotter than noon in June.</item>
        <item>And I\'ma make you beg \'cause you look pretty when you begging. So meet me on the campus, I\'ll be there around 11:00.</item>
        <item>I tell a bitch this: I\'m not impressed bitch I\'m Nicki M trick, I\'m always on the guest list.</item>
        <item>I\'ve had my highs and had my lows but you can\'t tell me that I am not the baddest chick.</item>
        <item>I don\'t give a fuck about you or your bum crew.</item>
        <item>Step ya cookies up. Girl get you a ladder.</item>
        <item>You know they say \'who is Nicki Minaj\' and you know I\'m like a multiple personality bitch.</item>
        <item>Which bitch you know made a million off a mixtape.</item>
        <item>I\'m a bad bitch, I ain\'t never been a mixed breed.</item>
        <item>I\'m still hood, Hollywood couldn\'t change me.</item>
        <item>I\'m tighter than face lifts and flyer than spaceships.</item>
        <item>My haters are my motivators.</item>
        <item>I say I body b*tches, it means that b*tch got killed. Ridin\' the baseline like I\'m Quile O\'Neal</item>
        <item>Cause you thought you\'d win, but I knew you\'d lose honey. I\'m flyer than altitude cruise.</item>
        <item>There\'s always gonna be evil people in the world who just do negative shit. You just got to kill \'em with kindness barbs, and they\'ll die slow.</item>
        <item>You gave me strengh gave me hope for a lifetime.</item>
        <item>Only one chance one bullet in the gun. This is my life and I only got one, yeah. The safety\'s off and I put on her. Oh stick \'em up, stick \'em up. Ready to shoot.</item>
        <item>I no longer need your attention;&#8230;at ease</item>
        <item>Strange how someone you once loved can become just another person you once knew."</item>
        <item>I\'m badder than the dude at the Neverland, Get the money green coupe with a lepre-can (leprechaun)</item>
        <item>You\'ll be gone to November like Wyclef, I move weight and I ain\'t talkin\' bout biceps</item>
        <item>Tell Stack, to bring the black Carter, But If I f*ck em, would he? Would he yell \'Squad Up!\'</item>
        <item>My flow stupid; wheel chair bound, Take the small bus.. All year round</item>
        <item>I\'m the one! I\'m the one, ya heard me?, The same number that\'s stitched on McGrady\'s jersey</item>
        <item>Every, every time I spit I mas-a-cre (masacre); So you better run quick like Nas-a-car (Nascar)</item>
        <item>Yes I\'m the girl that they hearda, I commit murda, I body bitches, I don\'t need a burna</item>
        <item>I\'m bout that fast money, money ain\'t got no patience, But if them boys come, run like you on probation</item>
        <item>I only fuck with bad bitches. no homo</item>
        <item>So where my cash at, where my stash at?, I mean, where the Dow Jones, where the NASDAQ?</item>
        <item>I stay around the white like the Klu Klux Klan, stay around the sand butter pecan tan</item>
        <item>I say I body b*tches, it means that b*tch got killed, Ridin\' the baseline like I\'m Quile O\'Neal </item>
        <item>I\'m from the Philipine, badder than Billy Gene, That\'s why I get more head than a guillotine</item>
        <item>Back to basics, bitch I been hot since Asics, And I\'m tighter than face lifts, flier than spaceships</item>
        <item>When I come around it gets hotter than a soup kitchen, I\'ll leave clips in your head like a beautician</item>
        <item>I\'ma spit on it, then I\'m gon sit on it, You can f*ck my girls too daddy, I\'m kin-done-it (condone it)</item>
        <item>I never knew my titties was bigger than Pamela, So paparazzi flickin\' be flickin\' they camera</item>
        <item>One Two Buckle My Shoe, No One On The Corner Has Swagga Like I Do</item>
        <item>Get me my limozine, all in your magazine, And when I come dem better lean like Promethazine</item>
        <item>Ask Rocko, ask Gucci, Gucci bandana, I\'m a star, I\'m the black Hannah Montana</item>
        <item>I keep three hoes, But don\'t\'call me Santa Anna-and I\'m flyer than reindeers in the winter</item>
        <item>I mean Tinker, tell n*gga link her, Cause I\'m lookin\' for some good brain from a thinker</item>
        <item>Now I\'m a dime, you a nickellete, Light skinned-ed pig-ament, stop copyrightin\' infringement, I eat these rap b*ches, somebody get me a dinner mint</item>
        <item>You can hate me but why knock my hussle, I\'mma be the queen no matter how they shuffle, Skirts with the ruffle, Louie on the duffle, I\'m a bad b*tch, no muzzle</item>
        <item>I\'mma need a coupleof those benz-ez-ez, I be up out China spendin Yenz-ez-ez, Gucci on my lens-ez-ez, my leather so sensetive, Scratch my 9 o\'clock, I wanna shop, make it ten-tative</item>
        <item>She Gets No Burn No Smoking Sign Yea Metaphor Heaven Cause They Approve Nicki Like My Credit Score 7″</item>
        <item>Wanna Play Meet Me At The Fumble Line Cause Umma Ninja Cowabunga Time</item>
        <item>Money in the air it\'s a festival Cause I ba-ba-ba-ba ball no testicles</item>
        <item>I Been Bad Since Sticky Hands Now All These Bitches is Nicki Fans</item>
        <item>Thumbs up like im hailin a yellow cab, My flow NUTS like M&amp;Ms in a yellow bag</item>
        <item>To live doesn\'t mean your alive</item>
        <item>I am so territorial, that I just felt like whatever I was gonna do I was gonna write it myself, its my personal preference to always be in control of everything I do in life.</item>
        <item>May the lord protect me as the world gets hectic; My voice projected my life reflected</item>
        <item>Days of our lives, you wink it goes by.</item>
        <item>I believe that life is a prize.</item>
        <item>This one goes out to all my critics: don\'t you feel stupid? Look how I did it. Look how it came to pass when I said it.</item>
        <item>Just for the record, I\'m all that I can be, and I\'ll admit I\'m appauled when you envy.</item>
        <item>Nicki Minaj is who you ain\'t fu*kin\' with</item>
        <item>If you ain\'t shi**in\', then get off the pot</item>
        <item>Why are you speaking when no one asked you?</item>
        <item>Shoutout to my haters, sorry that you couldn\'t phase me.</item>
        <item>Cause you thought you\'d win, but I knew you\'d lose honey. I\'m flyer than altitude cruise</item>
        <item>White boys tell me that I rock like guitars</item>
        <item>My pu**y on another planet; got that NASA pu**y</item>
        <item>On a diet, but I\'m doing donuts in the six speed.</item>
        <item>When you was on stage with ya brain on drugs, Nick Nack Carry Crack what my nickname was</item>
        <item>And when he spank this I make that pu**y fart. I\'m such an actress, Melissa Joan Hart.</item>
        <item>And I\'m all up all up all up in the bank with the funny face. And if I\'m fake I aint notice cause my money aint</item>
        <item>Yeah I\'m in that Tonka, color of Willy Wonka</item>
        <item>Pull up in the monster; Automobile gangster with a bad b-tch that came from Sri Lanka</item>
        <item>I know you love her, but I love you</item>
        <item>Bitches is like crabs in a butcket. You see a bad bitch gettin shine you should love it </item>
        <item>Muahhhh me love you long time like I\'m asian</item>
        <item>Nigga got the peep hole to my soul.</item>
        <item>And if he think I like him then he might be right</item>
        <item>Control my mind - Capture my soul</item>
        <item>You like me, you don\'t like me, you love me, you hate me.I\'m gonna be me, but one thing I have to back it up is skills.</item>
        <item>Similes, metaphors and we pop pills. Sick flow inundated with the doc bills.Work hard, now we know how to top bills; in the middle of the street doing cartwheels.</item>
        <item>I think big, get cash, make \'em blink fast</item>
        <item>Can I get that tron? Can I get that remy? Can I get that coke? Can I get that henny?</item>
        <item>You could be the King, but watch the Queen conquer</item>
        <item>So I\'ma bounce back, and I\'ma ball out, and everytime you see me I\'ma go all out, and I\'ma win til the ending.</item>
        <item>Defend my honor - Protect my pride</item>
        <item>Once upon a time not long ago lived a chick named Nicki wit a naughty flow</item>
        <item>All I do is sign boobs and be taking pics. Got the new benz the color of bacon bits.</item>
        <item>See I\'m a hater, I go hard. Listen let\'s begin. You know her last name Minaj, she a lesbian</item>
        <item>Nicki sexy any time of day</item>
        <item>Bitch won\'t blow, but she can blow my saxophone</item>
        <item>What the fuck I look like bitch, I run this town.</item>
        <item>Why don\'t you just sit back or dance? Sorry we don\'t chit-chat with fans</item>
        <item>I eat these rap bitches, somebody get me a dinner mint</item>
        <item>Young Money Nicki, Bad Boy Cassie.You wanna minaj? Now lets get nasty.</item>
        <item>Roscoe\'s on his knees with a snot nose</item>
        <item>I just give him a wink; what the f**k did ya think?</item>
        <item>Now All These Bitches Wanna Try And Be My Bestie. But I Take A Left And Leave Em Hanging Like A Testie</item>
        <item>You be yellin boom-boom; When you really poom-poom.</item>
        <item>If you don\'t have critics, you probably don\'t have success either.</item>
        <item>These broke rappers always rappin bout a pink truck, I\'m only happy wen I hoppin\' out da brincks truck</item>
        <item>I think better with thick chicks with lip stick.</item>
        <item>If he work the middle like a mohawl, tell \'em he can meet me where them girls say Aloha</item>
        <item>I\'m like 5\'2 my S.A.T. scores was high too.</item>
        <item>All my New York broads spend chips in the village.</item>
        <item>Bitch I ball no peep show; dead ass no peep show!</item>
        <item>I keep three hoes, But don\'t call me Santa</item>
        <item>I had to laugh at dat one, bitch get outta line I\'m a slap da fat one</item>
        <item>I\'m the mothafuckin\' boss, overwrite.</item>
        <item>Pu**y real good, it taste like mango</item>
        <item>If you ain\'t shittin\', then get off the pot.</item>
        <item>Is this the thanks that I get for puttin\' you bitches on?</item>
        <item>So far ahead, these bums is laggin\'</item>
        <item>I\'m the baddest in the game. Excuse me, honey. Nobody\'s in my lane.</item>
        <item>Please you can never compare to me, all these bi**hes is scared of me. I am who they couldn\'t even dare to be</item>
        <item>I got that kinda money that make a bitch broke bitter.</item>
        <item>F-ck I look like ho? I look like yes and ya look like no.</item>
        <item>Got\'damn, aint even pregnant, But i\'m birthin bitches</item>
        <item>Nicki ain\'t a rapper, she\'s a brander</item>
        <item>All these bitches is my sons</item>
        <item>Just for the record: get wetter than a fisherman</item>
        <item>Why did you envy? Why you go against me when I got trendy? Why you ain\'t commend me?</item>
        <item>I never knew my titties was bigger than Pamela. So paparazzi flickin\' be flickin\' they camera.</item>
        <item>Young Money Nicki, Bad Boy Cassie You wanna minaj? Now lets get nasty.</item>
        <item>White boys tell me that I rock like guitars.</item>
        <item>See see ya see Anna Mae, I\'m bout to slap y\'all bitches around and call y\'all Anna Mae.</item>
        <item>Pink wig thick ass give em whip lash.</item>
        <item>Don\'t talk to me about chicks got skills; she\'s alright, but she\'s not real.</item>
        <item>Just when they thought it was safe to play I hit \'em with the N.I.C. the K.I.</item>
        <item>I wanna know why you waste ya time on these rap hoes that don\'t write they rhymes.</item>
        <item>Money money money always on my mind.</item>
        <item>Dodged to the room and whipped out the magnum.</item>
        <item>Slim trim also light skinned</item>
        <item>I told Khaled that you the best, but I\'m the bestest. Better run for cover if your name is on my checklist.</item>
        <item>Flyer than a rocket, money in my polly. My Pocket what you coppin; keep that work up in my pippy long stocking bitch</item>
        <item>If he work the middle like a mohawk, tell \'em he can meet me where them girls say Aloha</item>
        <item>Grab him by his locks and give \'em some good box</item>
        <item>My pussy on another planet; got that NASA pussy</item>
        <item>Kick it like Air Max, I don\'t wanna hear that.</item>
        <item>Why when I needed it? Why you couldn\'t lend me why you was a secretive frontin\' like you friendly.</item>
        <item>A shot is a shot if you got a good aim.</item>
        <item>Class is finished, you\'ll be home by three. Tell all of them rap bitches what you know \'bout me.</item>
        <item>I done put two sticks in my bun, so they recognize me when I come, I\'m D.M.C. like Run.</item>
        <item>You don\'t like me, you just like my flow. Just booked a show, but I might not go; nigga said he didn\'t have a pole for my hoe.</item>
        <item>Nicki sexy any time of day.</item>
        <item>I just give him a wink; what the fuck did ya think?</item>
        <item>Just for the record: get wetter than a fisherman.</item>
        <item>You bad, but Nicki is badder Step ya cookies up, go get you a ladder.</item>
        <item>Hmmm I feel freer than the slaves on the railroad.</item>
        <item>And if he think I like him then he might be right.</item>
        <item>You can talk slick all the way down to the welfare. Ask the I.R.S. bitch I\'m payin for ya health care.</item>
        <item>I\'m in that money green jag. Lotta money bags.</item>
        <item>He said he want a marshian, he can be my Tarzan.</item>
        <item>When I throw this pussy, you better not start duckin\'.</item>
        <item>Now that\'s one bottle, two bottle, three bottle, four!</item>
        <item>That is where a real bad barbie raom r-r-r-r-r-raom. Sorry I broke up, excuse my cell phone, it must be a ATaT dead zone.</item>
        <item>Bitch won\'t blow, but she can blow my saxophone.</item>
        <item>I\'m the Barbie. Keep a lot of plastic, little pink stars, put \'em on my jacket. Somebody tell her I\'ma put her in a casket.</item>
        <item>Old ass broad off track like bad weave.</item>
        <item>Name a girl that\'s real as her. Nope, not them.</item>
        <item>Ya caramel dream ya girl from queens.</item>
        <item>I\'m a winner mommy, your career\'s a gamble.</item>
        <item>But then I\'m dumbstruck cause you bums suck.</item>
        <item>Who\'s ya best MC\'s? Nick, Fox And Kim, Cant Forget Remi.</item>
        <item>I got that presidential cooch, when he see it he salute.</item>
        <item>He make my pussy sing like it\'s a mozart. He say the pussy pretty, it look like show art.</item>
        <item>And everywhere I go they tell me that I\'m pretty.</item>
        <item>I hit one, you hit one. That mean two alive, but if they come back to Queens its a suicide.</item>
        <item>954 Double R Zoom Zoom. I don\'t give a fuck about ya looney toon goon Yell boom boom when ya really poom poom.</item>
        <item>I eat these rap bitches, no fork, no spoon. I\'m Nicki, I\'m finicky, I\'m picky.</item>
        <item>You guys are like above and beyond anything that I could EVER freakin imagine.</item>
        <item>Did you roger that? Did you c-c-copy that?</item>
        <item>Roscoe\'s on his knees with a snot nose.</item>
        <item>Got a spot in every state; Dalmation bitch.</item>
        <item>I\'m such a girl, I\'m such a girly girl. I\'m sippin on my milkshake with this swirly swirl.</item>
        <item>See I\'m a hater, I go hard. Listen let\'s begin. You know her last name Minaj, she a lesbian.</item>
        <item>Write it down, take a picture, bitches email that. I came to save a thing called female rap.</item>
        <item>Thank you. Thank you for coming out tonight. Ladies and Gentlement, I am the president of dirty money records.</item>
        <item>Everybody gon\' see where I\'m lyrically at; used to hate Nicki, now they givin me dap.</item>
        <item>I\'m always on the run; got weight to burn. Ease off the gas then I make the turn.</item>
        <item>Can I get a encore? I know you want more.</item>
        <item>Bitches is like crabs in a butcket You see a bad bitch gettin shine you should love it </item>
        <item>I heard you was lookin for the big bad wolf? I mean the bad bitch from the big apple.</item>
        <item>Why don\'t you just sit back or dance? Sorry we don\'t chit-chat with fans.</item>
        <item>Pussy this, pussy that; Thick pussy fat Break me off a piece of that pussy kit pussy kat.</item>
        <item>I\'ll pop you then I\'ll pop ya little sister.</item>
        <item>I just came out of the mothafuckin\' old school. Got my mac notebook with the pro tools.</item>
        <item>These broke rappers always rappin bout a pink truck, I\'m only happy wen I hoppin\' out da brincks truck.</item>
        <item>I\'m bout that fast money, money ain\'t got no patience. But if them boys come run like you on probation.</item>
        <item>I keep three hoes, But don\'t call me Santa.</item>
        <item>I never knew my titties was bigger than Pamela. So paparazzi be flickin\' they camera.</item>
        <item>I eat these rap bitches, somebody get me a dinner mint.</item>
        <item>Okay I get it, let me think I guess it\'s my turn. Maybe it\'s time to put this pussy on ya sideburns.</item>
        <item>Bank rolls give mBank rolls give me all them pretty furs cause my pussy game cold when he hit it he say \'burr\', he say \'burr\' \'bur bur bur burr, I\'ma i\'ma marry her\' and he play with that purr like he strummin\' his guitar.</item>
        <item>I say balling I don\'t mean \'Spalding\'. I never answer when the referee is calling.</item>
        <item>You was sleeping on me thinking it was slumber time. Now I\'m a trending topic Lil mama number sign.</item>
        <item>Lookin\' for good brain. Where ya thinking cap?</item>
        <item>Detonating my bomb, detonating them hits. Gonna buy out the bar, all my bitches is rich.</item>
        <item>Detonate in the palms, detonate in the fire. Rose by the bucket. Money make an attire.</item>
        <item>But a star will arise and she\'ll originate from the streets of South side.</item>
        <item>Aye can anybody hear me!</item>
        <item>I am Nicki Minaj and it\'s all on me.</item>
        <item>Sort of lost sight of what I\'m doin\' it for. Thought that I was doin\' something good for the game til they all started throwin\' dirt on my name.</item>
        <item>Dear God, I am only what you made and I appreciate everything that you gave me, but like I don\'t want to do it no more. Sort of lost sight of what I\'m doing it for.</item>
        <item>Got that eninini-eninini Little Mermaid on my linen When yo mama sleepin you call me and get all up in it.</item>
        <item>Once upon a time not long ago lived a chick named Nicki wit a naughty flow.</item>
        <item>I really like your kitty cat and if you let me touch her I know you\'re not a bluffer, I\'ll take you to go see Usher.</item>
        <item>I\'m such a diva, number one dick pleaser. Nicki been hot since you was rockin Adidas.</item>
        <item>I know you love her, but I love you.</item>
        <item>Please you can never compare to me, all these bitches is scared of me. I am who they couldn\'t even dare to be.</item>
        <item>Step yo dick down, to like basement status.</item>
        <item>Ask Lil Wayne who the 5-star bitch is.</item>
        <item>If every nigga can say he had it, you\'re not exclusive. You\'re not a bad bitch.</item>
        <item>I\'m gettin\' the munchies, I think I\'ll have a rap bitch for my entree.</item>
        <item>Cause it\'s Barbie bitch, you can join the wave. I done penny, nickel, dime, I done coined the phrase.</item>
        <item>Which bitch you know made a million off a mixtape?</item>
        <item>Cause my flow\'s stupid, wheelchair bound, take the small bus all year round.</item>
        <item>I keep three hoes, But don\'t\'call me Santa.</item>
        <item>I get what I desire, it\'s my empire.</item>
        <item>I fly with the stars in the skies.</item>
        <item>And yes I call the shots, I am the umpire.</item>
        <item>Put it on everything, that I will retire with the ring. And I will retire with the crown yes. No I\'m not lucky, I\'m blessed yes. Clap for the heavy weight champ me.</item>
        <item>Cause I\'m still hood, Hollywood couldn\'t change me.</item>
        <item>Shout out to my haters, sorry that you couldn\'t phase me.</item>
        <item>Flow tighter than a dick in the butt.</item>
        <item>Yo, now all these bitches wanna try and be my bestie, but I take a left and leave them hanging like a testie. Trash talk to \'em, then I put \'em in a Hefty.</item>
        <item>White girls tell me hey, Nicki your camp rules. Is that why you get more head than shampoos?</item>
        <item>Been around the world, I still can\'t find, another girl that can steal my shine. I\'ve had my highs, I\'ve had my lows, but you can\'t tell me that I am not the baddest bitch!</item>
        <item>Bad bitches do not have promiscuous sex.</item>
        <item>And if he want some pussy that\'s a no-no. I only fucks with bad bitches, no homo.</item>
        <item>I\'m a bad bitch, I\'m a cunt. And I\'ll kick that hoe, punt.</item>
        <item>I get the kind of money that make a broke bitch bitter.</item>
        <item>Forget barbie, f-ck Nicki, she\'s fake. She\'s on a diet but my pockets eating cheesecake.</item>
        <item>Keep a couple wet wipes case a bum try to touch me, ew</item>
        <item>I mean, sigh, sickenin\' eyes. I can tell that you\'re in touch with your feminine side.</item>
        <item>Excuse me, you\'re a hell of a guy you know. I really got a thing for American guys.</item>
        <item>He just gotta give me that look, when he give me that look. Then the panties comin\' off, off, uh.</item>
        <item>Boy you got my heartbeat runnin\' away. Beating like a drum and it\'s coming your way. Can\'t you hear that boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass. Yeah that\'s that super bass.</item>
        <item>Yes I did, yes I did, somebody please tell him who the F I is.</item>
        <item>I said, excuse me you\'re a hell of a guy. I mean my, my, my, my you\'re like pelican fly.</item>
        <item>That\'s the kind of dude I was lookin\' for and yes you\'ll get slapped if you\'re lookin\' hoe.</item>
        <item>He cold, he dope, he might sell coke. He always in the air, but he never fly coach.</item>
        <item>He ill, he real, he might gotta deal. He pop bottles and he got the right kind of built.</item>
        <item>I get what I desire, its my empire And yes I call the shots, I am the umpire.</item>
        <item>Ho-s is mad cause these ho-s is losing!</item>
        <item>Kisses to my bad bitches.</item>
        <item>I remember standing in the mirror, searching for a winner but I didnt see it in her. Now Ive gone from a zero to a super-hero-oh-oh.</item>
        <item>Sometimes you get mad, wanna blaze the gun. I see you without a man, might erase ya son.</item>
        <item>One time for my niggas that be huggin the block. 2 Times for my niggas that be ducking the cops. 3 Times for my girls that pushing they own rides. Stooshing they own rides from bitches they dont like.</item>
        <item>Shout outs to my brothers Jelani and Makiah. Thanks to the Messiah, my money getting higher.</item>
        <item>No matter the squadron, lieutenant or sargeant. Air Force, the army, air force and army fatigues is on em.</item>
        <item>This is for my little homies that be asking for kisses. When Im granting they wishes they be passing they digits.</item>
        <item>I do it for the kids that cant do no more.</item>
        <item>How them girls blow up but dont come to the hood. How they turn they nose up like they dont come from the hood.</item>
        <item>This is for the little girls that say Nicki you pretty. When you come to the city you dont act high for Diddy?</item>
        <item>Chasing dreams got me all over the World. Now Im sitting on top of the World. We winning, we winning. Cause we sitting on top of the World.</item>
        <item>Sniff, sniff, cries, I done slayed your whole entire fucking life. Oh oh, you got some Epson Salt. I done balled all day you aint touched the court.</item>
        <item>I notice that you got it. You notice that I want it. Know that I can take it to the next level baby.</item>
        <item>What, what you tired, you need a break You was hot when? Ricki Lake!</item>
        <item>Anyway Britney, why they so jealous that you teamed up with me. Tell em they my son, yup, gyal em a mi pickney.</item>
        <item>Told you theyd revive your career but somebody lied. I aint talking poultry when I say this chickens fried.</item>
        <item>Chimpanzees is hatin but I take it all in stride. Put her in a jungle with bananas on the side.</item>
        <item>Pray for my enemies, my names still Nicki. In time youll changebut time dont freeze. You better leave better fore you get wetter than iceys?</item>
        <item>You can have my ring, you can add it to your bling. Cause Im ok and Im still a G.</item>
        <item>Nigga you softer than a homosexual and I am so extraterrestrial.</item>
        <item>Is it wrong for thinking that I can trust you? Never holding all this shh against you.</item>
        <item>Yes I did, yes I did, somebody please tell him who the eff I is.</item>
        <item>Nintendo and we in the end zone. I dont give a fuck ho, like we in the friend zone.</item>
        <item>Anyway, Im on that new shit. Every trend, I introduce it. Motherfuck you with a big d*ck.</item>
        <item>Bitches is insane. These bitches aint in my lane. Only bitches in the plane is bitches that give me brain!</item>
        <item>Im a racist, Im a bigot. Bitch, Im thicker than a midget. Yeah Im crazy;&#8230;just a smidgen.</item>
        <item>Starships were meant to fly. Hands up and touch the sky. Can\'t stop cause were so high. Let\'s do this one more time.</item>
        <item>Your favorite rapper prolly suck. As for me? Icy; hockey puck.</item>
        <item>Hold on fuck you. Brace yourself; buck tooth. Yeah I golf; putt too. Swallow balls; nuts toooooooo.</item>
        <item>I can be selfish. Yeah, so impatient. Sometimes I feel like Marilyn Monroe. Im insecure, yeah I make mistakes. Sometimes I feel like Im at the end of the road.</item>
        <item>Witch, twitch, bitch! God, mother\'s right, this is World War 6.</item>
        <item>Im big willie, no bike gear. I told you bitches last year Im a rap bitch nightmare.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="videos">
        <item>2ZCUtnuAXg8|Nicki Minaj - Massive Attack ft. Sean Garrett|Music video by Nicki Minaj performing Massive Attack. &#169; 2010 Cash Money Records Inc.|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/2ZCUtnuAXg8/0.jpg</item>
        <item>pSFyrrhKj1Q|Nicki Minaj - Your Love|Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/pSFyrrhKj1Q/0.jpg</item>
        <item>pqky5B179nM|Nicki Minaj - Check It Out|Music video by will.i.am, Nicki Minaj performing Check It Out. &#169; 2010 Interscope RecordsiTunes UK&#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/pqky5B179nM/0.jpg</item>
        <item>5FJO6b8GL3M|Nicki Minaj - Right Thru Me|Nicki Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/5FJO6b8GL3M/0.jpg</item>
        <item>D7GW8TYCEG4|Nicki Minaj - Moment 4 Life ft. Drake|Nicki Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/D7GW8TYCEG4/0.jpg</item>
        <item>4JipHEz53sU|Nicki Minaj - Super Bass|Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/4JipHEz53sU/0.jpg</item>
        <item>xzXDSWz3Nbw|Nicki Minaj - Did It On Em|Nicki Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/xzXDSWz3Nbw/0.jpg</item>
        <item>3n71KUiWn1I|Nicki Minaj - Fly ft. Rihanna|Nicki Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/3n71KUiWn1I/0.jpg</item>
        <item>T6j4f8cHBIM|Nicki Minaj - Stupid Hoe|Nicki Minaj\'s new album \'Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded\' is out now! Buy it here: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/T6j4f8cHBIM/0.jpg</item>
        <item>KnOSCjfIdaE|Yo Gotti - 5 STAR Remix ft. Gucci Mane, Trina &amp; Nikki Minaj|The official 5 Star Remix!|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/KnOSCjfIdaE/0.jpg</item>
        <item>5i7GEMQC2IY|Mariah Carey - Up Out My Face ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Mariah Carey performing Up Out My Face. &#169; 2010 &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/5i7GEMQC2IY/0.jpg</item>
        <item>JqHliQijgvA|Ludacris - My Chick Bad ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Ludacris performing My Chick Bad. &#169; 2010 DTP Records, LLC|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/JqHliQijgvA/0.jpg</item>
        <item>dNVNzRzDt-k|Usher - Lil Freak ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Usher featuring Nicki Minaj performing Lil Freak. &#169; 2010 &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/dNVNzRzDt-k/0.jpg</item>
        <item>-JGbpVcSyPk|Sean Garrett Ft. Nicki Minaj - Get It All|Sean Garrett goes back to school in the video for \'Get It All\' featuring hip-hop\'s sweetheart Nicki Minaj&#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-JGbpVcSyPk/0.jpg</item>
        <item>OciO2MPnmzU|Diddy - Dirty Money - Hello Good Morning (Remix)|On Tour Now! Music video by Diddy - Dirty Money performing &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/OciO2MPnmzU/0.jpg</item>
        <item>eh8mRjO1nhg|DJ Khaled \'All I Do Is Win\' - Official REMIX video (ft. Nicki Minaj&#8230;)|The official video for DJ Khaled\'s \'All I Do Is Win (Remix)\' Featuring Rick Ross, Busta Rhymes&#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/eh8mRjO1nhg/0.jpg</item>
        <item>ekAXPCphKXQ|Trey Songz - Bottoms Up ft. Nicki Minaj|© 2010 WMG "Passion, Pain &amp; Pleasure" In Stores Now! Get it now!|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/ekAXPCphKXQ/0.jpg</item>
        <item>4uFalk1y38I|Jay Sean - 2012 (It Ain\'t The End) ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Jay Sean performing 2012 (It Ain\'t The End). &#169; 2010 &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/4uFalk1y38I/0.jpg</item>
        <item>jdLAvOMHpqo|Keyshia Cole - I Ain\'t Thru ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Keyshia Cole performing I Ain\'t Thru.|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/jdLAvOMHpqo/0.jpg</item>
        <item>tLPZmPaHme0|The Creep (feat. Nicki Minaj &amp; John Waters)|Buy at iTunes: http://goo.gl/zv4o9. New album on sale now! &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/tLPZmPaHme0/0.jpg</item>
        <item>p4kVWCSzfK4|David Guetta - Where Them Girls At ft. Nicki Minaj&#8230;|Buy David Guetta\'s hit album \'Nothing But the Beat\' &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/p4kVWCSzfK4/0.jpg</item>
        <item>jHgOvf7710k|Birdman - Y.U. MAD ft. Nicki Minaj, Lil Wayne|Music video by Birdman performing Y.U. MAD. &#169; 2011 &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/jHgOvf7710k/0.jpg</item>
        <item>g7AQ7No84Uc|Willow featuring Nicki Minaj - Fireball|Music video by Willow featuring Nicki Minaj performing Fireball. &#169; 2011 Roc Nation, LLC|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/g7AQ7No84Uc/0.jpg</item>
        <item>pn1VGytzXus|Big Sean - Dance (A$$) Remix ft. Nicki Minaj|Music video by Big Sean performing Dance (A$$) Remix. &#169;: Getting Out Our Dreams, Inc. &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/pn1VGytzXus/0.jpg</item>
        <item>EmZvOhHF85I|Nicki Minaj - Beez In The Trap ft. 2 Chainz|Music video by Nicki Minaj performing Beez In The Trap. &#169; 2012 &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/EmZvOhHF85I/0.jpg</item>
        <item>YVw7eJ0vGfM|David Guetta - Turn Me On ft. Nicki Minaj|Download the hit single "Turn Me On" on iTunes: http://goo.gl/VF7QpMusic &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/YVw7eJ0vGfM/0.jpg</item>
        <item>cItHOl5LRWg|Give Me All Your Luvin (Feat. M.I.A. and Nicki Minaj)|Track from Madonna\'s MDNA album. Download it now on iTunes: &#8230;|http://i.ytimg.com/vi/cItHOl5LRWg/0.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>