<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I'm God, I look like Jesus."</item>
		<item>"Give it up one times for the playa hatas, yall motivate me so I gotta thank you."</item>
		<item>"Oh my God I got b*tches."</item>
		<item>"Old friends you grew up with really can't trust em' and the cops is watching you so you really can't bust em'"</item>
		<item>"A lot of people said I would never do it, that's what scares me."</item>
		<item>"Hoes suck my dick cuz' I sing like Ke$ha."</item>
		<item>"Keep ya family close and your based family closer."</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz I look like Jesus."</item>
		<item>"I'm a f-ckin livin legend."</item>
		<item>"Get off the stages, this is my show, my performance, for the ages."</item>
		<item>"I'm that pretty b*tch."</item>
		<item>"25 b*tches on my dick and it's nothin."</item>
		<item>"Let that boy cook."</item>
		<item>"Swag to the maximum."</item>
		<item>"Different color diamonds all the women love me she asked about my job and I told her it was lovely."</item>
		<item>"Every time the earth shake is when you feeling me speak, I dont try to talk to much but the feeling is deep."</item>
		<item>"I look at myself like that goon. The first goon ever to have a baby pink shirt and that respectability."</item>
		<item>"You can have the tiniest pants ever. You can do it in the most square way. You can do it like a nerd or whatever. None of that matters because you can remain you and remain real regardless."</item>
		<item>"You can be thuggin' at heart, but you don't gotta be literally thuggin' in the streets and hurtin' people and doin' shit. But you could be real at the heart."</item>
		<item>"I feel like I'm that new age. Real futuristic grimy shit. But it's like, now niggas will step up to where you're respectably dressed, you're well-mannered, but you're still thuggin'."</item>
		<item>"Do whatever makes you feel comfortable."</item>
		<item>"You can fuck my bitch, it's happy hour."</item>
		<item>"Niggas see me with a SIX FOOT BITCH!"</item>
		<item>"I swear to god, I hit 40 licks. My name LIL B, And I'm not no bitch! When I'm off that dope, I'll rob my bitch!"</item>
		<item>"First I Park My Car....Then I Fuckk Yo Bitch.."</item>
		<item>"I'ma die with 30 bitches on my dick."</item>
		<item>"Bitch I think I'm basedgod with a arc like noah."</item>
		<item>"Knock a bitch head off﻿ my dick like the ocean."</item>
		<item>"20 bitches on my dick tonight, I lied... 100 bitches on my dick!!!! Ahhh fuckkk"</item>
		<item>"Emo hoes on my schlong cuz I make large purchases with coins, southern mistresses on my ass cuz I use a target gift card at walmart"</item>
		<item>"Golddigger whores on my sack cuz my shirt tag irritate me, groupie cunts on my cock cuz I put a dollar in the tip jar n take the rest out."</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz i look like Ray Charles."</item>
		<item>"Ten bitches ride my dick like a school bus."</item>
		<item>"I'm paris hilton woo woo swag."</item>
		<item>"Yeah were gonna be staying on the moon. But there's still gonna be racists...so in the end are we really winning?"</item>
		<item>"About time I said this..... if your not based get the fuck from round me!"</item>
		<item>"Shotgun in the trunk. And its fat like Rick Ross."</item>
		<item>"Damn basedgod you lookin like donald trump. Swagg on a hunid trillion."</item>
		<item>"Oh god damn I got sluts on my ass cuz errytime I dunk a donut I 360 windmill that bitch, whores on my nuts cuz I look like angry beavers."</item>
		<item>"Word around town the I aint got no bitches what thats﻿ a damn lie nigga my nuts is my witness."</item>
		<item>"I'm a fuckin nerd, and I'm fat. Nyeeah I'm a nerd. Calculus, addition, but I don't give a fuck cuz hoes love me, I'm a nerd yeah yeah yeah."</item>
		<item>"Bet I'll bubble up like the dopeman rock, bet I make crack like the dopeman pot."</item>
		<item>"I been crossed over, I'm the Answer, YOU DIG ME?!"</item>
		<item>"Bullets spread ova ya body fast like cancer, now you in tha sky like pisces and cancers."</item>
		<item>"The glock leave ya head stuck to walls like a poster."</item>
		<item>"Come on my court, jumpshot with the hookey. come on my court, you gettin punched like Snookie."</item>
		<item>"Bet I'm the only goon nigga in these tiny pants."</item>
		<item>"Then I realize the power...of jacking off every hour."</item>
		<item>"What are you gonna do when the lions eat you?!"</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz i look like rice milk, girls suck my nuts cuz i look like the goon pope, thugged out bitch and i look like jersey"</item>
		<item>"Girls on my dick cuz i look like a baby goon, milk on my nuts cuz the girls look hungry, Young BasedGod got girls in cages, suck my nuts ho."</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz i payed for the butt-cheeks, girls on my nuts look i look like whole wheat, baby nuts brandon came with the gloc 10."</item>
		<item>"Told my main bitch that she worthless, spanked her. Ask my main bitch if she hungry, spanked her."</item>
		<item>"Hoes suck my dick cause I'm white like Asher Roth."</item>
		<item>"Tiny jean nigga and i comes with that choppa, bitches on my dick cuz i look like they FATHER."</item>
		<item>"Ladies, if you saw me jackin off in a ferrari would you be jealous?"</item>
		<item>"Iced out chain lookin like Sonny Liston, knock ya ass out with the 3-D vision."</item>
		<item>"Glock 10 ill have you lookin like cousin skeeter."</item>
		<item>"Bulletproof vest purple jeans lookin fru-tay."</item>
		<item>"These tiny pants are amazing to me."</item>
		<item>"He who walks his own path of greatness will never be ancient."</item>
		<item>"Went to the mall with my dikin' ass bitch, she a faggot bitch, but she still suck my dick."</item>
		<item>"Word around town is that I'm finer than my bitch."</item>
		<item>"Young Based God and my nuts look like raisins."</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz I look like matlock."</item>
		<item>"Pure devotion, Hip Hop, is on my skin like lotion."</item>
		<item>"Swag! Swag! Swag!"</item>
		<item>"Woop woop woop."</item>
		<item>"No i aint no bitch....a few bars later....i'm a pretty bitch."</item>
		<item>"I'm so wet her pussy get mad at me."</item>
		<item>"Hoes on my dick cuz I smell like squidward."</item>
		<item>"Cracked a hot sauce bottle in my ass and made a bitch suck it out wooh wooh."</item>
		<item>"Fuck a maserati I pull up in a minvan swaggin like a mommy."</item>
		<item>"I pull up to the club smellin like gym socks and mashed potatoes."</item>
		<item>"11, 10, 12, 30, 16, i'm on these bitches."</item>
		<item>"Oh my god we're in Japan."</item>
		<item>"I can't smoke a bitch, so I'm smokin Mary Jane."</item>
		<item>"We're in England now."</item>
		<item>"I'm soo marvelous, And soo happy cuz she suckin me like Artemis."</item>
		<item>"I'm not Drake I ain't come in the game rich, Fuck you if you don't feel﻿ my game bitch!"</item>
		<item>"Word around town that you still hate my dick."</item>
		<item>"My bruh got grapes in Palo Alto."</item>
		<item>"Shouts out to Palo Alto, bruh bruh got grapes there."</item>
		<item>"Mainstream: dick suck, Underground: no cash"</item>
		<item>"Young Basedgod never fed my bitch sushi, bitch kiss my ring cuz im Kristi Yamaguchi."</item>
		<item>"Shouts out man I got some of the best scarves."</item>
		<item>"Won't Suck my dick? that's a first, your a fagggggooott."</item>
		<item>"Picked up my bitches, most of them foreign, hoes suck my dick when my day gets boring."</item>
		<item>"Nut on her lips and in her ass thats a creampie. Oh my God creampie."</item>
		<item>"I'm doin it for the youth, tryna set the right example feel me."</item>
		<item>"I'm livin in the world where the sun wanna kiss me."</item>
		<item>"Bitches suck my dick cuz I look like a Frenchmen."</item>
		<item>"Word around town bitch imma nasty neighbor."</item>
		<item>"I'm really waterfront on a bitch!"</item>
		<item>"The only time i went to class was when i was serving a detention."</item>
		<item>"Swag like I'm marrow, in my bones. Swag in my bones. Bone Marrow Swag."</item>
		<item>"My white girl fuck me good, interracial datin. My black girl suck my dick and she on probation."</item>
		<item>"Feel me im in this bitch , man lookin like heidi montag swaggin."</item>
		<item>"Mansion looking like fruity pebbles, and Crisco."</item>
		<item>"I'm so wet I should be in the Navy."</item>
		<item>"Yeah the niqqa rap but do he got bitches? Young Baselord and I look like Jesus."</item>
		<item>"Fucked the bitch in her ass and the pussy squirted milk."</item>
		<item>"Roll with the piece beside him not talkin bout the gun, but the peace inside him."</item>
		<item>"Everybody say that I'm a young ass bitch til I caught my first case now I'm a thug ass bitch."</item>
		<item>"10 on my dick cuz I look like patrick ramsey."</item>
		<item>"I won't eat a girl out, but my lawyers will!"</item>
		<item>"Hoes suck my dick, and my dick touch her brain."</item>
		<item>"Dirty everythang. You can't be half ass dirty you gotta be all the way, ya feel me?"</item>
		<item>"The mind is so complex when your based. 32 levels. Welcome to my world."</item>
		<item>"Yeah drake I fuckin feel ya, I was in the hood while you were shopping at whole foods."</item>
		<item>"I'm just robbing like baskins."</item>
		<item>"Put money on god and bust on him."</item>
		<item>"20 on my dick because I look like Miss America."</item>
		<item>"She was like OWWW, I was like OWW, i am like GOD, call me Based god!"</item>
		<item>"My people, you gota think before you move, you gota speak before you cry, you gota live before you die."</item>
		<item>"I'm not guna let anything take the love from my heart, the love of life and spreading peace and positive, thank you earth I'm alive."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
