<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Some women choose to follow men, and some women choose to follow their dreams. If you're wondering which way to go, remember that your career will never wake up and tell you that it doesn't love you anymore."</item>
	<item>"Peace. it does not mean to be in a place where there is no trouble, noise, or hard work. it means to be in the midst of those things and still be calm in your heart."</item>
	<item>"Trust is like a mirror, you can fix it if it's broken, but you can still see the crack in that mother fucker's reflection."</item>
	<item>"You have to be unique, and different, and shine in your own way."</item>
	<item>"They can't scare me, if I scare them first."</item>
	<item>"Well, that's your opinion, isn't it? And I'm not about to waste my time trying to change it."</item>
	<item>"... I want the deepest, darkest, sickest parts of you that you are afraid to share with anyone because I love you that much."</item>
	<item>"Love is like a brick. You can build a house, or you can sink a dead body."</item>
	<item>"And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time."</item>
	<item>"I'm a free bitch baby"</item>
	<item>"I remember watching the mascara tears flood the ivories and I thought, \"It's OK to be sad.\" I've been trained to love my darkness."</item>
	<item>"When you make music or write or create, it's really your job to have mind-blowing, irresponsible, condomless sex with whatever idea it is you're writing about at the time."</item>
	<item>"Cause it's a hard life, with love in the world. and i'm a hard girl, loving me is like chewing on pearls."</item>
	<item>"I used to walk down the street like I was a fucking star... I want people to walk around delusional about how great they can be - and then to fight so hard for it every day that the lie becomes the truth."</item>
	<item>"Do not allow people to dim your shine because they are blinded. Tell them to put on some sunglasses, cuz we were born this way bitch!"</item>
	<item>"I had a boyfriend who told me I’d never succeed, never be nominated for a Grammy, never have a hit song, and that he hoped I’d fail. I said to him: Someday, when we’re not together, you won’t be able to order a cup of coffee at the fucking deli without hearing or seeing me."</item>
	<item>"I'm obsessively opposed to the typical."</item>
	<item>"All that ever holds somebody back, I think, is fear. For a minute I had fear. [Then] I went into the [dressing] room and shot my fear in the face..."</item>
	<item>"Don't you ever let a soul in the world tell you that you can't be exactly who you are."</item>
	<item>"Once you kill a cow, you gotta make a burger."</item>
	<item>"I want women -- and men -- to feel empowered by a deeper and more psychotic part of themselves. The part they're always trying desperately to hide. I want that to become something that they cherish."</item>
	<item>"Sometimes in life you don't always feel like a winner, but that doesn't mean you're not a winner, you want to be like yourself. I want my fans to know it's okay."</item>
	<item>"You're love is nothing I can't fight. Can't sleep with a man who dims my shine."</item>
	<item>"People will always talk, so lets give them sumthin to talk about."</item>
	<item>"I'm already crazy. I'm a fearless person. I think it creeps up on you. I don't think it can be stopped. If my destiny is to lose my mind because of fame, then that's my destiny. But my passion still means more than anything."</item>
	<item>"live your eyeliner, breathe your lipstick, and kill for each other"</item>
	<item>"If you dont have any shadows you're not in the light."</item>
	<item>"I just I felt like a freak, I guess what I'm trying to say is I want to liberate them, I want to free them of their fears and make them feel that they can create their own space in the world."</item>
	<item>"As artists, we are eternally heartbroken."</item>
	<item>"I'm beautiful in my way, 'cause God makes no mistakes. I'm on the right track, baby. I was Born This Way."</item>
	<item>"Just dance — it's gonna be okay."</item>
	<item>"Well my music was different in high school; I was singing about love—you know, things I don't care about anymore."</item>
	<item>"Sexuality is half poison and half liberation. What’s the line? I don’t have a line."</item>
	<item>"I'm telling you a lie in a vicious effort that you will repeat my lie over and over until it becomes true."</item>
	<item>"We're plastic, but we still have fun."</item>
	<item>"Do you know the feeling,when your heart is so hurt,that you could feel the blood dripping?"</item>
	<item>"I am focused on the work. I am constantly creating. I am a busy girl. I live and breathe my work. I love what I do. I believe in the message. There's no stopping. I didn't create the fame, the fame created me."</item>
	<item>"Prom girl wipes her tears with silver lines."</item>
	<item>"I don't want the 5 dollars in your pocket, I want your soul."</item>
	<item>"To everyone who says this is wrong to feel like this say, 'I was born this way baby."</item>
	<item>"My friends joke that I’m dead until I get onstage. I’m dead right now as you’re speaking to me."</item>
	<item>"I want you to walk out of her tonight not loving me more, but loving yourselves more."</item> 
	<item>"I've always been famous, it's just no one knew it yet."</item>
	<item>"When I wake up in the morning, I feel like any other insecure 24-year-old girl. Then I say,'Bitch, you're Lady Gaga, you get up and walk the walk today."</item>
	<item>"Some women choose to follow men, and some women choose to follow their dreams. If you're wondering which way to go, remember that your career will never wake up and tell you that it doesn't love you anymore."</item>
	<item>"I used to walk down the street like I was a star. I want people to walk around delusional about how great they can be - and then to fight so hard for it that the lie becomes the truth."</item>
	<item>"I'm a little bit naked, but that's okay."</item>
	<item>"I'd wear any of my private attire for the world to see. But I would rather have an open flesh wound than ever wear a band aid in public."</item>
	<item>"For all my love little monsters i am your mom you are my child in my hand i protect you like my eyes but dont worry ill cacth you if you fall."</item>
	<item>"I would rather die than have my fans see me without a pair of heels on. And that's show business."</item>
	<item>"So many will try to destroy me. So many, over and over, coming in periods of greatness. But in this period, I cannot be broken: GAGAKLEIN."</item>
	<item>"My new album that I'm creating, which is finished pretty much, was written with this new instinctual energy that I've developed getting to know my fans. They protect me, so now it's my destiny to protect them."</item>
	<item>"That's Right Hunny-B."</item>
	<item>"I am beautiful in my own way, 'Cause God makes no mistakes. I'm on the right track, baby, I was born this way."</item>
	<item>"pppppoker face ppppoker face"</item>
	<item>"We are not just Art for Michelangelo to carve, he can't rewrite the agro of my furied heart."</item>
	<item>"Prejudice is a disease. And when they come for you, or refuse your worth, I will be ready for their stones. I belong to you. GAGAKLEIN."</item>
	<item>"Stop calling! Stop calling! I don't want to talk any more!"</item>
	<item>"Just remember: i love you, and love yourselves. 'cause, little monsters, you were born that way baby."</item>
	<item>"Trust is like a mirror. You can fix it if it's broken, but you can still see the crack in its reflection."</item>
	<item>"A middle finger is more New York than a corporate ambush. I bleed for my hometown, and I'd die for my fans."</item>
	<item>"The Monster Ball is by nature a protest: A youth church experience to speak out and celebrate against all forms of discrimination + prejudice."</item>
	<item>"Being gay is like glitter, it never goes away."</item>
	<item>"Dont be a drag just be a queen... baby i was born this way!"</item>
	<item>"How can I protect something so perfect without evil..."</item>
	<item>"A different lover is not a sin..."</item>
	<item>"Love is like a mirror. You can fix it when it’s broken. That is true. But you can still see the crack in the motherfucking reflection."</item>
	<item>"This is who the fuck I am."</item>

</string-array>
</resources>
