<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"At first everybody was submitting really tacky songs, … Like \"miaow, miaow\"… stuff about pussy power, bad kitties."</item>
	<item>"When I think about eighteen months ago when this all began and how far we’ve come, I can’t wait to see where we are eighteen months from now. It’s also such an honor to have the baton of a number one song passed to us by an icon like Mariah Carey."</item>
	<item>"We’re very sensitive about what we do, or don’t do. We’re sassy and classy."</item>
	<item>"The word feminism has negative connotations for men. Rather, we are wanting to celebrate females and their confidence. There is no political agenda behind my work. I’m just trying to make music that makes me feel good and confident. We’ve got a cool message."</item>
	<item>"We’re on a wave, … And we’re going to ride it as long as we can."</item>
	<item>"All I could say was, Go get our album. And God bless you."</item>
	<item>"We don’t take ourselves too seriously. I don’t think we’re trying to be anything that we’re not. We’re not, like, trying to reinvent the wheel or anything."</item>
	<item>"A lot of time we didn’t know where we were going or how it was going to transition from fishnets into hip-hop. But it’s worked out. We believe in what we do and I think people get that."</item>
	<item>"It just seemed fitting to have our own lounge with our own dance review that paid homage to where The Pussycat Dolls originated, … So it wasn’t just another nightclub."</item>
	<item>"It was somewhere where people can go and see an old school show with real dancing and real performing and real singing. It’s perfect for Vegas. It’s got that whole cabaret, burlesque-inspired review of dancing, and the whole fishnets, and boas."</item>
	<item>"Will was a big fan of the message of the song. He was just the perfect person to work with."</item>
	<item>"Once you stay true to just having a good time and being honest to your fans and your audience, you can`t go wrong. "</item>
	<item>"To me, a Pussycat Doll is fearless but also vulnerable. We're strong, but we like to play too."</item>
	<item>"I want to bring awareness to how special people with Down syndrome are... I used to tell my girls in the Pussycat Dolls that I would have my own musical camp or school where I would teach people with special disabilities or Down syndrome."</item>
	<item>"It was wretchedly hot, But you gotta do what you gotta do — you’ve got to hustle and grind."</item>
	<item>"The guy who marries me is going to be with me for ever because I’m very traditional. There’s no rush. I just want to make sure it’s the right time for everything. And I’m also really married to my work. It takes up all of my time!"</item>
	<item>"I’ve tried every diet out there and they don’t work, because eventually the diet ends and I want the foods that I restrain myself from eating."</item>
	<item>"It’s about having everything in moderation as long as you’re staying active. I also try not to eat late at night, not after 7pm if I can help it."</item>
	<item>"Lewis is always telling me that I`d be a really good mum and I know he`d be a great dad."</item>
	<item>"We had our time. Some of the girls left the group. That was out of my hands. I wouldn`t want to be in a group with other girls -- we were like a tight family."</item>
	<item>"I’m looking forward to getting together and having some quiet prayer meetings with Britney."</item>
	<item>"Dancing is another way to communicate. That`s what separates Pussycat Dolls from other groups."</item>
	<item>"Once you stay true to just having a good time and being honest to your fans and your audience, you can`t go wrong."</item>
	<item>"Stay true to who you are. Keep the faith. Be yourself, and love yourself."</item>
	<item>"If I really get into acting, I'm not going be that girl in the bathing suit who steals the guy. That's not me. I'd rather play the nerdy girl. I'm the biggest nerd I know."</item>
	<item>"We're on a wave ... And we're going to ride it as long as we can."</item>
	<item>"I knew by the people who were involved, the machine behind it, that this was going to be something."</item>
	<item>"I could have been the best dancing toothbrush ever..."</item>
	<item>"I think it's a very different sound to GaGa - the music is a lot more raw, soulful and funk-inspired. I'm a different artist and I have a different energy. It's a mini thriller, it's so in your face and strong."</item>
	<item>"I know this sounds cheesy, but the first thing that comes to mind is world peace. It's always in the back of my head. I mean, what could you say? I want a really hot car, but how far would it take you?"</item>
	<item>"I really would love to do a romantic comedy because I am pretty much the nerdiest, goofiest girl you have ever met. I think having a sense of humor is the hottest thing. I love Will Ferrell. I am such a huge fan of his. I think he is wonderful."</item>
	<item>"The word feminism has negative connotations for men. Rather, we are wanting to celebrate females and their confidence. There is no political agenda behind my work. I'm just trying to make music that makes me feel good and confident. We've got a cool message."</item>
	<item>"It was like a train and it was moving fast and people had to jump on board -- it`s been crazy, ... When you`re in the Top Ten, you never dream of being No. 1. Eventually, not with your first debut song. When our song hit No. 1, it was like, Is this real? Are you guys kidding me?"</item>
	
</string-array>
</resources>
