<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll was born on February 2nd 1977, in Columbia. "</item>
	<item>"She's Catholic by religion, and speaks three languages: Spanish, Portuguese, and English."</item>
	<item>"Shakira has eight older siblings from her Italian father's first marriage, and her mother is Lebanese. "</item>
	<item>"Her father was a writer, who crafted a story for her as a Christmas gift when she was seven years old."</item>
	<item>"Shakira means in Hindi, Goddess Of Light and in Arabic, Woman Full Of Grace."</item>
	<item>"Since becoming rich and famous, Shakira has created the Bare Feet Foundation. The charity builds schools for poor children in her home country."</item>
	<item>"She's a regular performer at benefit concerts and other community building and charitable events."</item>
	<item>"A talented tot, Shakira began belly dancing after her father took her to a restaurant and she entertained the other diners with her antics."</item>
	<item>"She won a kids' singing competition called \"Vinan Los Niños\". But the music teacher in charge of the school choir rejected her, saying she sounded \"like a goat\"."</item>
	<item>"Shakira recorded her first album, Magia, in 1990 when she was only 13 years old. Despite her Lolita belly dancing moves, it was a belly flop, as was her second."</item>
	<item>"But she hit the big time in Columbia with her own sound on her third record, Pies Descalzos (Bare Feet) and became a huge latin star with 1998's Dónde Están los Ladrones? (Where are the thieves?)."</item>
	<item>"Her papa went bankrupt when she was a young girl. But when she acted like the world had ended, he showed her street kids living even harder, and she realised she was actually lucky."</item>
	<item>"She made the cover of Time magazine in the article about the Latin American wave conquering the world, titled \"Era of the Rockera\"."</item>
	<item>"Success in the English-speaking world followed, after she dyed her hair blonde and released Laundry Service together with a sexy music video for the hit single, \"Whenever, Wherever\"."</item>
	<item>"\"Hips Don't Lie\" is the biggest US hit of the 21st century - so far."</item>
	<item>"Shakira regularly appears in US men's magazine \"Hottest women\" lists."</item>
	<item>"But though she's famous for her hip-shaking dance moves and her sexy lyrics, Shakira claims to be a shy girl, who's not at all like the siren in her music videos."</item>
	<item>"At some point, she fired her style and beauty staff. The reason? She felt she was becoming too obsessed with the way she looked, and also decided against breast augmentation."</item>
	<item>"She' s literally a \"shorty\", standing only 1.57m tall in her socks... and we'll give you a minute to get that image out of your mind, boys and girls..."</item>
	<item>"She loves chocolate balls. But she has very few real vices – or so it seems. She doesn't drink booze, or even coffee."</item>
	<item>"Although she claims to dislike wearing jewellery, she's apparently a fan of ring collecting, and owns more than 200 of the finger-trinkets."</item>
	<item>"She's won two Grammy awards, and another three Latin Grammy awards, so far. And you could say she's earned every one - she writes most of her own songs."</item>
	<item>"Her most recent album, She Wolf has taken a much more dance-pop direction."</item>
	<item>"Heavily influenced by Arabic writings of Lebanese father, who was a jeweler and writer."</item>
	<item>"Shakira sings the Official Song for the 2010 FIFA World Cup: Waka Waka - This Time For Africa, with local legends Freshlyground."</item>
	<item>"She also recorded a \"Bamboo\" version of her huge \"Hips Don't Lie\" for the 2006 Fifa World Cup."</item>
	<item>"Announced engagement to Antonio de la Rua, son of the present President of Argentina. [March 2001]"</item>
	<item>"She is of Colombian and Lebanese heritage."</item>
	<item>"She named her album \"Laundry Service\" because when she is in love she feels \"clean and fresh\"."</item>
	<item>"She has an IQ of 140!"</item>
	<item>"Her Lebanese grandmother taught her the art of Arabian Belly Dancing so she can stay true to her middle eastern roots."</item>
	<item>"Has perfect pitch (the ability to recognize any note upon hearing it or sing any note without prior to hearing it)"</item>
	<item>"Her manager for Latin America, Patricia Tellez, the woman who helped her go from being local artist to Grammy-winning global artist, died of a heart attack in Bogota on 17 August 2004."</item>
	<item>"Father's name is William Mebarak Chadid and mother's name is Nidia del Carmen Ripolli Torrado."</item>
	<item>"Her mother is half Colombian and half Italian and her father is American with Lebanese ancestry."</item>
	<item>"She has 5 half brothers Alberto, Edward, Moises, Tonino and Robin and 3 half sisters Ana, Lucy and Patricia."</item>
	<item>"Steven Spielberg offered her the role of Elena Montero in The Mask of Zorro (1998) back when he was originally in talks to direct it. But she turned the offer down."</item>
	<item>"When she was two years old her oldest half-brother died in an accident while he was riding a motorcycle and a drunk man hit him with his car."</item>
	<item>"The first English song she wrote was Objection, from the album Laundry Service."</item>
	<item>"She loves to eat corozos, a little Colombian fruit that is sweet-sour."</item>
	<item>"Lost her suitcase with all her songs from Donde Estan Los Ladrones in an airport in Bogota Colombia. This happened a couple of months before she walked into the recording studio to begin on that album."</item>
	<item>"Mattel put out several Barbie dolls inspired by Shakira and her look."</item> 
	<item>"Her album \"Fijacion Oral Vol.1\" is #1 on the Billboard Latin Albums Chart in September 2005."</item>
	<item>"Attended La Ensenanza School in Barranquilla."</item>
	<item>"Emerged victorious in local and national talent contests by age of 10."</item>
	<item>"Signed Sony record deal by age 13; subsequently released debut CD \"Magia (Magic)\"."</item>
	<item>"Graduated from high school at age 15."</item>
	<item>"Breakthrough recording: \"Pies Descalzos\" sold four million copies worldwide."</item>
	<item>"Appeared on cover of Time Magazine's \"Era of the Rockera\" issue."</item>
	<item>"Earned honor of Latin Female Artist of the Year at World Music Awards in Monaco, 2001."</item>
	<item>"Became the youngest ever goodwill ambassador for the United Nations UNICEF on October 24, 2003 "</item>
	<item>"Donated 10,000 pairs of tennis shoes to her hometown of Barranquilla to impoverished children."</item>
	<item>"Shakira is a walking, living, breathing, singing contradiction."</item>
	<item>"She's a perfectionist who spends hours in the studio, she needs to be close to nature but her passion is the crackle of electric guitars."</item>
	<item>"Made emergency helicopter landing. Bad weather forces the singer's chopper down over a baseball diamond in the Dominican Republic on Friday, August 2, 2002. She and family escaped injury."</item>
	<item>"Lists John Lennon as her #1 musical influence."</item>
	<item>"She admires Gloria Estefan."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite band is U2."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite Latin band is Soda Stereo."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite actor is Hugh Grant."</item>
	<item>"Her favourite color is black."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite flowers are daisy and sunflower."</item>
	<item>"Her favorite kind of music is merengue."</item>
	<item>"Her dream wedding is to dress in white and hold the ceremony on a beach."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer will be designing a fashion line for animals."</item>
	<item>"In July 2008 Shakira signed a prestigious $70 million contract with Live Nation including recording, touring, merchandising, and other rights."</item>
	<item>"In 2006 a 4.5m (14' 8") tall and five-ton (10,000 pounds) heavy giant metal statue of Shakira has been put up on the central square of her hometown Barranquilla, Colombia."</item>
	<item>"Shakira participated in a poetic social mission Moving Stars and Earth for Water, reading a poem by novelist Yann Martel, along with 14 other artists, for the organization onedrop.org, which raises awareness for preserving water in the world."</item>
	<item>"She was considered as one by LA Times as one of the most sucessful and charismatic people on the planet."</item>
	<item>"Together with Red Hot Chili Peppers Shakira was the most nominated artist for the 2006 MTV Video Music Awards and both received seven nominations, but she won only the prize for best choreography."</item>
	<item>"Alejandro Sanz and Shakira became the first Latin duet to performed live at the MTV Awards Ceremony in Miami."</item>
	<item>"Shakira's car accidentally crash over a fan and a security guard after a concert in Texas."</item>
	<item>"After the release of her album Peligro, she decided to take a hiatus from recording so that she could graduate from high school."</item>
	<item>"Her first album Magia did not fare well commercially as less than one thousand copies were sold."</item>
	<item>"On April 3, 2006, Shakira was honored at an United Nations ceremony because she created the Pies Descalzos Foundation, a charity that helps to protect children from violence in Colombia."</item>
	<item>"In June 2006, Shakira started her biggest tour ever, called the Oral Fixation Tour, which will lasted until the summer of 2007."</item>
	<item>"In 2002, emails were circulating about a supposed interview of MTV Europe where she said that Israelis and Jews were \"pigs\". This has never been confirmed."</item>
	<item>"Her tour around Latin America began on August 1st 2006 in Mexico City, and officially started on September 30th 2006. She has said that the tour is one of the most important in her career."</item>
	<item>"Her rendition of the Flores song Amor has become a collectors' item because of its rarity."</item>
	<item>"Shakira was the mystery singer on Al Compás de un Sentimiento, a television special produced by the Banco Popular de Puerto Rico in 1996 which featured the music of Puerto Rican composer Pedro Flores."</item>
	<item>"She was once concerned about the size of her breasts, but finally decided against having plastic surgery, insisting that she is happy being natural."</item>
	<item>"She does not think of herself as a feminist, just that she is a strong woman with masculine qualities."</item>
	<item>"She is to become the first pop star to release a single only as a mobile-phone download."</item>
	<item>"Shakira states that both she and Wyclef Jean dream about each other, and as soon as they contacted each other they began making the video for Hips Don't Lie."</item>
	<item>"Her cousin is fashion designer and Miss Colombia 2006, Valerie Dominguez Tarud."</item>
	<item>"Her album Fijacion Oral Vol.1 was #1 on the Billboard Latin Albums Chart in September 2005."</item>
	<item>"Her nickname is Shaki."</item>
	<item>"Her first UK released singles from the album Laundry Service, which sold 13 million copies worldwide and was Shakira's most selling album, include: Whenever Wherever, Underneath Your Clothes and Objection."</item>

</string-array>
</resources>
