<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I know I'm talented, but I wasn't put here to sing. I was put here to be a wife and a mom and look after my family. I love what I do, but it's not where it begins and ends."</item>
		<item>"We're not planning a honeymoon. Every day is a honeymoon – I've married the best man in the world."</item>
		<item>"I’m not a fighter, but if I am backed up against the wall I’ll kick the shit out of anyone."</item>
		<item>"I don’t think your ability to fight has anything to do with how big you are. It’s to do with how much anger is in you."</item>
		<item>"I'm of the school of thought where, if you can't sort something out for yourself, no one can help you. Rehab is great for some people but not others."</item>
		<item>"My justification is that most people my age spend a lot of time thinking about what they’re going to do for the next five or ten years. The time they spend thinking about their life, I just spend drinking."</item>
		<item>"I’m either a really good drunk or I’m an out-and-out sh*t, horrible, violent, abusive, emotional drunk."</item>
		<item>"(on the pain of getting her 13 tattoos) It's a way of suffering for the things that mean a lot to you."</item>
		<item>"It's a funny thing, a morbid curiosity. I'm talking about when I was nine. What does that feel like? 'Ow, that f***ing hurts.' It's probably the worst thing I've done."</item>
		<item>"Girls talk to each other like men talk to each other. But girls have an eye for detail."</item>
		<item>"After Frank I didn’t write for 18 months but when I met Mark (Ronson) I pretty much wrote the album in six months — he was so inspiring."</item>
		<item>"My first kiss was about 11 or 12 and it was with a Greek boy called Chris. .... who's gay now!"</item>
		<item>"I like pin-up girls. I’m more of a boy than a girl. I’m not a lesbian, though — not before a sambuca anyway."</item>
		<item>"(About her health) A little bit of anorexia, a little bit of bulimia. I'm not totally okay now but I don't think any woman is."</item>
		<item>"I have a really good time some nights, but then I push it over the edge and ruin my boyfriend’s night. I’m an ugly dickhead drunk, I really am."</item>
		<item>"I don't listen to anyone except my ... inner child anyway. If someone had said to me, Amy, lose a stone - which they wouldn't - I don't think I would have listened anyway."</item>
		<item>"I can’t even listen to Frank any more... In fact, I’ve never been able to. I like playing the tracks live because that’s different but listening to them is another story."</item>
		<item>"(about cocktail Rickstasy) By the time you’ve had two of them you’re like, don’t even try and go anywhere. Sit down and stay down, until the birds start singing."</item>
		<item>"We only said goodbye with words, I died a hundred times. You go back to her and I go back to... I go back to us."</item>
		<item>"We're not planning a honeymoon. Every day is a honeymoon - I've married the best man in the world."</item>
		<item>"I'm not a fighter, but if I am backed up against the wall I'll kick the shit out of anyone."</item>
		<item>"Girls talk to each other like men talk to each other. But girls have an eye for detail."</item>
		<item>"I don't think your ability to fight has anything to do with how big you are. It's to do with how much anger is in you."</item>
		<item>"I like pin-up girls. I'm more of a boy than a girl. I'm not a lesbian, though - not before a sambuca anyway."</item>
		<item>"I'm either a really good drunk or I'm an out and out shit, horrible, violent, abusive, emotional drunk."</item>
		<item>"After Frank I didn't write for 18 months but when I met Mark (Ronson) I pretty much wrote the album in six months - he was so inspiring."</item>
		<item>"I have a really good time some nights, but then I push it over the edge and ruin my boyfriend's night. I'm an ugly dickhead drunk, I really am."</item>
		<item>"They tried to make me go to rehab I said no no no."</item>
		<item>"You went back to what you knew, so far removed from all that we went through. And I tread a troubled track, my odds are stacked. I'll go back to black."</item>
		<item>"I'm of the school of thought where, if you can't sort something out for yourself, no one can help you. Rehab is great for some people but not others."</item>
		<item>"I can't even listen to Frank any more... In fact, I've never been able to. I like playing the tracks live because that's different but listening to them is another story."</item>
		<item>"I don't ever wanna drink again. I just, ooh, I just need a friend."</item>
		<item>"I love you much, it's not enough. You love blow and I love puff, and life is like a pipe ."</item>
		<item>"For you I was a flame, love is a losing game. Five story fire as you came, love is a losing game."</item>
		<item>"If I go to the gym and I have a drink, I'm lovely to be around and really sweet."</item>
		<item>"Played out by the band, love is a losing hand. More than I could stand, love is a losing hand."</item>
		<item>"Drinking long-term is a lot worse than doing heroin. Alcohol's a real poison."</item>
		<item>"Self professed, profound till the chips were down. Know you're a gambling man, love is a losing hand."</item>
		<item>"I cheated myself, like I knew I would. I told you I was trouble. You know that I'm no good."</item>
		<item>"When will we get the time to be just friends. It's never safe for us not even in the evening 'cos I've been drinking."</item>
		<item>"There are certain instances where I'll be out and I'll be drunk, and I'll come to work and I'll be shattered."</item>
		<item>"I don’t listen to anyone except my . . . inner child anyway."</item>
		<item>"I just dress like… I’m an old black man. Sorry! Like I’m an old Jewish black man. I just dress like it’s still the ’50s."</item>
		<item>"People don’t change their behavior unless it makes a difference for them to do so."</item>
		<item>"I’m of the school of thought where, if you can’t sort something out for yourself, no one can help you. Rehab is great for some people but not others."</item>
		<item>"Since I was 16, I’ve felt a black cloud hangs over me. Since then, I have taken pills for depression. "</item>
		<item>"Having listened to great songwriters like James Taylor and Carole King, I felt there was nothing new that was coming out that really represented me and the way I felt. So I started writing my own stuff."</item>
		<item>"If you act like you know what you’re doing, you can do anything you want."</item>
		<item>"If I died tomorrow, I would be a happy girl."</item>
		<item>"I wouldn't want it to be all roses because life isn't like that. "</item>
		<item>"About Christina Aguilera: She’s a talented girl — but you couldn’t really see it until she was wearing those chaps with her ninny hanging out."</item>
		<item>"A little bit of anorexia, a little bit of bulimia. I'm not totally OK now but I don't think any woman is."</item>
		<item>"Even if I stop wanting you a perspective pushes through and I'll be some next man's other woman soon."</item>
		<item>"For you I was a flame, love is a losing game."</item>
		<item>"Why can't he see? How blind can he be? Someday he'll see that he was meant for me."</item>
		<item>"I'll be good to him, I'll bring joy to him."</item>
		<item>"Just to see that smile, makes my life worthwhile."</item>
		<item>"To know know know him is to love love love him."</item>
		<item>"I was on my way to Banbury Cross, then I see a monkey upon a white horse."</item>
		<item>"Now I know that, now I understand."</item>
		<item>"I never saw you, I only heard of you."</item>
		<item>"Now cupid if your arrow makes his love strong for me, I swear I'm gonna love him until eternity."</item>
		<item>"Hey cupid cupid I'm calling.. Don't you hear me I'm calling you?"</item>
		<item>"Listen, I don't want to bother you but I'm in distress. there's danger of me loosing all of my happiness."</item>
		<item>"Cupid please hear my cry and let your arrow fly straight to my lover's heart for me."</item>
		<item>"Cupid draw back your bow and let your arrow flow."</item>
		<item>"I think of all the things, what you're doing and in my head I paint a picture."</item>
		<item>"I hope you didn't catch a tan, I hope you find the right man who'll fix it for you."</item>
		<item>"Stop making a fool out of me, Why don't you come on over?"</item>
		<item>"Don't make no difference if I end up alone, I'd rather have myself a smoke my homegrown."</item>
		<item>"I'm my own man so when will you learn that you got a man but I got to burn."</item>
		<item>"Tell your boyfriend next time he around to buy his own weed and don't wear my shit down."</item>
		<item>"The miss misses the man that he belongs to be."</item>
		<item>"Though he tries to pacify her, whats inside her never dies."</item>
		<item>"How can he have her heart when it got stole?"</item>
		<item>"She's so vacant her soul is taken, he is what she's running from."</item>
		<item>"He can only hold her for so long."</item>
		<item>"He still stands in spite of what his scars say.. I'll battle till this bitter finale just me, my dignity and this guitar case."</item>
		<item>"It's you I'm fighting for, he can't lose with me in tow . I refuse to let him go."</item>
		<item>"I stand before him, It's all I can do to assure him."</item>
		<item>"This ache in my chest as my day is done now, the dark covers me and I cannot run now."</item>
		<item>"If I was my heart I'd rather be restless."</item>
		<item>"Moon spilling in and I wake up alone.."</item>
		<item>"This face in my dreams seizes my guts, he floods me with dread."</item>
		<item>"That silent sense of content that everyone gets just disappears soon as the sun sets."</item>
		<item>"Got so sick of crying so just lately, when I catch myself I do a 180."</item>
		<item>"It's okay in the day I'm staying busy.. Tied up enough so I don't have to wonder where is he."</item>
		<item>"I wish I could say no regrets and no emotional debts."</item>
		<item>"So we are history, your shadow covers me."</item>
		<item>"I shouldn't play myself again, I should just be my own best friend."</item>
		<item>"I don't understand why do I stress a man."</item>
		<item>"And in this grey, in this blue shade my tears dry on their own."</item>
		<item>"He walks away, the sun goes down."</item>
		<item>"I don't know why I got so attached, It's my responsibility and you don't owe nothing to me but to walk away I have no capacity."</item>
		<item>"All I can ever be to you is a darkness that we knew and this regret I had to get accustomed to."</item>
		<item>"Memories mar my mind, love is a fate resigned."</item>
		<item>"Love is a losing hand more than I could stand."</item>
		<item>"I wish I never played.. oh what a mess we made."</item>
		<item>"You go back to her and I go back to black."</item>
		<item>"I love you much It's not enough.."</item>
		<item>"You go back to her and I go back to us."</item>
		<item>"We only said goodbye with words, I died a hundred times."</item>
		<item>"My odds are stacked I'll go back to black."</item>
		<item>"You went back to what you knew, so far removed from all that we went through."</item>
		<item>"He left no time to regret, kept his dick wet with his same old safe bet."</item>
		<item>"I wanna touch you but that just hurts.."</item>
		<item>"I'll never love you like her.. Though we need to find the time to just do this shit together.."</item>
		<item>"And no I'm not ashamed but the guilt will kill you, if she don't first."</item>
		<item>"It's always dangerous when everybody's sleeping and I've been thinking: can we be alone?"</item>
		<item>"When will we get the time to be just friends?"</item>
		<item>"But I could swear that we were through.. I still want to wonder about the things you do."</item>
		<item>"What kind of fuckery are we? Nowadays you don't mean dick to me."</item>
		<item>"You can't keep lying to yourself like this.. Can't believe you played yourself like this."</item>
		<item>"No you ain't worth guest list plus one of all them girls you kiss."</item>
		<item>"You thought I didn't love you when I did, can't believe you played me out like that."</item>
		<item>"You say \"what did you do with him today?\" and sniffed me out like I was Tanqueray."</item>
		<item>"You shrug and it's the worst, who truly stuck the knife in first."</item>
		<item>"\"There'll be none of him no more\". I cried for you on the kitchen floor."</item>
		<item>"Upstairs in bed with my ex boy, he's in a place but I can't get joy."</item>
		<item>"I cheated myself like I knew I would.. I told you I was trouble you know that I'm no good."</item>
		<item>"It's not just my pride. It's just 'til these tears have dried."</item>
		<item>"I don't ever wanna drink again, I just ooh I just need a friend."</item>
		<item>"I'm gonna, I'm gonna lose my baby.. so I always keep a bottle near."</item>
		<item>"There's nothing you can teach me that I can't learn from Mr Hathaway."</item>
		<item>"Yes I've been black but when I come back you'll know know know."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
