<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Scherzinger was born on 29 June 1978 in Honolulu, Hawaii to a Filipino father and a Hawaiian/Russian mother."</item>
	<item>"She grew up in Louisville, Kentucky with stepfather Gary Scherzinger, mother Rosemary and sister Ke’ala."</item>
	<item>"She began her life as a performer in Louisville, attending the Youth Performing Arts School at duPont Manual High School and performing with Actors Theatre of Louisville."</item>
	<item>"Scherzinger majored in theater arts at Wright State University, but put her studies on hold in 1999 to sing backing vocals for the rock band Days of the New."</item>
	<item>"Mother was a professional hula dancer."</item>
	<item>"Nicole’s mother’s name is Rosemary, and her stepfather’s name is Gary."</item>
	<item>"Former member of teen pop group Eden’s Crush."</item>
	<item>"Nicole’s job before joining burlesque troupe Pussycat Dolls was working as King Louie at the Six Flags in her home state of Kentucky."</item>
	<item>"Attended Wright State University in Fairborn, Ohio."</item>
	<item>"Is a member of the Pussycat Dolls."</item>
	<item>"Ethnicities are Hawaiian, Filipino, and Russian."</item>
	<item>"When Nicole joined the infamous Burlesque group Pussycat Dolls she was under the stage name, Nicole Kea."</item>
	<item>"Nicole cut her academics short for the opportunity to go on tour with the rock group Days of the New."</item>
	<item>"Nicole always loved to sing and dance just from an early age."</item>
	<item>"In 2003 (prior to joining the Pussycat Dolls), Scherzinger sang live at the Tokyo International Forum performing \"I’ll Be Your Love\", a song by composer Yoshiki."</item>
	<item>"Nicole, along with the rest of Eden’s Crush, appear on the \"Jessica Simpson: Dream Chaser Tour\" DVD. "</item>
	<item>"Even though she is Hawaiian, Filipino, and Russian, she played a Puerto Rican in 2003′s Chasing Papi."</item>
	<item>"Nicole has been dubbed by rap mogul Diddy as the \"next Madonna or Beyonce\"."</item>
	<item>"Formerly engaged to 311 singer Nick Hexum."</item>
	<item>"Nicole won the Coca-Cola Classic Talent Contest."</item>
	<item>"In 2001, she competed in the premiere season of The WB’s television show Popstars, on which she earned a spot in the all-girl pop group Eden’s Crush."</item>
	<item>"Has a younger sister named Ke’ala."</item>
	<item>"Her mother’s name is Rosemary, and her step-dad’s name is Gary."</item>
	<item>"Nicole openned for bands including Foo Fighters and Bush, and also sang on their CD."</item>
	<item>"Joined the infamous Burlesque group Pussycat Dolls under the stage name, Nicole Kea."</item>
	<item>"In June 2003, following her stint with Eden’s Crush, Scherzinger joined The Pussycat Dolls burlesque troupe, who were being re-cast as recording artists."</item>
	<item>"She had first seen them performing on The Late Show with David Letterman in 2002, where Carmen Electra sang \"Big Spender\" from the Bob Fosse musical Sweet Charity."</item>
	<item>"Nicole guest-starred in an episode of Sabrina, The Teenage Witch."</item>
	<item>"Despite her being Russian, Hawaiian, and Filipino, she played \"Miss Puerto Rico\" in Chasing Papi"</item>
	<item>"Opened for Nsync on their Pop Odessey Tour as a member of Eden’s Crush."</item>
	<item>"Toured with Days of the New as a female background vocalist."</item>
	<item>"Nicole appeared in the 2005 movie \"Be Cool\" along with the rest of the Pussycat Dolls."</item>
	<item>"Scherzinger was once engaged to lead singer of the American rock band 311, Nick Hexum. She appeared in the video for their hit song \"Amber\"."</item>
	<item>"Hexum produced the song that Scherzinger sang on for the 50 First Dates soundtrack, as they were still dating at the time."</item>
	<item>"Has worked with the Black Eyed Peas, Busta Rhymes and Timberland."</item>
	<item>"In acting roles she has appeared on the television shows My Wife and Kids, Las Vegas, and Half and Half; and in the films Chasing Papi and Love Don’t Cost a Thing."</item>
	<item>"Song \"Don’t Cha\" with the Pussycat Dolls went to number one in America."</item>
	<item>"In September 2006 advertisements appeared in which Scherzinger modeled Bench Body underwear, which is manufactured by the Filipino-based company Suyen."</item>
	<item>"Scherzinger has been working on a solo album since late 2005. The singer has already worked with producers Akon, Timbaland and Polow Da Don."</item>
	<item>"A track completed in mid 2006, tentatively titled \"Steam,\" was leaked on the Internet days after it was recorded with Bryan Michael Cox and co-producer Wyldcard."</item>
	<item>"In addition, she featured as vocalist on the Diddy single called \"Come To Me\" released in July 2006."</item>
	<item>"n 2010, Scherzinger was announced the winner of the tenth season of Dancing with the Stars."</item> 
	<item>"On June 4, 2010, it was announced that Nicole would take on the role of Maureen in the Hollywood Bowl production of the rock musical Rent, directed by Neil Patrick Harris."</item>
	<item>"On May 25, 2010 Nicole won Dancing with the Stars season 10."</item>
	<item>"Has worked with Shaggy, Will Smith, Will.I.Am, Nelly and Rihanna."</item>
	<item>"Nicole is ranked #45 in the \"100 Hottest Brunettes of AIM\"."</item>
	<item>"In 2008 Nicole wrote a song titled, I think I'm in Love for her boyfriend, Formula One driver Lewis Hamilton."</item>
	<item>"Nicole ranked #22 in Maxim's 2007 Hot 100 List."</item>
	<item>"Nicole's job before joining burlesque troupe Pussycat Dolls was working as King Louie at the Six Flags in her home state of Kentucky."</item>
	<item>"Nicole has long, black hair."</item>
	<item>"Nicole has also guest starred on the short lived series Wanda At Large (The Plane Trip). She was cast as a passenger/witch."</item>
	<item>"Nicole performed in plays at The Actors Theater of Louiville when she was in high school."</item>
	<item>"Nicole is 5ft 5inches tall."</item>
	<item>"Nicole is the lead singer of the Pussycat Dolls."</item>
	<item>"Nicole's favorite movie is Napoleon Dynamite."</item>
	<item>"Nicole's nickname is Cola and Elikolani."</item>
	<item>"Nicole performed as a female background vocalist in concerts."</item>
	<item>"Nicole attended a theater arts high school."</item>
	<item>"Nicole would love to meet Jesus Christ."</item>
	<item>"Nicole believes in guardian angels."</item>
	<item>"Nicole always loved to sing and dance just from an early age."</item>
	<item>"She says that her all-time celebrity crush is Johnny Depp."</item>
	<item>"Girl power pop isn't all she's capable of! This doll can rock out, too. Nicole recently recorded a track with former Guns N' Roses guitarist Slash, and did a duet with Alice Cooper!"</item>
	
</string-array>
</resources>
