<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I never knew my titties was bigger than Pamela. So paparazzi flickin’ be flickin’ they camera."</item>
		<item>"Why did you envy? Why you go against me when I got trendy? Why you ain’t commend me?"</item>
		<item>"Just for the record: get wetter than a fisherman"</item>
		<item>"Nicki ain’t a rapper, she’s a brander"</item>
		<item>“All these bitches is my sons”</item>
		<item>“Got’damn, aint even pregnant, But i’m birthin bitches”</item>
		<item>“F-ck I look like ho? I look like yes and ya look like no.”</item>
		<item>“I got that kinda money that make a bitch broke bitter.”</item>
		<item>“Please you can never compare to me, all these bi**hes is scared of me. I am who they couldn’t even dare to be”</item>
		<item>“I’m the baddest in the game. Excuse me, honey. Nobody’s in my lane.”</item>
		<item>“So far ahead, these bums is laggin’”</item>
		<item>“Is this the thanks that I get for puttin’ you bitches on?”</item>
		<item>“If you ain’t shittin’, then get off the pot.”</item>
		<item>“I’m the mothafuckin’ boss, overwrite.”</item>
		<item>“Pu**y real good, it taste like mango”</item>
		<item>“I had to laugh at dat one, bitch get outta line I’m a slap da fat one”</item>
		<item>“I keep three hoes, But don`t call me Santa”</item>
		<item>“Bitch I ball no peep show; dead ass no peep show!”</item>
		<item>“All my New York broads spend chips in the village.”</item>
		<item>“I’m like 5’2 my S.A.T. scores was high too.”</item>
		<item>“If he work the middle like a mohawl, tell ‘em he can meet me where them girls say Aloha”</item>
		<item>“I think better with thick chicks with lip stick.”</item>
		<item>“These broke rappers always rappin bout a pink truck, I’m only happy wen I hoppin’ out da brincks truck”</item>
		<item>“If you don’t have critics, you probably don’t have success either.”</item>
		<item>“You be yellin boom-boom; When you really poom-poom.”</item>
		<item>“Now All These Bitches Wanna Try And Be My Bestie. But I Take A Left And Leave Em Hanging Like A Testie”</item>
		<item>“I just give him a wink; what the f**k did ya think?”</item>
		<item>“Roscoe’s on his knees with a snot nose”</item>
		<item>“I eat these rap bitches, somebody get me a dinner mint”</item>
		<item>“These broke rappers always rappin bout a pink truck, I’m only happy wen I hoppin’ out da brincks truck”</item>
		<item>“Young Money Nicki, Bad Boy Cassie.You wanna minaj? Now lets get nasty.”</item>
		<item>“What the fuck I look like bitch, I run this town.”</item>
		<item>“Why don’t you just sit back or dance? Sorry we don’t chit-chat with fans”</item>
		<item>“Bitch won’t blow, but she can blow my saxophone”</item>
		<item>“Nicki sexy any time of day”</item>
		<item>“See I’m a hater, I go hard. Listen let’s begin. You know her last name Minaj, she a lesbian”</item>
		<item>“All I do is sign boobs and be taking pics. Got the new benz the color of bacon bits.”</item>
		<item>“Once upon a time not long ago lived a chick named Nicki wit a naughty flow”</item>
		<item>“Defend my honor – Protect my pride”</item>
		<item>“So I’ma bounce back, and I’ma ball out, and everytime you see me I’ma go all out, and I’ma win til the ending.”</item>
		<item>“You could be the King, but watch the Queen conquer”</item>
		<item>“I think big, get cash, make ‘em blink fast”</item>
		<item>“Can I get that tron? Can I get that remy? Can I get that coke? Can I get that henny?”</item>
		<item>“Similes, metaphors and we pop pills. Sick flow inundated with the doc bills.Work hard, now we know how to top bills; in the middle of the street doing cartwheels.”</item>
		<item>“You like me, you don’t like me, you love me, you hate me.I’m gonna be me, but one thing I have to back it up is skills.”</item>
		<item>“Control my mind – Capture my soul”</item>
		<item>“Nigga got the peep hole to my soul.”</item>
		<item>“And if he think I like him then he might be right”</item>
		<item>“Muahhhh me love you long time like I’m asian”</item>
		<item>“Bitches is like crabs in a butcket. You see a bad bitch gettin shine you should love it “</item>
		<item>“I know you love her, but I love you”</item>
		<item>“Pull up in the monster; Automobile gangster with a bad b-tch that came from Sri Lanka”</item>
		<item>“Yeah I’m in that Tonka, color of Willy Wonka”</item>
		<item>“And I’m all up all up all up in the bank with the funny face. And if I’m fake I aint notice cause my money aint”</item>
		<item>“And when he spank this I make that pu**y fart. I’m such an actress, Melissa Joan Hart.”</item>	
		<item>“When you was on stage with ya brain on drugs, Nick Nack Carry Crack what my nickname was”</item>
		<item>“On a diet, but I’m doing donuts in the six speed.”</item>
		<item>“White boys tell me that I rock like guitars”</item>
		<item>“My pu**y on another planet; got that NASA pu**y”</item>	
		<item>“Cause you thought you’d win, but I knew you’d lose honey. I’m flyer than altitude cruise”</item>
		<item>“Shoutout to my haters, sorry that you couldn’t phase me.”</item>
		<item>“Nicki Minaj is who you ain’t fu*kin’ with”</item>
		<item>“If you ain’t shi**in’, then get off the pot”</item>
		<item>“Why are you speaking when no one asked you?”</item>
		<item>“Just for the record, I’m all that I can be, and I’ll admit I’m appauled when you envy.”</item>
		<item>“This one goes out to all my critics: don’t you feel stupid? Look how I did it. Look how it came to pass when I said it.”</item>
		<item>“I believe that life is a prize.”</item>
		<item>“Days of our lives, you wink it goes by.”</item>
		<item>“May the lord protect me as the world gets hectic; My voice projected my life reflected”</item>
		<item>“To live doesn’t mean your alive”</item>
		<item>“I am so territorial, that I just felt like whatever I was gonna do I was gonna write it myself, its my personal preference to always be in control of everything I do in life.”</item>
		<item>"Thumbs up like im hailin a yellow cab, My flow NUTS like M&amp;Ms in a yellow bag"</item>
		<item>“I Been Bad Since Sticky Hands Now All These Bitches is Nicki Fans”</item>
		<item>“Money in the air it’s a festival Cause I ba-ba-ba-ba ball no testicles”</item>
		<item>“Wanna Play Meet Me At The Fumble Line Cause Umma Ninja Cowabunga Time”</item>
		<item>“She Gets No Burn No Smoking Sign Yea Metaphor Heaven Cause They Approve Nicki Like My Credit Score 7″</item>
		<item>“I’mma need a coupleof those benz-ez-ez, I be up out China spendin Yenz-ez-ez, Gucci on my lens-ez-ez, my leather so sensetive, Scratch my 9 o’clock, I wanna shop, make it ten-tative”</item>
		<item>“You can hate me but why knock my hussle, I’mma be the queen no matter how they shuffle, Skirts with the ruffle, Louie on the duffle, I’m a bad b*tch, no muzzle”</item>
		<item>“Now I’m a dime, you a nickellete, Light skinned-ed pig-ament, stop copyrightin’ infringement, I eat these rap b*ches, somebody get me a dinner mint”</item>
		<item>“I mean Tinker, tell n*gga link her, Cause I’m lookin’ for some good brain from a thinker”</item>
		<item>“I keep three hoes, But don’t’call me Santa Anna-and I’m flyer than reindeers in the winter”</item>
		<item>“Ask Rocko, ask Gucci, Gucci bandana, I’m a star, I’m the black Hannah Montana”</item>
		<item>“Get me my limozine, all in your magazine, And when I come dem better lean like Promethazine”</item>
		<item>“One Two Buckle My Shoe, No One On The Corner Has Swagga Like I Do”</item>
		<item>“I never knew my titties was bigger than Pamela, So paparazzi flickin’ be flickin’ they camera”</item>
		<item>“I’ma spit on it, then I’m gon sit on it, You can f*ck my girls too daddy, I’m kin-done-it (condone it)”</item>
		<item>“When I come around it gets hotter than a soup kitchen, I’ll leave clips in your head like a beautician”</item>
		<item>“Back to basics, bitch I been hot since Asics, And I’m tighter than face lifts, flier than spaceships”</item>
		<item>“I’m from the Philipine, badder than Billy Gene, That’s why I get more head than a guillotine”</item>
		<item>“I say I body b*tches, it means that b*tch got killed, Ridin’ the baseline like I’m Quile O’Neal ”</item>
		<item>"I stay around the white like the Klu Klux Klan, stay around the sand butter pecan tan”</item>
		<item>“So where my cash at, where my stash at?, I mean, where the Dow Jones, where the NASDAQ?”</item>
		<item>“I’m bout that fast money, money ain’t got no patience, But if them boys come, run like you on probation”</item>
		<item>“I only fuck with bad bitches. no homo”</item>
		<item>“Every, every time I spit I mas-a-cre (masacre), So you better run quick like Nas-a-car (Nascar)”</item>
		<item>“Yes I’m the girl that they hearda, I commit murda, I body bitches, I don’t need a burna”</item>
		<item>“I’m the one! I’m the one, ya heard me?, The same number that’s stitched on McGrady’s jersey”</item>
		<item>“My flow stupid; wheel chair bound, Take the small bus.. All year round”</item>
		<item>“Tell Stack, to bring the black Carter, But If I f*ck em, would he? Would he yell ‘Squad Up!’”</item>
		<item>“You’ll be gone to November like Wyclef, I move weight and I ain’t talkin’ bout biceps”</item>
		<item>“I’m badder than the dude at the Neverland, Get the money green coupe with a lepre-can (leprechaun)”</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
