<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"There's definitely a dangerous feeling when you're in love--it's giving your heart to someone else and knowing that they have control over your feelings. I know for me, who always tries to be so tough, that's the dangerous thing."</item>
		<item>"When you really don't like a guy, they're all over you, and as soon as you act like you like them, they're no longer interested."</item>
		<item>"I'm a human being and I fall in love and sometimes I don't have control of every situation."</item>
		<item>"Trust is really important, just in relationships in general. I really don't like people that aren't real people around me at all. I don't like people that are 'yes' people. I don't like people that tell me what they think I want to hear."</item>
		<item>"Love is something that never goes out of style. It's something everybody experiences, and if they are not in love, people usually want to feel that. So if you hear the album, it's very romantic."</item>
		<item>"You know what, I'm very attracted to someone who makes me laugh and is that charming. Really, I could be charmed by anyone. I'm just a sucker for somebody that is charming."</item>
		<item>"The more successful I become, the more I need a man."</item>
		<item>"I get nervous when I don't get nervous. If I'm nervous I know I'm going to have a good show."</item>
		<item>"I don't use backing tapes when I am singing and dancing on stage. I can do cartwheels and sing."</item>
		<item>"There's plenty of days when I'm like 'Oh God, why? But that's just life. It's every job, not just mine. Every moment is not perfect. But it's definitely more good times than bad. You can't even compare. And when I'm on stage it feels incredible."</item>
		<item>"If he invited you out, he's got to pay."</item>
		<item>"We don't want the guys to think we're male-bashing or that we're thinking that guys should pay all girls bills, because that's not where we're coming from."</item>
		<item>"At the Billboard Awards my skirt was so tight they had to lift me on stage."</item>
		<item>"Y'all are so cute and y'all talk so proper over here. I love England."</item>
		<item>"I have a song that's called 'Me, Myself and I,' which is one of my favorites, and it basically talks about a girl who the guy's not right for her and he's cheating and whatever."</item>
		<item>"They do get on but I'm a daddy's girl and that's what he finds so hard to let go of."</item>
		<item>"I just hope people don't get sick of us. I'm sick of us and I'm in Destiny's Child."</item>
		<item>"The great thing about McDonald's is that they have a lot of different things on the menu. I love their salads."</item>
		<item>"There are certain things in there that are unrealistic. But it has worked for me."</item>
		<item>"It was great for that to be my first movie with such a wonderful cast, and such a huge movie. And now I get to do The Fighting Temptations, which is coming out soon--it wasn't much of a character, it was more of a real person, so I got to show more of my acting range."</item>
		<item>"We're negotiating solo projects for all three of us. They're all going to come out at the same time."</item>
		<item>"I'd done a couple of sitcoms earlier on, but I wasn't very good in them, so I thought that meant I couldn't act."</item>
		<item>"I grew up in a very nice house in Houston, went to private school all my life and I've never even been to the 'hood. Not that there's anything wrong with the 'hood."</item>
		<item>"It’s hard for me to meet someone, because guys are intimidated. They see the glamour and the security guys and don’t know how to deal. Honestly, even if I give a guy my number, they don’t call."</item>
		<item>"We live in different cities. But we started -- and most people don't know this -- when we were 9 years old. It's been amazing, the things that we've accomplished. There just comes a point where you have to challenge yourself and try new things. ... But we're still best friends."</item>
		<item>"On our tour, we met many of the children and families who are assisted by the funds raised through World Children's Day. We really recorded this song for them and all of the people who stand up and help."</item>
		<item>"Diana Ross is a big inspiration to all of us. We all grew up watching everything about her -- her mike placement, her grace, her style and her class."</item>
		<item>"We are so excited. I can't believe we're winning a Grammy."</item>
		<item>"We started when we were 9 years old, and here we are getting a Hollywood star. Dreams come true. So thank you all so much for supporting us."</item>
		<item>"I didn't have to do a lot of research for the role. It wasn't difficult at all."</item>
		<item>"It's great to come home. I am so glad we're having the All-Star Game in Houston. It's such a great city."</item>
		<item>"I love god!!"</item>
		<item>"The great thing about McDonald's is that they have a lot of different things on the menu. I love their salads."</item>
		<item>"I’d done a couple of sitcoms earlier on, but I wasn’t very good in them, so I thought that meant I couldn’t act."</item>
		<item>"I get nervous when I don’t get nervous. If I’m nervous I know I’m going to have a good show. "</item>
		<item>"At the Billboard Awards my skirt was so tight they had to lift me on stage."</item>
		<item>"I don’t use backing tapes when I am singing and dancing on stage. I can do cartwheels and sing."</item>
		<item>"They do get on but I’m a daddy’s girl and that’s what he finds so hard to let go of [on tension between her Dad and boyfriend Jay-Z]"</item>
		<item>"We all have our imperfections. But I'm human and you know, it's important to concentrate on other qualities besides outer beauty."</item>
		<item>"It's frustrating, because sometimes, when you are attractive, people don't acknowledge that you are talented as well. I mean, I'm a songwriter, I'm a producer, I have a strong voice, I'm a dynamic performer."</item>
		<item>"(about b-day album)I actually scream on the album and I don’t scream very often. People will be surprised, but they’ll also relate because everyone feels like screaming every now and again."</item>
		<item>"Love is always dangerous because that person has a control over you. That’s why you have to choose someone who you know is going to be good to you and bring out the best in you."</item>
		<item>"I feel a lot older than 25, to be honest. I feel like an old woman, like I’ve been around a long time, not in a physical way, but spiritually."</item>
		<item>"(on Oprah Winfrey) When I’m around her, I want to stand up straight, pronounce my words right and articulate."</item>
		<item>"I'm not one of those girls who has always dreamed of getting married. I'd like to get married one day, but I'm only 24. I'm in no rush. If it happens, it happens. "</item>
		<item>"One of the things that kept me out of trouble was doing something creative - creativity can't be judged."</item>
		<item>"There is always a lot of stress when you're making a new album, that's why there were only very few people who knew that i was working on B-Day. Not even my father knew anything about it!"</item>
		<item>"I don't see myself as a brand, a brand sounds fake, I am real."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes you have to remind your lover, why he fell in love with you. When you wear that one special dress then, the passion is back."</item>
		<item>"People look at us head to toe, judge us and think we're not human. We are. Nobody's a celebrity but God."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, I hated my name. I just wanted to blend in. I kept asking, ‘Mama, why is my name Beyoncé?’ I used to think it was made up, but it was actually her maiden name. "</item>
		<item>"You know what, I'm very attracted to someone who makes me laugh and is that charming. Really, I could be charmed by anyone. I'm just a sucker for somebody that is charming."</item>
		<item>"(on 2006's \"B'Day\") I made probably my most emotional aggressive record ever. "</item>
		<item>"(complaining that as she’s so good-looking, people ignore her artistic merits) It’s frustrating because sometimes, when you are attractive, people don’t acknowledge that you are talented as well."</item>
		<item>"(on shopping at Wal-Mart) My sister and I have so much fun there. I get everything there - CDs, all kinds of make-up like mascara, lipstick. And then I never end up using any of it."</item>
		<item>"(on meeting Diana Ross) I've met Diana Ross and she is one of the nicest women in the world. She came up to me and said if I ever needed anything, just to let her know."</item>
		<item>"(on playing board games) My favorite game is Guess Who. It's like charades, and I love Connect Four. I'm really good at it. I swear, I could kick anyone's a** at Connect Four."</item>
		<item>"(on losing weight for “Dreamgirls) I didn't recognize myself during filming because I looked like a cotton bud, and that wasn't a nice feeling. I look better with a few pounds on my bones."</item>
		<item>"I love fried fish, fried shrimp and all different types of pasta. If it's fattening, I love it! The trouble is it goes to my sides, my hips and my butt real quick."</item>
		<item>"I'm not naturally skinny. I fasted for two whole weeks, than got by on vegetables. I was starving. I didn't recognize myself. I was like a cotton bud. I look better with a few pounds on my bones."</item>
		<item>"(on the \"Dreamgirls'\" set) It is so tempting on film sets. They have these tables with every kind of food. I'd eat pork skins because that's the closest thing to chips. "</item>
		<item>"There's definitely a dangerous feeling when you're in love - it's giving your heart to someone else and knowing that they have control over your feelings. I know for me, who always tries to be so tough, that's the dangerous thing. "</item>
		<item>"I'm just jealous that I wasn't born Latina. I wish I had been, because the culture is so beautiful. I noticed a big difference between speaking to all of the Latino stations and speaking to the pop stations or the other stations."</item>
		<item>"With the Latino stations, there was so much love and everyone is so genuine."</item>
		<item>"When I was 10, I recorded a song called 632-5792 - a phone number. It's a little embarrassing but it's cute. There's a recording of that song on the phone exclusively for my fans."</item>
		<item>"(on her fall in July 2007) I recently fell down the stairs because my heel got caught in the hem of my coat. But really, I've fallen down the stairs a lot of times, so I can't only blame it on the coat."</item>
		<item>"At one point, I was a tomboy and wouldn't wear dresses. And when I first became a teenager, I hated purses. My mom used to say, 'You're a young lady, you should have a purse.' I refused. She had to beg me."</item>
		<item>"(on marriage) I don't know when I'll want to get married, I never pictured myself as a bride, but after my sister's wedding, I did start thinking about what kind of wedding I'd want. I don't think I want a big one."</item>
		<item>"I can't really go to church anymore, which is a shame. People have come up to me in church during the sermon and, of course, people watch everything I do. "</item>
		<item>"(on Barack Obama's presidential bid) I'm really proud. I think we're making a lot of progress. It's an exciting time for my generation, regardless of whether you're African-American or not. The level of excitement, I've never seen anything like it."</item>
		<item>"(on gaining 20 pounds for "Cadillac Records") I ate a lot of butter pecan ice-cream it when I was preparing for Cadillac Records. I was able to eat as much as I wanted because they wanted me to gain the weight. It was heaven."</item>
		<item>"(on waiting to get married) Before the age of 25, I would never get married. I feel like you have to get to know yourself, know what you want, spend some time by yourself, and be proud of who you are before you can share that with someone else."</item>
		<item>"I like that I'm curvy but sometimes I get too curvy in the wrong places. I have days where I'm like, "Oh God, please let me go back to sleep," but I just have to accept I'm never going to be skinny because I love food."</item>
		<item>"I don't really go out much. If I wasn't a celebrity then I don't know how I would feel, but it's not that much fun for me - it feels like I'm in a cage and everyone is watching."</item>
        <item>"I don't drink often. But when I'm drunk, I'm very quiet and I observe and I go to sleep. I don't think I'm much fun."</item>
        <item>"I always said I would never do (drugs). I've never seen a person who was high and thought, 'Wow, I want to do that!' I'm like, 'That''s cool for them, but no thank you.'"</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
