<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Kim Kardashian was born in Los Angeles on October 21, 1980."</item>
		<item>"She is the daughter of Kris Jenner and the late attorney Robert Kardashian."</item>
		<item>"She is the second oldest of four, with older sister Kourtney and younger siblings Khloe and Robert."</item>
		<item>"During high school, Kim worked at her father’s music marketing firm, Movie Tunes."</item>
		<item>"Kim’s first acting role came in 2006 in the television series \"Beyond the Break\"."</item>
		<item>"According to E!, Kim makes $5.545 million a year."</item>
		<item>"Kardashian appeared as a guest judge on Cycle 13 of America’s Next Top Model."</item>
		<item>"Kim posed nude in the December 2007 issue of Playboy magazine."</item>
		<item>"In April 2009, Kardashian released a workout DVD series, \"Fit in Your Jeans by Friday,\" with trainers Jennifer Galardi and Patrick Goudeau."</item>
		<item>"Kim Kardashian is the co-founder and chief fashion stylist for ShoeDazzle."</item>
		<item>"In the spring of 2010, Kim and her sisters released a clothing line for Bebe. They also own Dash clothing store."</item>
		<item>"In 2000, Kardashian married music producer Damon Thomas. They divorced in 2004."</item>
		<item>"Kim was partnered with Mark Ballas on season 7 of Dancing with the Stars, but was the third contestant voted off."</item>
		<item>"Kim starred in the 2008 film spoof “Disaster Movie” as Lisa."</item>
		<item>"Kim considers singer/actress Jennifer Lopez to be her style icon."</item>
		<item>"Dr. Sanford Siegal, the creator of the Cookie Diet, sued Kardashian, claiming she defamed him on Twitter."</item>
		<item>"According to Siegal, Kardashian tweeted that he was \"falsely promoting\" that she was on the cookie diet."</item>
		<item>"Kim worked as a wardrobe stylist for television shows and photo shoots."</item>
		<item>"She was the closet designer for Cindy Crawford, Nicole Richie, Kathie Lee Gifford and Kenny G."</item>
		<item>"The reality star celebrated her 14th birthday at Michael Jackson’s Neverland Ranch."</item>
		<item>"Kim Kardashian’s first boyfriend was Tito Jackson’s son, T.J."</item>
		<item>"Deep-fried Oreos are Kim’s favorite sweet. \"If I like a food, I’ll eat it, even if I know it’s not good for me\"."</item>
		<item>"Kim appears in the Fall Out Boy music video \"Thnks fr th Mmrs\" and gets cozy with bassist Pete Wentz."</item>
		<item>"Kim rarely drinks alcohol, but when she does, she enjoys sipping on a White Russian."</item>
		<item>"Kim once said, \"I want to be a Bond Girl and film a love scene with Daniel Craig after he’s rescued me\"."</item>
		<item>"Kim released her own perfume \"Kim Kardashian\" in February 2010."</item>
		<item>"Famous Cupcakes in Los Angeles created a vanilla cupcake mix for Kim. It’s called Va-Va-Va-Nilla."</item>
		<item>"Kardashian is the producer of \"SPINdustry,\" a reality show about Command PR, a NYC public relations firm run by Jonathan Cheban and Simon Huck."</item>
		<item>"Kim’s favorite movies include \"Clueless\" and \"The Notebook\"."</item>
		<item>"n 2009, Kim had a severe case of sunburn she got on a trip to Mexico that made the news."</item>
		<item>"Kim is ranked #10 in the \"100 Hottest Brunettes of AIM\"."</item>
		<item>"Kim was nominated for a 2009 Razzie Award for Worst Supporting Actress in the film, Disaster Movie."</item>
		<item>"The first fashion show Kim ever walked in was fashion designer, Christian Audigier's first fashion show he ever led at Locke High School."</item>
		<item>"Kim used to be Paris Hilton's best friend."</item>
		<item>"Kim believes in Christianity."</item>
		<item>"Kim likes to sky dive, ski, and play outside sports."</item>
		<item>"In 2007, Kim released a workout video."</item>
		<item>"Kim admits that the hardest celebrity closet to organize was Paris Hilton because she had so many clothes that she had to convert a bedroom into a closet."</item>
		<item>"Kim has said that she would love to give Britney Spears a style makeover."</item>
		<item>"In 2008, Kim made #3 on the E! list of the best beach bodies."</item>
		<item>"Kim admits that she does not know as much about her Armenian culture as she would like to know."</item>
		<item>"Kim's godmother is Sugar Ray's wife, Bernadette Leonard."</item>
		<item>"Kim was named number 28 of the Top 99 Most Desirable Women of 2008."</item>
		<item>"Kim was married to actor Damon Thomas III from 2000-2004."</item>
		<item>"Kim is 5' 2" (1.57 m) tall."</item>
		<item>"Kim is of Turkish Armenian, Russian Armenian, Irish, and German descent."</item>
		<item>"On E!, Kim is \"The Bombshell\"."</item>
		<item>"By her sisters, Kim is known as the diva of the family."</item>
		<item>"Kim was in a sextape with RnB singer Ray J."</item>
		<item>"Kim used to date actor/rapper Nick Cannon. Kim has also been reported to have dated Nick Lachey, Ray J, The Game, Damon Thomas, Jeremy Ferrer, Reggie Bush and Marques Houston."</item>
		<item>"Birth Name: Kimberly Noel Kardashian "</item>
		<item>"Kim Kardashian’s name is searched on Google over 9 million times per month."</item>
		<item>"Her dad, who passed away in 2003, was Robert Kardashian, an attorney in the O.J. Simpson trial."</item>
		<item>"Kim’s zodiac sign is Libra. Libras are flirtatious, self-indulgent, gullible, charming, elegant and good looking."</item>
		<item>"In an interview with Matt Lauer, Kim called herself a \"loner\"."</item>
		<item>"Kim earns as much as $50,00 per appearance. She shows up somewhere, take pictures, has fun and gets paid. For example, she got paid $25k per hour to party at Tao nightclub in Las Vegas in 2009. Not too shabby…"</item>
		<item>"Her first boyfriend was Tito Jackson’s son.  Kim Kardashian’s family were friends with the Jacksons, in fact, her fourteenth birthday party was at Michael Jackson infamous Neverland Ranch."</item>
		<item>"Her step father is an Olympic God Medalist.  Bruce Jenner competed in the 1976 Olympic Games."</item>
		<item>"She was guest host as a wrestlemania XXIV."</item>
		<item>"She has worked with her sisters Kourteney and Khloe to write an biography called Kardashian Konfidential."</item>
		<item>"No matter what your view on Kim Kardashian or her sisters, if she really did donate 10% of her earnings she at least has a good heart."</item>
		<item>"She donated 10% of her estimated 2010 earnings of $6 million to charity."</item>	
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
