<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Gossip Girl is based on the book series, it is written by Cecily von Ziegesar."</item>
		<item>"The character of Lily van der Woodsen was originally named Darla, writers changed it at the last moment."</item>
		<item>"Leighton Meester had to dye her naturally blonde hair brunette merely to audition for the role of Blair Waldorf."</item>
		<item>"Every episode title is a word play on the title of a movie, book or TV show."</item>
		<item>"Originally, Georgina Sparks was offered to Mischa Barton, who turned down the role. Michelle Trachtenberg was then cast as Georgina Sparks."</item>
		<item>"\"I'm not maternal! I've just been spending too much time with Cyrus and I'm turning Jewish.\" - Blair"</item>
		<item>"2008 - Teen Choice Awards, Best Drama (Winner)"</item>
		<item>"Taylor has the same birthday as The Rolling Stones' Mick Jagger."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves movies, singing and dancing."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's favorite school subject is chemistry."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves the bands Garbage and the Black Eyed Peas."</item>
		<item>"Blake dated actor Kelly Blatz for 3 years from 2004 to 2007."</item>
		<item>"As a teenager, Blake was a huge fan of Justin Timberlake and Leonardo DiCaprio."</item>
		<item>"Blake is right-handed."</item>
		<item>"Blake has confirmed that she is dating Gossip Girl co-star Penn Badgley, whom she has known since she was 11."</item>
		<item>"Blake is the youngest of the four leads in The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants."</item>
		<item>"Blake attended Burbank High School in Burbank, California."</item>
		<item>"Blake loves going to Disneyland. "</item>
		<item>"Blake: \"I can't believe we're being paid to live in New York\"."</item>
		<item>"Blake is the sister-in-law of Bart Johnson."</item>
		<item>"Blake: \"My whole family's been in the business. My whole family is crazy\"."</item>
		<item>"Leighton Meester's first experience in acting came when she was 11, while she was growing up in Marco Island, Florida."</item>
		<item>"Leighton is one of the few people who refers to Ed Westwick as /"Eddy/"."</item>
		<item>"Leighton Meester is naturally blonde but dyed her hair brown for the role of Blair Waldorf on Gossip Girl."</item>
		<item>"Leighton's favorite song is "Out On The Weekend" by Neil Young."</item>
		<item>"Penn Badgley's hobbies include singing, writing, and playing the guitar. "</item>
		<item>"Penn's favorite sports are surfing, skiing and snowboarding."</item>
		<item>"Penn Badgley began acting while growing up in Seattle, Washington"</item>
		<item>"Badgley made his on-screen debut on a 1999 episode of Will&amp;Grace."</item>
		<item>"Before Chace broke into the acting business, he was a valet. He admits to stealing customer's gum while on the job."</item>
		<item>"Besides getting married, Chace would love to fly a plane before he dies."</item>
		<item>"Chace's worst habit is that he doesn't clean his dishes."</item>
		<item>"Edward Westwick is the lead singer of the band The Filthy Youth."</item>
		<item>"'American Psycho' is Edward's favorite film, and he usually watches it with 'Gossip Girl' co-star Chace Crawford. "</item>
		<item>"Jessica:\"Jeans and T-shirts is pretty much what I like. And flip-flops\"."</item>
		<item>"Jessica did print modeling for Kohl's Department Store during high school."</item>
		<item>"Kelly gave birth to her first child, Hermés Gustaf Daniel Giersch on October 2006."</item>
		<item>"When Kelly was 17, she moved to California by herself, where she began a career as a TV actress."</item>
		<item>"Matthew Settle moved to New York City at age 18 to pursue an acting career."</item>	
		<item>"Settle has a daughter with his former wife, Israeli actress Naama Nativ."</item>
	
	
	</string-array>
</resources>
