<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Panic! contributed the song New Perspective to the Jennifer's Body sountrack."</item>
	<item>"Nine In The Afternoon ranked at #44 in Rolling Stone's Top 100 Songs of 2008."</item>
	<item>"Panic's song Nine In The Afternoon was nominated for Best Pop Video at the 2008 MTV VMA's."</item>
	<item>"Not only was Nine In The Afternnon the first song released from Pretty. Odd., it was also the first song written on the album."</item>
	<item>"Some of the album Pretty. Odd. was recorded at the famous Abbey Road Studios."</item>
	<item>"Panic's sophmore album Pretty. Odd. came out on the 25th of March 2008. It debuted at #2 on the Billboard charts."</item>
	<item>"Panic! was nominated for Best Boxed Or Limited Edition Package for their A Fever You Can’t Sweat Out Limited Edition Collectible Deluxe Box at the 2008 Grammy Awards."</item>
	<item>"Panic! At The Disco is one of the bands to have an artist-designed guitar faceplate for the game Guitar Hero III."</item>
	<item>"Because Panic! won the VMA for Best Video on August 31, 2006, fans declared August 31 Panic! At The Disco Day."</item>
	<item>"At the Reading Festival 2007, Jon Walker was hit in the head with a bottle after it was thrown on stage, right after Brendon Urie joked that they were doing better than last year, when he was knocked out with one."</item>
	<item>"Jonathon Jacob Walker was born on September 17, 1985"</item>
	<item>"George Ryan Ross III was born on August 30, 1986"</item>
	<item>"Born Brendon Boyd Urie on April 12, 1987 in Las Vegas, Nevada."</item>
	<item>"Spencer James Smith V was born on September 2, 1987 "</item>
	<item>"The demo for Panic!'s song Time To Dance (Boys Will Be Boys) was on the Release the Bats DVD during the end credits."</item>
	<item>"Panic! performed a new song titled It’s True Love at Milwaukee’s Summerfest 2007, but the band had no plans to include it on their sophomore album."</item>
	<item>"The first big venue Panic! played was the Marcus Amphitheatre in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, which holds 23,000, for Summerfest 2007."</item>
	<item>"Panic! appears in Gym Class Heroes' video for Clothes Off!."</item>
	<item>"The members of Panic! worked on songs for their second album in a cabin in the woods of Nevada in March 2007."</item>
	<item>"At the 2007 NME Awards, Panic! was named Worst Band."</item>
	<item>"In a 2006 readers' poll in Spin magazine, Panic! got named Best Band, Worst Band, Best Spin cover (October), Most Overrated, and Worst Live Band."</item>
	<item>"Panic! was one of the musical performers featured in Sports Illustrated 2007 Swimsuit Edition. In the ten page spread, they are posing with model Julie Henderson."</item>
	<item>"According to guitarist Ryan Ross, their goal for their Nothing Rhymes With Circus tour was to put on a show, not a concert."</item>
	<item>"Panic!’s look comes from their favorite movies: Moulin Rouge!, The Nightmare Before Christmas, and Edward Scissorhands."</item>
	<item>"On Panic!'s fall 2006 Nothing Ryhmes With Circus tour, due to their extravagant production, the only money they made was from t-shirt sales."</item>
	<item>"Panic! recorded A Fever You Can’t Sweat Out for only $10,000."</item>
	<item>"While recording A Fever You Can’t Sweat Out, the members of Panic! were forced to live in a one-room apartment that had bugs."</item>
	<item>"Panic! was named Breakout Band of 2006 by EW magazine."</item>
	<item>"The song Build God, Then We’ll Talk was originally going to be about prostitution and living in Las Vegas."</item>
	<item>"Panic! At The Disco’s song The Only Difference Between Martyrdom and Suicide Is Press Coverage was ranked at # 84 for Rolling Stone’s Best 100 Songs of 2006."</item>
	<item>"Panic! could not actually afford certain instruments for their album, such as an accordian and a piano. In fact, the piano music during Intermission is not an actual piano."</item>
	<item>"The band's hit song I Write Sins Not Tragedies is featured on the CD \"Only Hits,\" which features the top songs of 2006."</item>
	<item>"Panic! contributed a cover of the song This Is Halloween to the soundtrack for The Nightmare Before Christmas 3D."</item>
	<item>"Panic!'s first tour was the Take Cover Tour."</item>
	<item>"Because they only had their debut album to perform songs from, Panic! did covers of other songs on their Nothing Ryhmes With Circus tour in Fall 2006 to fill their set."</item>
	<item>"P!ATD performed But It's Better If You Do and I Write Sins Not Tragedies at the Boost Mobile Rock Corp. 2006, which is a concert for teens that have volunteered in their community."</item>
	<item>"Panic! was nominated for Choice Rock Track (I Write Sins Not Tragedies) at the 2006 Teen Choice Awards."</item>
	<item>"Brent Wilson is demanding the cut of royalties he earned from the band’s debut album, or else he is threatening to take his former band mates to court."</item>
	<item>"Panic! won the award for Best Breaking New Band on the MTV2 All That Rocks Awards 2006."</item>
	<item>"The band's favorite song on A Fever You Can't Sweat Out is Build God, Then We'll Talk."</item>
	<item>"Ryan, Spencer, and Brent got to keep their costumes from the video for I Write Sins Not Tragedies, however Brendon was not. He says though that he really would have liked to have kept it."</item>
	<item>"P!ATD recorded A Fever You Can't Sweat Out in College Park, Maryland over the course of five weeks."</item> 
	<item>"Panic!’s first practice session with Brendon was in Spencer’s grandmother’s house."</item>
	<item>"Panic! played their first live show after recording their first album."</item>
	<item>"The video for I Write Sins Not Tragedies was shot 10 minutes away from L.A in the same spot where the movie The Devil’s Rejects was shot."</item>
	<item>"Brent Wilson, Spencer Smith, and Ryan Ross were childhood friends."</item>
	<item>"Ross, Wilson, and Smith originally created a band called Pet Salamander, then Summerleague Rock."</item>
	<item>"Panic! headlined a summer 2006 tour which also featured The Hush Sound, The Dresden Dolls, and Ok Go."</item>
	<item>"Guitarist Ryan Ross wrote the lyrics for the album A Fever You Can't Sweat Out."</item>
	<item>"Brendon Urie was named one of Spin.com's Hottest Stars Under 25."</item>
	<item>"The band's third single was Lying Is The Most Fun A Girl Can Have Without Taking Her Clothes Off, which was released July 31, 2006."</item>
	<item>"The band's video I Write Sins Not Tragedies has been played over 10 million times on YouTube."</item>
	<item>"The band does not have any beef with fellow Las Vegas band The Killers, though it had been rumored they might. Actually, Spencer has said that he liked their album, and the two bands have never met."</item>
	<item>"Spencer’s first show was a Backstreet Boys concert when he was 9 with Ryan. Spencer said that he and Ryan learned all of the moves from the \"Backstreet’s Back\" video."</item>
	<item>"According to Spencer, Brendon is the only one with acting skills in the band."</item>
	<item>"Panic! left to go record their first record four days after Brendon’s last day of school."</item>
	<item>"Brendon graduated at his high school. Spencer and Brent finished their senior year of high school by taking online classes, and Ryan completed his first semester of college."</item>
	<item>"Panic! headed to Europe in October 2006. They played twice at Brixton Academy in London."</item>
	<item>"The band first perfomed in Las Vegas."</item>
	<item>"Their album, A Fever You Can't Sweat Out, went platinum."</item>
	<item>"When the band's debut album was released, they said there wasn't a copy to be found in Las Vegas. Even the band member's parents had trouble getting it, though Brendon Urie's parents were lucky enough to find their copy."</item>
	<item>"Their song after I Write Sins Not Tragedies is But It's Better If You Do. It involves lead singer Brendon Urie playing in an illegal strip club, against his girlfriend's wishes."</item>
	<item>"The band got more notice when they were named Band Of The Day on October 3rd, 2005 by Spin magazine."</item>
	<item>"The band got their name from a line in Name Taken's song Panic."</item>
	<item>"Brandon plays keyboard, piano and guitar"</item>
	<item>"Brandon was raised as a member of the Mormon religion in Las Vegas."</item>
	<item>"Brandon attended Palo Verde High School."</item>
	<item>"Brandon's His parents wished him to attend law school, but he pursued his interests in taking part in Panic! At The Disco."</item>
	<item>"The band's first single was I Write Sins Not Tragedies and proved to be successful on the charts."</item>
	<item>"Pete Wentz (P!ATD record label owner) says that the guys in the band are \"good kids\"."</item>
	<item>"Singer Brendon Urie is friends with Fall Out Boy bassist Pete Wentz."</item>
	<item>"Their eighth song on their debut album is \"Intermission\" which is in fact an intermission on the album."</item>
	<item>"The band played zero shows before they were signed."</item>
	<item>"Guitarist Ryan Ross was 12 when he asked for a guitar from his parents."</item>
	<item>"The first songs the band wrote were Time To Dance and Nails For Breakfast, Tacks For Snacks."</item>
	<item>"Their debut album, A Fever You Can't Sweat Out, was released September 27th, 2005."</item>
	<item>"The band was formed in Las Vegas, Nevada, by childhood friends Ross on guitar and Smith on drums."</item>
	<item>"Band members Brendon Urie and Spencer Smith appeared in Fall Out Boy's video for A Little Less Sixteen Candles, A Little More Touch Me in March 2006."</item>
	<item>"P!ATD is on Pete Wentz's (of Fall Out Boy) label Decaydance. They got Pete's attention by contacting him through his LiveJournal."</item>
	<item>"A Fever You Can't Sweat Out, reached number 13 on the United States Billboard 200 and has sold over 2.2 million copies worldwide since its September 2005 release."</item>
	<item>"The band's second album, Pretty. Odd., was released on March 25, 2008 and debuted at number 2 in the US."</item>
	<item>"The band released their third album, entitled Vices and Virtues, on March 22, 2011, while the record's first single, \"The Ballad of Mona Lisa\", was released February 1, 2011."</item>

</string-array>
</resources>
