<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"3 things I want in a relationship: Eyes that wont cry, lips than wont lie, and love that wont die."</item>
		<item>"You don't have to like me, I'm not a Facebook status."</item>
		<item>"Girls fall in love with what they hear. Boys fall in love with what they see. That's why girls wear make up; and boys lie."</item>
		<item>"Taylor gang or die."</item>
		<item>"Ballin's not a hobby, it's my occupation. Hoes on my d*ck, that's my confirmation."</item>
		<item>"I dont love em, I dont chase em, I duck em."</item>
		<item>"Good things come in good time."</item>
		<item>"Any chick that I handle, I teach 'em patience. How not to win the award but be glad for your nomination."</item>
		<item>"Tatted like a mexican, fresher than a freshman."</item>
		<item>"If you don't smoke, I don't know why."</item>
		<item>"While they talkin it I'm out here livin it."</item>
		<item>"If I were a lame, only just for a week. Id look myself in the mirror and shoot the first thing I see."</item>
		<item>"Let ya hair blow in the breeze roll some bomb ass weed."</item>
		<item>"Don't care what your friends say, cause they dont know me. I can be your best friend, and you be my homie."</item>
		<item>"It's Taylor Gang over everything."</item>
		<item>"Being single doesn't necessarily mean you're available. Sometimes you have to put up a sign that says, \"Do Not Disturb\" on your heart."</item>
		<item>"Tired of saying shit to make these niggas understand, so I'll be everything that you say I am."</item>
		<item>"Aw man, still they hate and talk smack, Knowin if i was gone, theird be no thrown to throw your rocks at."</item>
		<item>"Breakin down the weed about to make a plane, a hundred niggas wit me all reppin taylor gang."</item>
		<item>"Yeah they talk but I can't hear what they say... cuz I'm flyin."</item>
		<item>"People tellin me I changed, that's exactly what I'm gettin so I'll never be the same."</item>
		<item>"Ni**as be pressed for pussy, it aint nothing Instead of worrying about who that bitch fuckin, why dont you get you some money."</item>
		<item>"Now the hoes say I'm conceited cuz they wanna give me brain and I say I don't need it."</item>
		<item>"Rolex, mo sex, good weed, no stress, run my town, arms, chest, lift weights, bowflex."</item>
		<item>"No love for em nigga breaking hearts...no keys, push the start."</item>
		<item>"No matter where I am, no matter where you are, I'll be there when its over baby. Cause I was there from the start."</item>
		<item>"I talk money so I save breath."</item>
		<item>"You show up to my concert looking like a fan, I pull up in the car service looking like the man."</item>
		<item>"I fell asleep on a plane and never woke and now I'm livin a dream."</item>
		<item>"Them hoes follow like twitter."</item>
		<item>"Ni**as hate, they don't say it but they think it. When you lame I can't hear what you sayin when you speakin."</item>
		<item>"Maybe one day, there can be "us" again, but if not fuck it then."</item>
		<item>"Lifes good, So im livin great. call me outta town shawty, every week a different state."</item>
		<item>"I don't have much but I take all I got and that's what I give, what I get in return is the money I earn and the life I live."</item>
		<item>"Stay high like how Im supposed to do that crowd underneath them clouds cant get close to you."</item>
		<item>"Got no money? Get some. You ain't got it? Go and get it."</item>
		<item>"When niggas say I'm lucky, I say that..I'm blessed."</item>
		<item>"They say the game done changed, theres just some new players in it, n they dont wanna see my team get up there n win it."</item>
		<item>"It's lonely at the top, Im tired of having company."</item>
		<item>"Plus my city on my back like its a mothafvckin last name."</item>
		<item>"Got you ni**as checking game Im balling out on every level, hear them haters talk but theres nothing you can tell em."</item>
		<item>"A lot of ni**as fake but me I give these hoes faith."</item>
		<item>"I finally found me a cloud to float on."</item>
		<item>"I aint gonna flex, Im not gonna front, you know if I ball, then we all gonna stunt."</item>
		<item>"I aint trippin, never slicking or slacking on my pimping."</item>
		<item>"They let me in the club fu*k a dress code. Me and my niggas rollin up the best smoke. OG kush from the west coast. Oh you down to fuck? Well shorty lets go."</item>
		<item>"They call me Pocahontas doin' that rain dance, talkin' like oh I got it, borderline insane man."</item>
		<item>"Grow some more weed and get medicated, everyday is a holiday so we celebrate it."</item>
		<item>"I seen ni**as fold... like paper. Got money seen friends turn haters, got money minor league turn major, got money white people turn neighbors."</item>
		<item>"Soon as I hit the club look at them hoes face, put the pedal once make the floor shake, suede inside, engine roaring its the big boy you know what I pay for it."</item>
		<item>"Very strange yes.. you niggas too plane I'm a taylor gang jet."</item>
		<item>"If the streets know anything about me, they know that imma ball. Different city every night, imma star."</item>
		<item>"Went form being hated on to niggas try to go down the same road I made it on. Ain't no love lost but ain't no love shown, so now when niggas call I just don't pick up the phone."</item>
		<item>"Send her my way, she ain't gotta hold up. Whenever you call baby I roll up."</item>
		<item>"Real niggas fuk wit me so drama is not a thing."</item>
		<item>"If I die today, remember me like Jimi Hendrix. Butt-ass nekkid covered in all bad bitches."</item>
		<item>"Lotta money, lotta luggage, lotta hoes. When you in puttin work..that's how it goes."</item>
		<item>"Stay away from the fake or phoney, ni**as who can't support their own."</item>
		<item>"I only like to see the hoes who keep their nose up, have any nigga in the world but she chose us."</item>
		<item>"Use to not be allowed in the building, but now we on the rooftop."</item>
		<item>"Most niggas is broke, they bank is injured. Bitches gon ride with who they think's a winner, and I'll be smiling in case they take a picture."</item>
		<item>"My cash change the forecast."</item>
		<item>"Self made G, in my early twenties and own more money then oprah."</item>
		<item>"Hoes treat me like I'm a king, they wanna live comfortably sippin on champagne."</item>
		<item>"She say she love my cologne, that's money that you smell."</item>
		<item>"You show to concerts lookin like a fan, I pull up in car service lookin like the man."</item>
		<item>"Doin everything that you say I can't. Not a stroke of luck player you can say I plan."</item>
		<item>"Them haters probably wonder when I'm gone stop, never! Most of it's been good but I've seen some bad weather."</item>
		<item>"I'm so gone yes I burn after rollin' (after rollin') And float ooon an float oooon an float oon."</item>
		<item>"If it's one thing I know it's smokin and livin large."</item>
		<item>"I'm on my level."</item>
		<item>"Beware of them ni**as wit tattoo sleeves."</item>
		<item>"I'm gonna spend it all why wait for another day, I'ma take all this money I own and blow it all away."</item>
		<item>"Find the baddest bitch and get her number I don't even call her, feel like a million dollars."</item>
		<item>"Hating niggas talk, hear they whispers in the wind, but I don't wanna do them harm so I kill them with my pen."</item>
		<item>"Doing everything that you say I can't, not a stroke of luck player you can stay I planned."</item>
		<item>"Heard that you the shit, girl we should blow up together."</item>
		<item>"Everybody smoking papers, nobody smoking blunts. Bitches rolling weed and my ni**as f-cked up yeaaaaaaaaa its a partyyyyyyyy, oh, its a party."</item>
		<item>"Store running out of papers cause I bought em all. Niggas claiming that they Taylors but they not at all."</item>
		<item>"Not a couple cameras now they bring the whole crew. Bad bitch ride wit me so she pose too."</item>
		<item>"Victory I envision, so my mission is to win. One look at my arm she like wizzle where your skin?"</item>
		<item>"I don't talk much, too many niggas hatin. By the boutique...that's my type of conversation."</item>
		<item>"When they make it they should put my face up on a million dollar bill, cuz that's how I feel."</item>
		<item>"Niggas acting mushy like cat food. Niggas acting pussy like cats do."</item>
		<item>"Thousand pounds of weed. Riding in my car so fast I wont turn down the speed."</item>
		<item>"Them hoes dont use they feet no more, they break down to their knees and suck me like a king."</item>
		<item>"Nicky Santoro, money don't bend. Root of all evil, guess my bank is full of sin."</item>
		<item>"No sweetener straight apple sauce. Doing movie roles, rapper slash actor dog."</item>
		<item>"Tailor gang they rolling up those paper planes."</item>
		<item>"Maserati look mean and its fast too. Cinderella bout to get that bitch some glass shoes."</item>
		<item>"I was doing good way before I met you. Now you're off the set and I'mma let you see the show go on without you."</item>
		<item>"Roll this up, after you hit it once, youll need a parachute."</item>
		<item>"Ink my whole body, I don't give a motherfuck."</item>
		<item>"Smoking 2 Ls, living large. See my watch and wanna know how much it really cost."</item>
		<item>"Aint no love lost but aint no love shown, so now when niggas call I just dont pick up the phone."</item>
		<item>"The money i get make a nigga rich and make a bitch nigga sit, make a hoe get on my dick, come to the crib and just strip."</item>
		<item>"No Blackberry, too many lame niggas call my phone. Call me world wide Wiz cause Im never home."</item>
		<item>"See Ive been going on and on for ever them haters probably wonder when Im gone stop, never!"</item>
		<item>"Party every weekend, hardly ever home, dont see me face to face so you have to talk about me when I gone."</item>
		<item>"Rose in my champagne glass and diamonds in my ring. Uh, roll some, thats your bitch on my dick, I might let her hold something."</item>
		<item>"Big house, 4 whips, hella tattoos. Smoke good and ya bitch think Im bad news."</item>
		<item>"Bout to go nuts, nigga, Cashews. A promoter asked me if Im booked I say Im past due."</item>
		<item>"Not far from the tree thats where the apple falls. Say the wrong words so guys knock ya apple off."</item>
		<item>"Little nigga, big money, big dreams. Tall nigga, small nigga, big team."</item>
		<item>"Ooooh, girl your ass is superthick. Lotta chicks off in this club and you the baddest in this bitch."</item>
		<item>"I can do what I what, went form being hated on to niggas try to go down the same road I made it on."</item>
		<item>"Definition of cold: ice, 30 below champagne, foreign names in my pool."</item>
		<item>"Take you home, let you sleep in my clothes, roll some weed the homies aint gotta know."</item>
		<item>"When I was 16, finna get put out my home now the man making money, my nigga, my money growing."</item>
		<item>"Yesterday's paper, that's why you old news. Hating on my team until they see we won't lose."</item>
		<item>"Put a joint to my lips, and get highed up, skried up mean skied up, my niggas fried but dont try to run up on us."</item>
		<item>"Can't deal with this relationship but this what you asked for ask for them pictures of them b*tches, shit I probably wouldn't be with them. If your ass wasn't trippin'."</item>
		<item>"Girl I'm not a travel agent so what you trippin on."</item>
		<item>"High as fuck, sloppy drunk when I'm passin' through. Rollin' doobies up, yo ho who we pass 'em to."</item>
		<item>"Go download some of my old track and go play somewhere theres hoes at."</item>
		<item>"Most of its been good but Ive seen some bad weather and niggas watching now, wouldnt even give me an umbrella."</item>
		<item>"Bring the rap you was the main player I had to bench you. When I showed your ass how to ball that Louie I bought it all."</item>
		<item>"Higher than hell flyer than Delta."</item>
		<item>"Now how you think don't even speak unless you talkin franklins, ran out of weed but see i kept a g and brought a joint to bake so..."</item>
		<item>"Homey used to be a player, now i coach fools on how to get your money, live it and spend it just how you're supposed to call some bitches to roll through."</item>
		<item>"If you offer me all the money in the world I wouldn't trade it for my girl, my family, or the niggas that you see riding with me."</item>
		<item>"Fuck a hater burn in hell, sipping champagne while the waiters break the shells."</item>
		<item>"As we proceed, to court bad bitches and roll dope weed."</item>
		<item>"You know what it is, everything I do, I do it big!"</item>
		<item>"Leave a joint on the table smoke, i dont drink syrup im not maple, no your not able to hate on me, shit."</item>
		<item>"How the fuck could you hate this? Half of these people lame real niggas shape shift. That's why I'm smoking OG til I'm weightless."</item>
		<item>"I'm smoking on OG til til my problems gone, you try to call your man he ain't got no more probably cause I brought it all."</item>
		<item>"So cool my bitch got no shoes my whip is new but i'm playin old school always keep it up to date that's why the hoes choose."</item>
		<item>"As fuck my nigga, rep taylor gang whats up my nigga, big as a truck my nigga."</item>
		<item>"Homey used to be a player, now i coach fools on how to get your money, live it and spend it just how you're supposed to call some bitches to roll through."</item>
		<item>"Yesterday's paper, that's why you old news. Hating on my team until they see we won't lose."</item>
		<item>"Little nigga, big money, big dreams. Tall nigga, small nigga, big team."</item>
		<item>"Girl I'm not a travel agent so what you trippin on."</item>
		<item>"Ooooh, girl your ass is superthick. Lotta chicks off in this club and you the baddest in this bitch."</item>
		<item>"Roll this up, after you hit it once, youll need a parachute."</item>
		<item>"Ink my whole body, I don't give a motherfuck."</item>
		<item>"High as fuck, sloppy drunk when I'm passin' through. Rollin' doobies up, yo ho who we pass 'em to."</item>
		<item>"How the fuck could you hate this? Half of these people lame real niggas shape shift. That's why I'm smoking OG til I'm weightless."</item>
		<item>"Higher than hell flyer than Delta."</item>
		<item>"If you offer me all the money in the world I wouldn't trade it for my girl, my family, or the niggas that you see riding with me."</item>
		<item>"As we proceed, to court bad bitches and roll dope weed."</item>
		<item>"I'm smoking on OG til til my problems gone, you try to call your man he ain't got no more probably cause I brought it all."</item>
		<item>"Fuck a hater burn in hell, sipping champagne while the waiters break the shells."</item>
		<item>"You know what it is, everything I do, I do it big!"</item>
		<item>"Great Minds Think Alone"</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
