<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"In 2008 Jay-Z and Beyoncé were named Hollywood's highest-earning couple by Forbes. The couple were stated as being worth $162 million."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z's height is 6'1" (1.85 meters)."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z's top friends are: Kanye West, Beanie Sigel, The Neptunes, and Foxy Brown. "</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z featured Chris Martin from the band Coldplay, to add the song Beach Chair to his 2006 album Kingdom Come. The song was produced by Chris Martin. "</item>
		<item>"During August 2008, some of Jay-Z's extravagances during a stay in Africa included a watermelon carved into the shape of Beyoncé's chest, with cherries acting as nipples."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z was listed at #9 in Forbes magazine's Celebrity 100 of 2007."</item>
		<item>"As of 2007, Jay-Z has been nominated for 20 Grammy Awards, eight of those collaborations. Of these nominations, he has six Grammy wins."</item>
		<item>"American Gangster, Jay-Z's 2007 album, is a \"concept\" album, inspired by the Denzel Washington movie of the same name. After seeing an advanced screening of the movie, Jay-Z was inspired to make the album. "</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z retired in 2003, only to come back with the hit album Kingdom Come in 2006. His next album American Gangster is set to be released in November 2007."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z got the Hard Knock Life chorus from the Broadway play Annie."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z was a high school friend of the Notorious B.I.G."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z's song Can I Live? samples The Look Of Love by Issac Hayes."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z's album The Blueprint was released on the tragic day of September 11, 2001. It's a coincidence that it is called The Blueprint. A blueprint is the architectural plan or design for a building or skyscraper before it is built."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z appears on Fall Out Boy's song Thriller from their album Infinity On High."</item>
		<item>"Beyoncé's father does not like Jay-Z."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, Jay-Z's request to be knighted was turned down by Prince Charles."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, Jay-Z received an award from Prince Charles in London for his contribution to UK music."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, R. Kelly sued Jay-Z for $75 million after he was kicked off their tour."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z often spoke of his nephews in his music, including tributes in hits U Don't Know, Sunshine, Anything and Lost One."</item>
		<item>"In 2005, Jay-Z lost his nephew in a car crash. He was driving a Chrysler 300 given to him by Jay-Z for a graduation present."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z and P. Diddy joined forces to donate $1.3 million to Hurricane Katrina victims."</item>
		<item>"On Beyoncé's 24th birthday, Jay-Z spent more than $1 million on a diamond ring and watch for her."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is worth a reported $182.1 million."</item>
		<item>"In 2005, Jay-Z was turned away from the Kabaret Prophecy club in London for having too big of an entourage."</item>
		<item>"Damon Wayans request to patent the controversial word that rhymes with Jay-Z's trademark persona "Jigga" was rejected by the U.S. patent office."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z was named the greatest hip-hop MC of all time by MTV."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is part-majority owner of the NBA's New Jersey Nets. He has decided to move them to Brooklyn, New York, his hometown. They will be called the Brooklyn Nets."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is the President of Def Jam Records. During his first year as President Def Jam struck gold with Mariah Carey, Young Jeezy, NE-YO, and Rihanna."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is the CEO, owner, and founder of his own record label, Roc-a-Fella Records."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z’s given name is Shawn Corey Carter."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z was born on December 4, 1969."</item>
		<item>"He co-owns the New Jersey Nets and the 40/40 Club."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is the creator of the highly successful Rocawear clothing line."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is one of three original founders of Roc-A-Fella Records."</item>
		<item>"He is the current holder of the most number one albums on the Billboard 200 chart."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is famous for saying: \"I’m not a businessman… I’m a business, man\"."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z Grew up in the projects of Brooklyn."</item>
		<item>"At the age of 12 he shot his brother in the shoulder for stealing his jewelry."</item>
		<item>"His passion for rap peaked when mom Gloria bought him a boom box for one of his birthdays."</item>
		<item>"He attended the same high school as Notorious B.I.G. and Busta Rhymes."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z did not graduate from high school."</item>
		<item>"He used to wake up his siblings and mother because of his drumming on the kitchen table."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z and Beyonce were named a Power Couple in Time Magazine’s list of the 100 Most Influential People of 2006."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z spent a whopping $5 million on Beyonce’s wedding ring, designed by Lorraine Schwartz."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is involved in various philanthropic activities."</item>
		<item>"During his first year as President Def Jam struck gold with Mariah Carey, Young Jeezy, NE-YO, and Rihana."</item>
		<item>"His album \"The Blueprint\" was released on the tragic day of September 11, 2001."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, R. Kelly sued Jay-Z for $75 million after he was kicked off their tour."</item>
		<item>"In 2005, Jay-Z lost his nephew in a car crash. He was driving a Chrysler 300 given to him by Jay-Z for a graduation present."</item>
		<item>"Included in GQ magazine's 11th annual Men of the Year list in November 2006."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z appears on Fall Out Boy's song Thriller from their album \"Infinity On High\"."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z is being sued by ex-WWF wrestler, Diamond Dallas Page, for using his Diamond Cutter symbol."</item>
		<item>"Jay-Z often spoke of his nephews in his music, including tributes in hits U Don't Know, Sunshine and Anything."</item>
		<item>"Launched a contest for the new theme song of NBA's New Jersey Nets (February 2006)."</item>
		<item>"Sign: Sagittarius"</item>
		<item>"Sold his clothing company \"Rocawear\" to Iconix Brand Group for $204 million in cash (March 2007)."</item>
		<item>"When he was 12, Jay-Z's father walked out on the family. "</item>
		<item>"Nicknames - S-dot, Young Hov, Jazzy, Hova, Jigga, J-Hova, Jiggaman, Iceberg Slim, Lucky Lefty, Joe Camel "</item>
		<item>"He first started releasing records in the late 1980s."</item>
		<item>"\"Ghostwriter\" for such stars as: Foxy Brown, Ma$e, Dr. Dre, and others."</item>
		<item>"His ex-girlfriend's pregnancy led to a miscarriage two years ago, a fact he laments in the song \"This Can't Be Life\", from 2000's The Dynasty: Roc La Familia (2000)."</item>
		<item>"Since his album \"Hard Knock Life/Volume 2\", every Jay-Z solo album has gone at least double platinum."</item>
		<item>"His \"The Blueprint 2\" has sold a total of 3 million copies."</item>
		<item>"Created urban clothing line Roca Wear."</item>
		<item>"Calls \"Reasonable Doubt\" the favorite of his own recordings because \"it's the first\"."</item>
		<item>"Calls "Blueprint 2" his weakest album because of \"too many songs\"."</item>
		<item>"The second rapper to have his own signature sneaker, the S. Carter by Reebok. (Master P was first, affiliated with Converse.) It went on to become one of the biggest-selling sneakers of 2003."</item>
		<item>"\"The Black Album\" is to be accompanied by his autobiography, \"The Black Book\"."</item>
		<item>"Ends the feud with Rapper Nas."</item>
		<item>"Is good friends with Eminem. They have worked together three times since 2003."</item>
		<item>"Has often been called \"The God MC.\" This is why he has been called Hova. J-Hova (Jehovah)."</item>
		<item>"He and Beyoncé Knowles are buying a house in Miami as well as in London, England."</item>
		<item>"Discovered rapper Malicious Jynx."</item>
		<item>"July 2004: Has a sneaker deal with Reebok to create his S. Carter sneaker line."</item>
		<item>"Is portrayed by Jimmie Walker in rapper Cam'Ron's video \"Wet Wipes\"."</item>
		<item>"Was among the guests at Usher Raymond's 26th birthday party."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #10 on VH1's 50 Greatest Hip Hop Artists."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, it was reported that he had amassed a fortune worth $286 million as founder of Roc-a-fella Entertainment."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Ralph Fiennes."</item>
		<item>"Son-in-law of Mathew Knowles and Tina Knowles."</item>
		<item>"Brother-in-law of Solange Knowles."</item>
		<item>"Along with his wife, Beyoncé Knowles, is good friends with Gwyneth Paltrow and Chris Martin."</item>
		<item>"It was controversially announced on February 2, 2008 that Jay-Z would headline Glastonbury Festival in Somerset, England, becoming the first major hip-hop artist to headline the British festival."</item>
		<item>"Good friends with Rihanna. He is also her mentor."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
