<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Taylor wrote every single song off her album "Speak Now" by herself."</item>
		<item>"When Taylor appeared at the 2009 CMA awards, she assisted magician David Copperfield with two illusions."</item>
		<item>"In 2009, Taylor won \"AP Entertainer of the Year\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was the first celebrity to star on the cover of Justine magazine."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was on the cover of the March 2009 issue of Rolling Stone." </item>
		<item>"Taylor was on the cover of the April 2008 issue of Blender."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was featured in the August 2009 edition of Glamour magazine, which includes a cover story titled \"Taylor Swift: The Deal On All Those Guys She Sings About\"."</item>
		<item>"Justin Gaston played Taylor's love interest in her music video for \"Love Story\". Lucas Till played her love interest in \"You Belong with Me\"."</item>
		<item>"At the 2009 CMT Music Awards, Taylor won Female Music Video and Music Video of the Year for the music video for her song \"Love Story\"."</item>
		<item>"She performed her song \"You Belong With Me\" at the awards show."</item>
		<item>"Taylor became good friends with Miley Cyrus in 2008. She has referred to Miley as \"so incredibly funny and sweet\". The two performed \"Fifteen\" at the 51st Annual Grammy Awards together."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift attended the Australian premiere of 17 Again movie."</item>
		<item>"Taylor is in the music video for Kellie Pickler's song \"Best Days of Your Life\".She was in Brad Paisley's music video for \"Online\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Fearless Tour began April 23, 2009 and will be visiting 53 cities in over six months. Her opening acts are Kellie Pickler and Gloriana."</item>
		<item>"Taylor made MySpace video about her ex-boyfriend Joe Jonas after he reportedly broke up with her via a phone call, by portraying him with a Camp Rock doll. Taylor's song \"Forever and Always\" on her Fearless album is about Joe."</item>
		<item>"The first thing Taylor Swift did when she turned 18 is register online to vote, in pajamas."</item>
		<item>"At 11, Taylor Swift took her demo of karaoke songs door-to-door in Nashville."</item>
		<item>"Taylor has been writing songs since she was 12 years old, which was also when she started to play guitar."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's 18th birthday party had about 200 guests."</item>
		<item>"Taylor said that her favorite part of being on CSI was when she got to die."</item>
		<item>"According to Taylor, she loves CSI and has seen every episode."</item>
		<item>"Taylor is ranked #17 in AIM's \"100 Celebs Under 25\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor ranked #17 in the \"100 Hottest Blondes of AIM\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor has used two One Tree Hill stars, in her music videos. In \"Teardrops On My Guitar\" was Tyler Hilton who plays Chris Kellar and \"White Horse\" was Stephen Colletti who plays Chase Adams."</item>
		<item>"Taylor is the host of the GAC's Top 50 Videos of 2008."</item>
		<item>"If Taylor could be really good at anything, it would be dancing."</item>
		<item>"On October 16, 2007, Taylor Swift was honored as Songwriter/Artist of the Year by the Nashville Songwriters Association International."</item>
		<item>"At the 10th annual Young Hollywood Awards, Taylor was honored with \"Superstar of Tomorrow\", even though she is not a Hollywood star. She is the first musician to be recognized with the honor."</item>
		<item>"Taylor won Breakout Artist in the 2008 Teen Choice Awards."</item>
		<item>"In 2008, Taylor continued touring (she was on the road with Rascal Flatts as well as headlining some shows), which she loves to do."</item>
		<item>"Taylor is consistently ranked Country's #1 artist on MySpace."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift has surpassed triple-platinum (3 million sales) status and has spent 20 weeks so far in the #1 position atop Billboard's Country CD Sales Chart."</item>
		<item>"Taylor signed a publishing deal with Sony/ATV Music."</item>
		<item>"At the age of 17, Taylor became the youngest person to single-handedly write and sing a number-one country single entirely on her own."</item>
		<item>"Taylor won 2008 CMT Music Awards for Video of the Year and Female Video of the Year."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was named 2008 Top New Female Vocalist by the Academy of Country Music."</item>
		<item>"Taylor first kissed a guy at the age of 15."</item>
		<item>"Taylor admitted that her dream date would be with Chace Crawford from Gossip Girl."</item>
		<item>"Joe Jonas broke up with Taylor over the phone in about 27 seconds."</item>
		<item>"Taylor lost some of her retainers in hotel rooms."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift wrote or co-wrote all of the songs on her sophomore album."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was ranked #57 in Maxim's Hot 100 Women 2008."</item>
		<item>"The name of the person Taylor Swift was talking about in \"Teardrops on my Guitar\" was her friend Drew Hardwick."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's childhood crush was all of the members of the band Hanson. She thought she was going to marry the middle child named Taylor. She says when she met him and his wife she told them the story and tried not to freak him out."</item>
		<item>"According to Taylor, she is a neat freak."</item>
		<item>"Taylor appeared in Hannah Montana: The Movie. Her song \"Crazier\" is on the soundtrack."</item>
		<item>"She was named number 52 on Maxim's Sexiest women of 08'."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift's best friend, Abigail Anderson, is in her \"Picture to Burn\" music video."</item>
		<item>"Taylor is the first teenager to make it big in country music since LeAnn Rimes in 1996, making her one of the youngest in history."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's favorite selections at In-N-Out Burger are a cheeseburger and a chocolate shake that she likes to use as dipping sauce for her fries."</item>
		<item>"Taylor has a younger brother named Austin Swift. He attended the 2009 CMT Music Awards, with her. In her speech for winning "Music Video of the Year", she thanked him for being her date."</item>
		<item>"She has written over 200 songs."</item>
		<item>"Her song 'Mary's Song (Oh My, My, My)' was written based on her next door neighbor's relationship."</item>
		<item>"She never actually dated the boy named Cory in her song Stay Beautiful."</item>
		<item>"Her song \"Tied Together with a Smile\" is about one of her best friends, who was absolutely beautiful. All the girls wanted to be her, all the guys wanted to be with her and then Taylor was shocked to find out that she had an eating disorder."</item>	
		<item>"Her song \"The Outside\" was one of the first song she wrote (she was twelve) and she felt like a complete outcast a school."</item>
		<item>"When Taylor gets bored she likes to conduct random baking experiments in her kitchen."</item>
		<item>"When Taylor is in Tennessee she likes to drive by her ex boyfriends houses."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite food is cheesecake."</item>	
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite color is white."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite holiday is Christmas."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves to drive fast."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves summer."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves to write songs."</item>
		<item>"She loves to write about LOVE."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite artists are Miranda Lambert and Tim McGraw."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite song is \"Can't Tell Me Nothin\" by Tim McGraw."</item>
		<item>"She loves honesty and sarcasm."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite movie is \"Love Actually\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor's Favorite number is 13."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift was nominated in the Best New Artist category at the 50th Grammy Awards. Unfortunately, she lost to Amy Winehouse."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift judged the Holiday Holla competion on December 8th, 2007."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift wrote a song with Colbie Caillat called \"Breathe\". It will be on her second CD with Colbie Caillat doing the back up vocals."</item>
		<item>"If Taylor Swift was not singing or songwriting she would be a forensic detective."</item>
		<item>"The first song Taylor wrote was called \"Lucky You\". The second song she wrote is called \"The Outside\"."</item>
		<item>"On November 7, 2007 Taylor won the CMA Horizon Award."</item>
		<item>"In 2007 Taylor Swift toured with Brad Paisley."</item>
		<item>"In 2007 she won CMT's \"Breakthrough Video of the Year\" for her video \"Tim McGraw\" and was nominated for ACM's \"Top New Female Vocalist\"."</item>
		<item>"She is 5' 11"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift's third single off of her album \"Taylor Swift\" is \"Our Song\". She shot the music video for it in August of 2007."</item>
		<item>"In her music video for Tim McGraw, Taylor Swift not only honors one country music celebrity, but two. The video was shot at Johnny Cash's cabin, and that's why they named the love interest in the video \"Johnny\"."</item>
		<item>"Before the ACM awards where Taylor performed her hit song "Tim McGraw," she had never met the actual Tim McGraw."</item>
		<item>"The actor that was in her music video "Tim McGraw," is named Clayton Collins. Although in the music video, they named him Johnny."</item>
		<item>"Taylor plays a 12-string guitar, and she has played one since she was twelve."</item>
		<item>"Her second single off her self titled album \"Taylor Swift\" is \"Teardrops on My Guitar\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor wrote every song off her self titled album \"Taylor Swift\"."</item>
		<item>"Tyler Hilton appears in Taylor's video, \"Teardrops on My Guitar\"."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift has a tattoo of a heart on her left foot on her CD."</item>
		<item>"One of Taylor's songs that she wrote when she was only 12 is called \"The Outside\"."</item>
		<item>"When she was only 11 she performed the national anthem at a Philadelphia 76ers game."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift was the opening act for a Rascal Flatts concert."</item>
		<item>"She used to keep practicing her guitar until her fingers bled."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift started writing her own songs at twelve."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift's first single is called \"Tim McGraw\". The concept of the song came to her in math class. Her boyfriend had just moved away and she was thinking about all of the things that would remind him of her."</item>
		<item>"Taylor Swift's maternal grandmother, Marjorie Finlay, was a professional opera singer, and inspired Taylor to become a singer."</item>
		<item>"Bubbles sat in on recording sessions for the Bad album and accompanied Jackson to Tokyo."</item>
		<item>"The artist Jeff Koons made a series of sculptures of Jackson and Bubbles"</item>
		<item>"Jackson fathered two children with Deborah Jeanne Rowe – Michael Joseph Jackson Junior (also known as \"Prince\") and a daughter, Paris Michael Katherine Jackson."</item>
		<item>"The couple divorced in 1999 and Rowe gave full custody rights to Jackson."</item>
		<item>"Vitiligo, the skin disease from which he suffered, affects 1 to 2 per cent to 2 per cent of the population."</item>
		<item>"Taylor was born as Taylor Alison Swift"</item>
		<item>"Her parents are Scott and Andrea."</item>
		<item>"Taylor has a brother, Austin."</item>
		<item>"She began writing songs at age 12."</item>
		<item>"When she was 13, Taylor was signed to a major label but she decided to walk away because she wanted to find some place that would really put a lot of time and care into her album."</item>
		<item>"Her grandmother was an opera singer."</item>
		<item>"When Taylor wanted to make decisions, her point of reference is the 6-year-old girl in the front row of her concert."0</item>
		<item>"Taylor is a Def Leppard Freak."</item>
		<item>"She tends to use real names in her songs."</item>
		<item>"Taylor written/cowritten all songs in her upcoming album Fearless."</item>
		<item>"Her ideal outfit are a sun dress and cowboy boots."</item>
		<item>"She loves surprises and hardwood floors."</item>
		<item>"Her Prince Charming criteria include great hear, immature sense of humor, and quiet confidence."</item>
		<item>"Taylor said she’s not the kind of girl who needs a boyfriend."</item>
		<item>"She loves wearing bracelets."</item>
		<item>"Taylor loves black and white pictures."</item>
		<item>"She likes to read up on weird medical problems."</item>
		<item>"Taylor thinks Keri Russell and Ellen DeGeneres are the coolest celebrities ever."</item>
		<item>"She like things to be organized."</item>
		<item>"She loves little kids."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
