<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Strong women leave big hickies."</item>
		<item>"I'm not interested in being Wonder Woman in the delivery room. Give me drugs."</item>
		<item>"Everybody loves you when they are about to cum."</item>
		<item>"Better to live one year as a tiger, than a hundred as a sheep."</item>
		<item>"Love is a bird, she needs to fly. Let all the hurt inside of you die."</item>
		<item>"When I get down on my knees, it is not to pray."</item>
		<item>"Everyone probably thinks that I'm a raving nymphomaniac, that I have an insatiable sexual appetite, when the truth is I'd rather read a book."</item>
		<item>"It is difficult to believe in a religion that places such a high premium on chastity and virginity."</item>
		<item>"I won't be happy till I'm as famous as God."</item>
		<item>"I always thought I should be treated like a star."</item>
		<item>"A lot of people are afraid to say what they want. That's why they don't get what they want."</item>
		<item>"When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it."</item>
		<item>"Freedom comes when you learn to let go. Creation comes when you learn to say no."</item>
		<item>"Music! Makes the people! Come together!"</item>
		<item>"I'm tough, ambitious, and I know exactly what I want. If that makes me a bitch, okay."</item>
		<item>"Better to live one year as a tiger, than a hundred as a sheep."</item>
		<item>"If I weren't as talented as I am ambitious, I would be a gross monstrosity."</item>
		<item>"I'm not interested in being Wonder Woman in the delivery room. Give me drugs."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes you have to be a bitch to get things done."</item>
		<item>"Don't just stand there let's get to it. Strike a pose, there's nothing to it."</item>
		<item>"Listen, everyone is entitled to my opinion."</item>
		<item>"When I get down on my knees, it is not to pray."</item>
		<item>"I wouldn't have turned out the way I was if I didn't have all those old-fashioned values to rebel against."</item>
		<item>"If I weren't as talented as I am ambitious, I would be a gross monstrosity."</item>
		<item>"Deep in my heart I'm concealing things that I'm longing to say. Scared to confess what I'm feeling - frightened you'll slip away."</item>
		<item>"I always thought I should be treated like a star."</item>
		<item>"It's none of my business what people say about me."</item>
		<item>"Deep in my heart I'm concealing things that I'm longing to say. Scared to confess what I'm feeling - frightened you'll slip away."</item>
		<item>"I miss New York. I still love how people talk to you on the street - just assault you and tell you what they think of your jacket."</item>
		<item>"There's a certain satisfaction in a little bit of pain."</item>
		<item>"I'm not interested in being Wonder Woman in the delivery room. Give me drugs."</item>
		<item>"I wouldn't have turned out the way I was if I didn't have all those old-fashioned values to rebel against."</item>
		<item>"I know I can feel bad, when I get in a bad mood, and the world can look so sad, only you make me feel good."</item>
		<item>"A lot of people are afraid to say what they want. That's why they don't get what they want."</item>
		<item>"Don't just stand there let's get to it. Strike a pose, there's nothing to it."</item>
		<item>"I stand for freedom of expression, doing what you believe in, and going after your dreams."</item>
		<item>"Poor is the man whose pleasures depend on the permission of another."</item>
		<item>"I am my own experiment. I am my own work of art."</item>
		<item>"I have the same goal I've had ever since I was a girl. I want to rule the world."</item>
		<item>"Never forget to dream."</item>
		<item>"To be brave is to love someone unconditionally, without expecting anything in return. To just give. That takes courage, because we don't want to fall on our faces or leave ourselves open to hurt."</item>
		<item>"Children always understand. They have open minds. They have built-in shit detectors."</item>
		<item>"I wouldn't have turned out the way I was if I didn't have all those old-fashioned values to rebel against."</item>
		<item>"Straight men need to be emasculated. I'm sorry. They all need to be slapped around. Women have been kept down for too long. Every straight guy should have a man's tongue in his mouth at least once."</item>
		<item>"To me, the whole process of being a brush stroke in someone else's painting is a little difficult."</item>
		<item>"I think that everyone should get married at least once, so you can see what a silly, outdated institution it is."</item>
		<item>"I am a survivor. I am like a cockroach, you just can't get rid of me."</item>
		<item>"He (singer Prince) reeks of lavender. It turned me on, actually."</item>
		<item>"I'm anal retentive. I'm a workaholic. I have insomnia. And I'm a control freak. That's why I'm not married. Who could stand me?"</item>
		<item>"I stand for freedom of expression, doing what you believe in, and going after your dreams."</item>
		<item>"It takes a REALLY big man to fill my shoes."</item>
		<item>"I always thought I should be treated like a star."</item>
		<item>"I'd like to be more involved in making the world a better place."</item>
		<item>"Effeminate men intrigue me more than anything in the world. I see them as my alter egos. I feel very drawn to them. I think like a guy, but I'm feminine. So I relate to feminine men."</item>
		<item>"There are moments when I can't believe I'm as old as I am. But I feel better physically than I did 10 years ago. I don't think, Oh God, I'm missing something."</item>
		<item>"I would like to see the Pope wearing my T-shirt."</item>
		<item>"I feel just as hungry today as I did the day I left home."</item>
		<item>"I always thought of losing my virginity as a career move."</item>
		<item>"Catholicism is not a soothing religion. It's a painful religion. We're all gluttons for punishment."</item>
		<item>"I became an overachiever to get approval from the world."</item>
		<item>"My priority is my family, absolutely, 100 percent."</item>
		<item>"I wanted to be a nun. I saw nuns as superstars.... When I was growing up I went to a Catholic school, and the nuns, to me, were these superhuman, beautiful, fantastic people."</item>
		<item>"I am not anti-Bush. I am not pro-Iraq. I am pro-peace. I have written a song and created a video which expresses my feelings about our culture and values and illusions of what many people believe is the American dream -- the perfect life."</item>
		<item>"I like to show off when I'm on stage, but I don't like to show on, like, 'Come in and check it out. Look how rich I am.' That's not my style."</item>
		<item>"I love living in England. I feel comfortable and safe here. I want my family to grow up here."</item>
		<item>"I suppose I sometimes used to act like I wasn't a human being... Sometimes I look back at myself and remember things I used to say, or my hairstyle, and I cringe."</item>
		<item>"He's [Prince Charles] very relaxed at the table, throwing his salad around willy-nilly. I didn't find him stiff at all."</item>
		<item>"If I was a girl again, I would like to be like my fans, I would like to be like Madonna."</item>
		<item>"How could I have been anything else but what I am, having been named Madonna. I would either have ended up a nun or this."</item>
		<item>"It's none of my business what people say about me."</item>
		<item>"take it or leave it"</item>
		<item>"I know I can feel bad, when I get in a bad mood, and the world can look so sad, only you make me feel good."</item>
		<item>"I love contradiction,"</item>
		<item>"Two days? No! It has to be right now - I have to prove that you're wrong now. Sometimes I need to learn to bite my tongue."</item>
		<item>"Freedom comes when you learn to let go. Creation comes when you learn to say no."</item>
		<item>"Are you ready to start a revolution? ... Are you ready to change history?"</item>
		<item>"If it makes Tom Cruise happy, I don't care if he prays to turtles, ... And I don't think anybody else should."</item>
		<item>"Don't just stand there let's get to it. Strike a pose, there's nothing to it."</item>
		<item>"Beauty's where you find it."</item>
		<item>"Be strong, believe in freedom and in God, love yourself, understand your sexuality, have a sense of humor, don't judge people by their religion, color, or sexual habits, love life and your family."</item>
		<item>"If I have a problem, I want to work it out, right now."</item>
		<item>"Without the heart, there can be no understanding between the hand and the mind."</item>
		<item>"I had to write my book because there weren't any good children's books out there."</item>
		<item>"Being in front of all the people, waiting for it to come up, and waiting to see the audience, my heart was just pumping out of my chest."</item>
		<item>"Ultimately it boils down to the same thing all relationships boil down to -- eating humble pie. I sometimes eat quite a lot. But, however bitter it might taste, it's the best pie. It's on the menu constantly for both parties."</item>
		<item>"There's a certain satisfaction in a little bit of pain."</item>
		<item>"I got tired of not being able to download my own music."</item>
		<item>"I am very grateful that justice has been served."</item>
		<item>"You stiffen up, ... and you have too many clothes on so you can't swing."</item>
		<item>"It's like me keeping a journal, but it's visual."</item>
		<item>"Stuart and I didn't want to remake the past, but make it into something new."</item>
		<item>"This is the song I performed here back then. I think I've had enough time to remember the words."</item>
		<item>"Confessions on a Dance Floor."</item>
		<item>"Our intention was to give a nod and a wink to people like Giorgio Moroder and the Bee Gees."</item>
		<item>"They had to think about it, Benny and Bjorn. They didn't say yes straight away."</item>
		<item>"Because my record company is not very keen on the idea of me injuring myself."</item>
		<item>"It would be less controversial if I joined the Nazi Party."</item>
		<item>"[The man of the moment shows his A-list wife the way forward.] I love it, ... I think it's a very brave film."</item>
		<item>"[Andersson said he thought the new single was] wonderful ... Hung Up is really good. If it wasn't any good we would not have said 'yes'. It is a wonderful track: 100 per cent solid pop music."</item>
		<item>"[Want parenting tips from the Material Mom?] When Daddy gets home, they get chocolate, ... I'm the disciplinarian."</item>
		<item>"She wears the same outfit every day to school until she learns her lesson."</item>
		<item>"This is embarrassing, ... I thought we were all up to date. If we owe, we will pay it (today)."</item>
		<item>"Yakov and the Seven Thieves..."</item>
		<item>"People do see me as a less threatening individual now. Perhaps that has something to do with it."</item>
		<item>"As it stands right now, he's got my support."</item>
		<item>"I think to be the general for as long as he's been, this is a man who knows how to deal with pressure and make decisions under pressure."</item>
		<item>"Confessions on a Dance Floor is all about having a good time straight through and non-stop ... I want people to jump out of their seats."</item>
		<item>"She loves him and said she would work with him again in a minute."</item>
		<item>"The same as it is right now. Two very big egos having discussions about things."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, this has been a great learning experience and Jonas kept me involved in a lot of the decision-making, so I like it."</item>
		<item>"What do you mean you pray to God and wear sexy clothes? We don't understand this.' It frightens people. So they try to denigrate it or trivialize it so that it makes more sense."</item>
		<item>"Naming names, identifying marketers, corporate interests, major lobbying groups who are trying to go over the heads of parents."</item>
		<item>"Do you think they would let me get away with that? I did that last time, it didn't work."</item>
		<item>"I love it. I think it's a very brave film, a bit macho."</item>
		<item>"(Corn) still hasn't provided evidence that he's done an investigation, ... We want to see the tax records ... whether or not there is some connection. We would like these (documents) to be made public."</item>
		<item>"Glossy magazine editors would kill for that interview."</item>
		<item>"I am rich and famous. I have a talented and gorgeous husband and two beautiful children. I could go on."</item>
		<item>"They are going to see Revolver."</item>
		<item>"[A fantasy sequence in] Swept Away ... Come on-a My House."</item>
		<item>"She's walking and talking. I don't know if she's going to be hanging from a disco ball anytime soon."</item>
		<item>"She was the easiest artist I ever worked with because she knew everything. Pretty soon it was as though we were working for her. She knew exactly what she wanted."</item>
		<item>"He is attempting to sell the liquor license to the bar."</item>
		<item>"Gwyneth, Stella and Chris composed a song together, which was brilliant - a spoof on American Life, except they called it American Wife."</item>
		<item>"I had the same thing when we were watching Live 8."</item>
		<item>"American Life."</item>
		<item>"If you leave your clothes on the floor, they're gone when you come home."</item>
		<item>"I wanted a record with no ballads, ... I wanted there to be no breaks, with one song segueing into the next -- just like in a disco."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to go there. I get flashbacks. I'm just starting to feel better."</item>
		<item>"My daughter Lourdes and I listen to Britney Spears songs together."</item>
		<item>"[My daughter Lourdes and I] listen to Britney Spears songs together."</item>
		<item>"That's so duh, ... Which one don't I have. You've got to stop being so prolific. Every time I get a new one, another comes out the next week."</item>
		<item>"She's a mess. Madge has reinvented herself so many times she's run out of steam."</item>
		<item>"With so many highlights of my career having taken place on MTV and VH1 and then with the addition of their new Logo network, it just made perfect sense to air it for my fans on those outlets."</item>
		<item>"I just realized that nothing is what it seems."</item>
		<item>"Love is a bird, she needs to fly. Let all the hurt inside of you die."</item>
		<item>"There's only so much you can learn in one place. The more that you wait, the more time that you waste."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
