<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Everything happens for a reason and, something better will come along for me!"</item>
		<item>"Always be yourself, there's no one better!"</item>
		<item>"I'm no beauty queen, I'm just beautiful me."</item>
		<item>"You have every right to a beautiful life."</item>
		<item>"Breathing in, breathing out, ain't that what it's all about. Living life crazy loud, like I have the right to."</item>
		<item>"Now's the time to take a chance, come on we've gotta make a stand. What do we have to lose the choice is in our hands."</item>
		<item>"Being your self its all a takes if you want to be impressed someone dont be some one else just be your self."</item>
		<item>"I need you here with me we look for our love but we dont find it im searching and searching, I really need you here with me boy were going Round-and Round!"</item>
		<item>"Who says, who says you're not perfect? Who says you're not worth it? Who says you're the only one that's hurting? Trust me, that's the price of beauty!"</item>
		<item>"When you are gone its not what I imagine i think of you you think of me i hard to stay away i want you here with me we to places you make me smile the only thing is Im never gonna let you Disappear!"</item>
		<item>"A day without you is like a year without rain."</item>
		<item>"If there never was a night or day and memories could fade away, then we'd be nothing left but the dreams we made."</item>
		<item>"I love you like a love song baby."</item>
		<item>"The truth is bury when u look into the mirror but the lies are getting clearer. Your eyes fixed,your smile so elastic he gave me roses but there all just made of plastic!"</item>
		<item>"The Jonas Brothers are all sweet. They’re so amazing to me. They’ve become really good friends of mine, but I’m not dating any of them. "</item>
		<item>"I don’t really like dressing up. Some people probably think actresses dress up everywhere they go. I’m in sweatpants half the time with my hair in a ponytail. "</item>
		<item>"It’s not as glamorous as it looks. I don’t do it for the glamour. I really do it because I love acting. We deal with things at work and we get in trouble every now and then when we have to focus."</item>
		<item>"I’d love to do my own music for sure. I’d love to have a band."</item>
		<item>"I was never the girl who thought I need to make sure I look like all the other girls. I think you look best when you stand out. "</item>
		<item>"My perfect guy wears converse, is totally laid back, and doesn’t worry about being cool."</item>
		<item>"I’ve had my ring since I was 12 years old. But for me it’s not something I want to go around saying, \"Hey, look what I have\"."</item>
		<item>"The day I got my first letter from a fan, I felt like I’d been touched by an angel. I opened the note and read every single word."</item>
		<item>"I can’t count how many pairs of Converse shoes I own."</item>
		<item>"It’s important to always say thank you to your BFF."</item>
		<item>"To be honest, I’m quite boring! I love to go bowling and to the movies. When it comes to my wardrobe, I think I dress like a 30-year-old woman. "</item>
		<item>"I’m pretty confident in who I am. For parents everywhere, it’s my job to be a role model, and I’m going to do the best I possibly can. "</item>
		<item>"It’s overwhelming … to know there are hundreds of kids out there that look up to me."</item>
		<item>"The Jonas Brothers are all sweet. They’re so amazing to me. They’ve become really good friends of mine, but I’m not dating any of them. "</item>
		<item>"I don’t get in as much trouble as my character, Alex, but I am sassy!"</item>
		<item>"I was never the girl who thought I need to make sure I look like all the other girls. I think you look best when you stand out."</item>
		<item>"I wanted to be like my friends. I hang out with girls who had blue eyes and blond hair and I thought, 'I want to look like them!"</item>
		<item>"I don't actually like dates. I get awkward as I never know what to do."</item>
		<item>"I'm not really a girly girl."</item>
		<item>"I like having people with me to lean on and write with and have fun with. "</item>
		<item>"I get so mad about ex-boyfriends, but if a boy hurts me, I don't write a song about it. They don't deserve it!"</item>
		<item>"I love acting, and that’s my passion. So I would love to do more movies and some serious things. "</item>
		<item>"I'm kind of lame. I prefer quiet evenings at home, hanging out with my family."</item>
		<item>"Everywhere you go you hear things that are untrue. You've just got to learn that if I don't say it, physically out of my mouth, on camera, it's not true."</item>
		<item>"I’m going to be in a band – no Selena Gomez stuff. I’m not going to be a solo artist. I think that I don’t want my name attached to it. "</item>
		<item>"I wanted to be like my friends. I hung out with girls who had blue eyes and blond hair and I thought, I want to look like them!"</item>
		<item>"I love Katy Perry! She gave me a song for my second album."</item>
		<item>"You kind of can’t help who you’ll fall in love with. I’d date someone who isn’t in the business in a heartbeat."</item>
		<item>"Everyone wants songs written by Katy Perry. I asked her and she was so nice – she just said, ‘Yeah, you can have it.’ She was very kind."</item>
		<item>"I’m going to be Katy Perry for Halloween. I’m going to have the blue hair and the ice cream outfit she did. It’s going to be awesome."</item>
		<item>"I love Justin. When he first started to come over from Canada his manager contacted me and he just said that he would like to meet me and he was just such a good kid."</item>
		<item>"(on Demi Lovato) I love her. I completely love her and her whole family to death. I will always talk extremely highly of her and I always have."</item>
		<item>"I love Nicki Minaj, Eminem, Katy Perry. They are all about being themselves and I love that."</item>
		<item>"(on going to her firs concert – a Britney Spears show) We were in the nosebleeds with my cousin. I got the T-shirt and glow sticks and I just remember it being the highlight of my life! I felt like I was on cloud nine!"</item>
		<item>"I’m not going to even touch Britney! She’s so good. I wouldn’t want to butcher it. I’m just going to pay tribute to her! I’m gonna say she’s awesome."</item>
		<item>"on Rebecca Black’s song ‘Friday’) I love it! Total guilty pleasure! I totally admire her, I think it’s awesome that she hasn’t taken that downward spiral that other child stars have taken."</item>
		<item>"I've done episodes on The Suite Life of Zack and Cody and Hannah Montana. On Hannah Montana everyone was so sweet, but I had to play a nasty girl. I'm not really that way - I love Miley!"</item>
		<item>"That's one of the craziest rumors I've heard. Well that, and the one that says Miley and I are feuding. None of it's true! Cole is sweet, but I'm not going out with him. AND I love Miley to death!"</item>
		<item>"I came to my mom and told her I wanted to do this[acting]."</item>
		<item>"Most of my songs are about love, I am a 16 year old teenager and I sing about what is on every girls mind. Love."</item>
		<item>"I love Friends, so I try to bring Jennifer Aniston's mannerisms to my show."</item>
		<item>"I’m pretty confident in who I am. I know that for parents everywhere, it’s my job to be a role model, and I’m going to do the best I possibly can."</item>
		<item>"Love is beautiful. It’s hard but so wonderful. You should enjoy it and make sure the person betters you. I’ve been told I keep my heart guarded. My advice is to have fun and to be prepared for anything."</item>
		<item>"There are worse things than someone disliking you and people on the Internet saying this or that, but I can’t lie. It hurts. I have a love-hate relationship with the Internet. I don’t like it in general"</item>
		<item>"Every choice that I make when it comes to my personal life, my films or my music, I always say, 'Would my fans be proud of that?' If I did something to kind of upset them, it would really crush me."</item>
		<item>"I feel like I’m still the girl from Texas that moved to L.A., just older and a little bit wiser."</item>
		<item>"I just tried to take everything in. I cried so much. The whole crew on that show has played a huge part of my life. They all watched me grow up and helped raise me in different ways."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
