<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Birth Name: Angelina Jolie Voight "</item>
		<item>"She was born on 4 June 1975, Los Angeles, California, USA."</item>
		<item>"Nicknames: Angie, Catwoman, Ange, AJ "</item>
		<item>"Angie stands 5' 8" (1.73 m)."</item>
		<item>"She become popular by taking on the title role in the \"Lara Croft\" series of blockbuster movies."</item>
		<item>"Off-screen, Jolie has become prominently involved in international charity projects, especially those involving refugees."</item>
		<item>"Angelina made her film debut in 1982's Lookin' to Get Out, which was written by and starred her father Jon Voight."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, Angelina was made an honorary citizen of Cambodia by the Prime Minister of Cambodia because of her social work there."</item>
		<item>"In the year 2003, Angelina appeared in print ads for Tissot watches. She has also appeared in TV commercials for Jeep, Kraft Macaroni and Cheese Deluxe and Animal Planet."</item>
		<item>"2009- Ranked as #1 in AIM's \"100 Hottest Brunettes\"."</item>
		<item>"2007- voted as the #9 fantasy girlfriend in a poll conducted by AskMen.com for the 'Top 99 Most Desirable Women of 2007'"</item>
		<item>"2007- chosen as one of People Magazine's annual '100 Most Beautiful People in the World'."</item>
		<item>"2007- ranked #12 in Maxim's 'Hot 100 List'."</item>
		<item>"2007- named Cosmopolitan magazine's 'Ultimate Woman Who Made Us Care'."</item>
		<item>"2006- ranked #1 in E! Television's 2006 '101 Sexiest Celebrity Bodies' list."</item>
		<item>"2006- ranked #3 on Entertainment Tonight's 'Hot List of 2006'"</item>
		<item>"2006- tied with Jennifer Aniston for #35 on Forbes 'Top 100 Celebrities' list."</item>
		<item>"2005- voted the #1 star most men would like to kiss under the mistletoe, in a poll for Sky Movies."</item>
		<item>"2005- named #7 on Maxim magazine's 'Hot 100 of 2005' list."</item>
		<item>"2004- voted as #6 on the 'Top 100 Sexiest Women' in FHM."</item>
		<item>"2004- named Esquire Magazine's 'Sexiest Woman Alive'"</item>
		<item>"2002- ranked #6 in Stuff magazine's '102 Sexiest Women in the World' list."</item>
		<item>"2002- ranked #87 in Premiere's 2002 annual 'Power 100' list."</item>
		<item>"2000- ranked #2 on 'Mr. Blackwell's Worst Dress List'"</item>
		<item>"Angelina is of Czech and American descent on her father's side and French and Haudenosaunee (Iroquian Indian) heritage on her mother's side."</item>
		<item>"Angelina's mother was actress, Marcheline Bertrand who passed away from ovarian cancer in Los Angeles after a 7 1/2 year battle (January 27, 2007)."</item>
		<item>"Her father is actor, Jon Voight."</item>
		<item>"Angelina is the sister of James Haven."</item>
		<item>"Angelina is the goddaughter of actress Jacqueline Bisset and actor Maximilian Schell."</item>
		<item>"Angelina is the niece of Chip Taylor."</item>
		<item>"Angelina was married to actor Jonny Lee Miller from 1995 until 1999."</item>
		<item>"Angelina was married to actor and director Billy Bob Thornton from May 5, 2000 until May 27, 2003."</item>
		<item>"Angelina's adopted son, Maddox Chivan Thornton Jolie, was born on August 5, 2001. Angelina adopted him when she was married to Billy Bob Thornton."</item>
		<item>"In July 2002, Angelina confirmed her break up with actor Billy Bob Thornton."</item>
		<item>"Angelina's adopted daughter, Zahara Marley Jolie, was born on January 8, 2005."</item>
		<item>"Angelina's children, Maddox and Zahara, share Brad Pitt's surname, after he legally adopted them in 2005."</item>
		<item>"Angelina and Brad's daughter, Shiloh Nouvel Jolie-Pitt, was born on May 27, 2006, at the small Cattage Medi-Clinic in Swakopmund, a coastal town in the African nation of Namib by C-section."</item>
		<item>"On March 15, 2007, Angelina adopted another son, a three year old from Vietnam, Pax Thien Jolie (originally Pham Quang Sang) born on November 29, 2003."</item>
		<item>"Angelina's and Brad's fraternal twins were born on July 12, 2008, a son, named Knox Léon Jolie-Pitt at, 6:27 p.m, weighing 5 lbs 3 oz and a daughter, Vivienne Marcheline Jolie-Pitt, at 6:28 p.m, weighing 5 lbs."</item>
		<item>"Angelina has a private pilot and Airbase single engine land civilian pilot's license."</item>
		<item>"Angelina is of Czech and American descent on her father's side, and French and Haudenosaunee (Iroquian Native) heritage on her mother's side."</item>
		<item>"\"Introducing Angelina Jolie\" in the opening credits of Love Is All There Is (1996) suggests a delayed release, as Ange already had at least two major screen roles by 1996."</item>
		<item>"Angelina was appointed Goodwill Ambassador for the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees in Geneva, Switzerland, after her visits to Sierra Leone, Tanzania and Pakistan."</item>
		<item>"Angelina collects knives and has an interest in mortuary science."</item>
		<item>"Angelina has made a reservation to fly into space on Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic."</item>
		<item>"Angelina performed her own stunts in Tomb Raider and received cuts from the chandelier scene as a result."</item>
		<item>"Favorite animals are lizards and snakes"</item>
		<item>"Favorite foods include McDonalds and Cheerios cereal."</item>
		<item>"Favorite color is black."</item>
		<item>"Favorite TV shows are King of the Hill and Animal Planet."</item>
		<item>"Favorite author is Ayn Rand."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Disney character is Dumbo."</item>
		<item>"Angelina was nominated for Worst Actress at the Razzie Awards for four straight years from 2002 to 2005, but each time was beaten by another of her fellow nominees."</item>
		<item>"Angelina consulted with real-life FBI profiler Robert Ressler for her role in Taking Lives. (2004)"</item>
		<item>"Angelina worked as a professional model in London, New York and Los Angeles."</item>
		<item>"appeared in music videos for such artists as Meatloaf, Antonello Venditti, Lenny Kravitz, Lemonheads and The Rolling Stones."</item>
		<item>"She has acted in five student films for the USC School of Cinema, all directed by her brother, James Haven."</item>
		<item>"She is extremely close to and protective of her older brother, James Haven. He often accompanies her to awards shows, and she used his name, or at least his memory, as inspiration in the \"Where's Jamie?!\" scene in Girl, Interrupted."</item>
		<item>"Has the letter \"H\" tattooed on the inside of her left wrist, which is a reference to two people she is close to who have this letter in their names: her brother, James Haven, and Timothy Hutton."</item>
		<item>"Has a tattoo of the Tennessee Williams quote, \"A prayer for the wild at heart, kept in cages.\" on her left forearm."</item>
		<item>"Was married to Jonny Lee Miller in a black leather pants and a white shirt. On the white shirt she painted her husband's name in her own blood (across the back)."</item>
		<item>"Tattoos include the Japanese sign for death, two pointy black American Indian symbols, a dragon, and a large black cross."</item>
		<item>"Angelina and her brother, to whom she is very close, publicly spoke out to deny false rumors that the two were having an incestuous love affair. [2000]"</item>
		<item>"Had a childhood dream of becoming a funeral director."</item>
		<item>"Named the world's sexiest woman in Swedish magazine Café."</item>
		<item>"\"Jolie\" means \"pretty\" in French."</item>
		<item>"She is goddaughter of actress Jacqueline Bisset."</item>
		<item>"Has the Latin phrase \"Quod me nutrit me destruit\" (\"What nourishes me also destroys me\") tattooed across her stomach."</item>
		<item>"Appointed Goodwill Ambassador for the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees in Geneva, Switzerland after her visits to Sierra Leone, Tanzania and Pakistan."</item>
		<item>"Born at 9:09 AM PDT"</item>
		<item>"In role as goodwill ambassador, visited Tham Hin refugee camp in Thailand, May 2002, to check on conditions of 9,000 refugees from bordering Myanmar."</item>
		<item>"Measurements (before pregnancy): 36C-27-36."</item>
		<item>"Announced in late 2002 that she is "in talks" to portray the late porn star Linda Lovelace. Eventually, she lost the role to Courtney Love."</item>
		<item>"Voted the 3rd Sexiest Female Movie Star in the Australian Empire Magazine September 2002."</item>
		<item>"Her favorite Disney character is Dumbo the flying elephant, she has said that she cried when he was able to fly."</item>
		<item>"Started modelling at the age of 14."</item>
		<item>"Favorite music: Madonna, Elvis Presley, Frank Sinatra, The Clash, Matchbox Twenty."</item>
		<item>"One of her favorite TV shows is \"King of the Hill\" (1997). She also enjoys the Game Show Network and Animal Planet."</item>
		<item>"Graduated from Beverly Hills High School at age 16, the same school as Lenny Kravitz. She also went to school with Michael Klesic and Bahar Soomekh."</item>
		<item>"Has said that she speaks \"very little French\"."</item>
		<item>"Voted #1 star most men would like to kiss under the mistletoe in a poll for Sky Movies."</item>
		<item>"Used to own several pet reptiles, including two snakes. Therefore she had no problem shooting the snake scene in Alexander (2004)."</item>
		<item>"Her father starred with her godmother Jacqueline Bisset in End of the Game (1975), which was directed by her godfather Maximilian Schell."</item>
		<item>"Voted Hollywood's Sexiest Single Mother, in a poll for website Date.com."</item>
		<item>"Consulted with real-life FBI profiler Robert K. Ressler for her role in Taking Lives (2004)."</item>
		<item>"In 2003 was first recipient of the Citizen of the World Award from the UN's Correspondents' Association for her work as a goodwill ambassador with the UNHCR."</item>
		<item>"July 6th 2005: adopted a baby girl (born on January 8th, 2005) from Ethiopia who was orphaned by AIDS."</item>
		<item>"Gave her Oscar Statuette, Golden Globes, SAG Awards, and Critic Choice Award to her mother. She felt she didn't need to hang on to awards."</item>
		<item>"Her godfather Maximilian Schell always gave her a doll as a birthday present, from her first to sixteenth. Sometimes it was a modern doll, made of plastic, sometimes it was an old and precious one, made of wood or porcelain."</item>
		<item>"Gave her mother the nickname \"Great Lady\"."</item>
		<item>"Has tattoos of the coordinates representing the birth countries of each of her kids (she even has the coordinates of France tattooed on her arm twice, one each for Knox and Viv), which cover up the Billy Bob Thornton tattoo (June 2006)"</item>
		<item>"Has a fondness for Liverpool Football Club because her son Maddox \"only wants to play for Liverpool\"."</item>
		<item>"She donated many items to Rocky Stone to be given to less fortunate kids as part of the Toy Mountain Campaign."</item>
		<item>"Became the third actress to join the coveted $20 Million Club (after Julia Roberts and Cameron Diaz), when she signed to do Mr. and Mrs. Smith (2005) for that amount."</item>
		<item>"Fan of author Ayn Rand."</item>
		<item>"Is left-handed and therefore had to have guns specially made so that she could reload them easily for Lara Croft: Tomb Raider (2001)."</item>
		<item>"Is an alumna of the Lee Strasberg Institute as are Frank Miranda, Harvey Keitel, Robert De Niro, Al Pacino, Sally Field."</item>
		<item>"In 2006, after the birth of her daughter Shiloh, she sold the first pictures of her newborn for $4,100,000. She later donated the profits to charity."</item>
		<item>"Was considered for the role of Kelly Kapowski on \"Saved by the Bell\"."</item>
		<item>"Since becoming a Goodwill Ambassador in 2001, she has visited over 20 countries."</item>
		<item>"In an interview about her movie Changeling (2008), Angie revealed that although her mom's name was Marcheline, everyone called her \"Marshmallow\", because she was such a softie."</item>
		<item>"Went to Beverly Hills High School with writer/actor Quincy Rose, son of Mickey Rose, and Antonia Bennett, daughter of Tony Bennett."</item>
		<item>"Returned to work eight months after giving birth to twins Vivienne Marcheline and Knox Leon in order to begin filming Salt (2010)."</item>
		<item>"In July 2009, she was voted in first place in a poll to find the 100 Greatest Sex Symbols for Britain's Channel 4. Elvis Presley was runner-up."</item>
		<item>"Returned to work four months after giving birth to her daughter Shiloh in order to begin filming A Mighty Heart (2007)."</item>
		<item>"When Jolie and Billy Bob Thornton first married, the couple moved into the Beverly Hills home formerly owned by Guns N' Roses guitarist Slash. [2000]"</item>
		<item>"Her natural hair color is dark blonde."</item>
		<item>"Was in consideration for the role of Natasha Rushman/Black Widow in Iron Man 2 (2010) after Emily Blunt dropped out of the project, but Scarlett Johansson was cast instead."</item>
		<item>"Replaced Charlize Theron as Elise in The Tourist (2010) shortly before filming began."</item>
		<item>"Was originally cast as Dagny Taggart in Atlas Shrugged: Part I (2011) before being replaced by Charlize Theron, who in turn was replaced by Taylor Schilling."</item>
		<item>"Was two months pregnant with twins Knox and Vivienne when she completed filming on Changeling (2008)."</item>
		<item>"Was six months pregnant with her daughter Shiloh when she completed filming on The Good Shepherd (2006)."</item>
		<item>"Was in consideration for the role of Ryan in Gravity (2012/I) but Sandra Bullock was cast instead."</item>
		<item>"Was born Angelina Jolie Voight, however in 2002 she dropped her surname \"Voight\" and began using her middle name \"Jolie.\"."</item>
		<item>"In March 1999 it was reported by People magazine that she would star as one of the three title characters in Charlie's Angels (2000) opposite Cameron Diaz and Drew Barrymore. However, she left the project shortly before production began and Lucy Liu was cast instead."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
