<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Jennifer Lopez was born in July 24, 1969 in the Bronx, NYC."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer Lopez is an American actress, singer, record producer, dancer, fashion designer and television producer."</item>
	<item>"In May 2001, Jennifer took part in a White House benefit for UNICEF, assisting magician David Copperfield with an illusion where it appeared that he sawed her into six pieces."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer and her babies were featured on the front cover of the March 21, 2008 issue of People when her twins were a month old. People magazine paid $6 million for the exclusive pictures of the new babies."</item>
	<item>"At the 2007 American Music Awards, Jennifer was chosen as the Favorite Latin Music Artist."</item>
	<item>"Even though Jennifer was raised by Puerto Rican immigrants, she struggles to speak in Spanish."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer and husband Marc Anthony are the parents of fraternal twins, Emme Maribel Muñiz, born at 12:12 am and Maximilian \"Max\" David Muñiz, born at 12:13 am in Long Island N.Y. on February 22, 2008 by C-section. "</item>
	<item>"As of 2007, Jennifer was the richest Hispanic in Hollywood according to Forbes Magazine."</item>
	<item>"In the year 2001, Jennifer was voted #1 in FHM's \"100 Sexiest Women\" list. Jennifer has the honor of being the only woman to have been voted the sexiest woman in the world twice in FHM."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer became the first Latina actress to be paid $1 million for a movie role. She was paid this amount for the movie Selena in 1997."</item>
	<item>"2001 - #1 position \"100 Sexiest Women in the World\"."</item>
	<item>"2007 - #40 position \"100 Sexiest Women in the World\"."</item>
	<item>"2008 - #11 position \"The 50 most glamorous women of '08\"."</item>
	<item>"2008 - #11 position \"100 Most Influential Hispanics\"."</item>
	<item>"2009 - #11 position \"100 Hottest Brunettes of AIM\"."</item>
	<item>"In November 2006, Jennifer attended the Accessories Council’s ACE Awards, where she was honoured for her J.Lo clothing and accessories line."</item>
	<item>"A man who was arrested after he and an accomplice tried to sell Marc and Jennifer's stolen wedding video back to the couple for $1.37 million, pleaded guilty to attempted grand larceny in July 2006."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer joined the long list of celebrities lampooned by South Park. It happened in the South Park episode 101, entitled Fat Butt and Pancake Head."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer is the executive producer of the UPN show South Beach. Her production company is called Nuyorican Productions."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer has a Pasadena restaurant named Madre's."</item>
	<item>"On The 6, the name of Jennifer's debut album, stands for the 6 train she took from the Bronx to Manhattan. The album was certified 3x platinum."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer has been under attack from PETA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) and other animal rights organization because of the use of animal fur and skin in her clothing line."</item>
	<item>"Jennifers range of perfume scents include: Glow, Miami Glow, and Still."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer says that I'm Real was one of her favourite videos to make."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was married to Ojani Noa, from February 22, 1997 to 1998."</item>
	<item>"She used to date singer Puff Daddy or P. Diddy from 1999-2001."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was married to Chris Judd, from September 29, 2001 to January 2003."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer's height is 5 feet 6 inches (1.68 metres)."</item>
	<item>"She wears a size 6 shoe."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer attended Baruch College in New York."</item>
	<item>"Lopez was the middle child of three musically talented sisters."</item>
	<item>"Both of J.Lo’s parents were born in Ponce, Puerto Rico."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer knew from a young age that she would be a superstar one day."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer Lopez got her \"in\" in the entertainment industry when she was offered a job as a fly girl on Fox’s hit comedy \"In Living Color\" in 1990."</item>
	<item>"Lopez and Anthony married on June 5, 2004, less than a week after his divorce from Dayanara Torres."</item>
	<item>"As of 2007, Jennifer is the richest Hispanic in Hollywood according to Forbes Magazine."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer is well-known for dating actor Ben Affleck, earning the nickname \"Bennifer\"."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer picked up her popular nickname \"JLO\" after a fan had made it up and called her it."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer is nicknamed "The Supernova" by her friends."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer's nicknames are \"J. Lo\", \"La Lopez\", and \"Jenny\"."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer became the first Latina actress to be paid $1 million for a movie role."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer attended an all-girls catholic highschool."</item> 
	<item>"Jennifer was one of the \"Fly Girls\" dancers on the TV comedy series \"In Living Color\"."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer’s nickname at the gyms was \"La Guitarra\" because her body curved like a guitar."</item>
	<item>"J.Lo moved to Manhattan to learn how to dance and would sleep in the studio where she was practicing."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer worked with Janet Jackson on the video \"That’s The Way Love Goes\" and on Janet’s tours."</item>
	<item>"J.Lo was the first actress to have a movie (\"The Wedding Planner\")and an album hit number one in the same week."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer is the only woman to twice be voted FHM’s Sexiest Woman in the World."</item>
	<item>"One of Jen’s first dancing gigs was as a backup dancer for New Kids on the Block during their AMA performance in the late 1980s."</item>
	<item>"J.Lo didn’t return to work until 15 months after giving birth to twins Max and Emme."</item>
	<item>"Lopez announced on the last night of her “En Concierto” tour (before a crowd of fans) that she and hubby Marc Anthony were expecting twins!"</item>
	<item>"She had been nominated for Golden Globe and Grammy Award."</item>
	<item>"Lopez made her debut in the big screen in the 1995 drama My Family and then appeared opposite Wesley Snipes in the action film Money Train."</item>
	<item>"She played roles in Francis Ford Coppola's 1996 comedy Jack starring Robin Williams, and the 1997 thriller Blood and Wine with Jack Nicholson."</item>
	<item>"Lopez's debut album, released on June 1, 1999, and On the 6, a reference to the 6 subway line she used to take growing up in Castle Hill reached the top ten of the Billboard 200."</item>
	<item>"Her parents were very strict, they were not allowed to miss one day of work, school, or church"</item>
	<item>"In 2000, she appeared at the Grammy Awards wearing only a skimpy peacock-colored dress, which she is famously remembered for."</item>
	<item>"In March 2007 it was revealed that Jennifer would appear on American Idol and sing on a Latin album themed night."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer has been doing huge renovations in her shared mansion with husband Marc Anthony, to get rid of all remnants of his ex-wife Dayanara Torres."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer skipped a charity event for under-privileged children to get married to Marc Anthony."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was nominated for \"Worst Actress\" for Maid In Manhattan and Enough at the 23rd Annual Razzie Awards."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was paid $15,000,000 for Monster-in-Law (2004)."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was voted 18th as one of the \"Greatest Pop Culture Icon of All Time\" in an UK poll."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer was voted number 1 in the People en Espanol's list of 100 Most Influential Hispanics in its February issue which pays tribute to Hispanics who have had an impact on their communities."</item>
	<item>"Jennifer will be designing a fashion line for animals."</item>
	<item>"On The 6, the name of Jennifer's debut album, stands for the 6 train she took from the Bronx to Manhattan."</item>
	<item>"She financed singing and dancing at age 16."</item>
	<item>"She started in TV as a video girl for M C Hammer."</item>
	<item>"She sold nearly 50 million records worldwide."</item>
	<item>"Owns a home in Old Westbury - Long Island, New York."</item>
	<item>"Grew up blocks away from actor, Mills Pierre, where they both took classes at Kips Bay Boys and Girls Club."</item>
	<item>"Years before they married (or even became a couple), she and Marc Anthony sang a song together called \"No Me Ames\" which appeared on her album "On the 6""</item>
	<item>"Her mother won a $2.4-million jackpot at the Borgata Casino in Atlantic City, New Jersey in April 2004."</item>
	<item>"Stepmom of her husband Marc's 3 children Ariana, Cristian and Ryan."</item>
	<item>"Wore a Vera Wang gown to her June 2004 wedding to Marc Anthony."</item>
	<item>"Chosen by \"People\" magazine as one of the 50 Most Beautiful People in the World. [1997]"</item>
	<item>"Does not drink alcohol."</item>
	<item>"Sister Linda López is an Entertainment Correspondent for WB Network Channel 11 News in New York."</item>
	<item>"Voted the #1 best female body in \"Celebrity Bodies\" (UK) magazine. [October 2001]"</item>
	<item>"Was one of the guests at Tom Cruise's and Katie Holmes wedding ceremony in Italy."</item>
	<item>"Named one of E!'s \"Top 20 Entertainers of 2001\"."</item>
	<item>"She loves NY and Miami"</item>
	

</string-array>
</resources>
