<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Pink's Live in Australia DVD became the highest selling DVD in Australian history, selling 170,000 copies in pre-orders alone. It is currently certified 28 times platinum in Australia."</item>
		<item>"After months of speculation, Pink confirmed on the Ellen DeGeneres Show that she is pregnant with her first child on the 17 November 2010. She stated that she was nervous about discussing the pregnancy, as she had had a miscarriage before."</item>
		<item>"After 11 sold out concerts in Brisbane during her Funhouse Tour, Pink had a bathroom named in her honour, which she signed \"Don`t forget to wipe\"."</item>
		<item>"On 15 July 2010, Pink suffered an on-stage accident where she was dragged off stage and thrown against a steel barrier, due to her harness not properly connected. The show ended immediately and she was rushed to hospital, however was soon released and did not suffer any injuries."</item>
		<item>"During Pink`s Show on May 1 during \'Glitter in the Air\', she slipped while the ribbon was been lifted into the air. So instead of singing, \"Have you ever felt this way?\", she sang, \"Have you ever felt... Scared sh*tless? .... If I had fell, would you have laughed?\""</item>
		<item>"Pink is left-handed."</item>
		<item>"Funhouse has been certified 5 times Platinum in Australia with 418, 826 albums been sold."</item>
		<item>"Pink originally wanted to name her new album Heartbreak is a Motherf*cker but the record label rejected the name because of fear that sales would be down due to offensive language."</item>
		<item>"Pink's Live in Europe DVD became the 6th highest selling DVD for 2007 in Australia. "</item>
		<item>"In 2002, Pink won an award for \"The Best Belly Button\", at the Conexion MTV Awards, in Latin America."</item>
		<item>"In Australia, Pink's album I'm Not Dead has been certified 8x Platinum, and has sold 560,000+ copies."</item>
		<item>"Just Like a Pill was Pink's first UK number-one hit."</item>
		<item>"When asked what her friends call her while appearing on Jimmy Kimmel Live, Pink said that her friends call her: Cheech, Chee-chee Marie, Fat momma, Pink, Alecia, Lesh, and Leech."</item>
		<item>"Pink lent her name to PlayStation to promote the special edition Pink PSP. "</item>
		<item>"In Australia, Pink's I'm Not Dead tour sold about 307,000 tickets, breaking Kylie Minogue's previous record. Altough only seven shows for the tour were announced for Australia, the demand was so high the the total amount of shows rose to thirty-seven. Majority of these shows were sold out."</item>
		<item>"According to Pink, her biggest influences include: Janis Joplin, Steven Tyler, Bad Religion, Mary J. Blige, Bob Marley, Billy Joel, Indigo Girls, Don McLean, 2Pac, The Notorious B.I.G."</item>
		<item>"Pink belonged to a band in high school called \"Middle Ground\"."</item>
		<item>"At the MTV Australia Video Music Awards, Pink won awards in the following categories: \"Best Female Artist\" - U + Ur Hand and \"Download of the Year\" - Who Knew."</item>
		<item>"Before releasing debut album, Pink did backing vocals for artists such as Diana Ross, Kenny Lattimore, Tevin Campbell and 98 Degrees."</item>
		<item>"Pink is an asthmatic."</item>
		<item>"In 2007 Pink's bulldog Elvis, who was a gift from long-time friend Lisa Marie Presley, drowned in her swimming pool."</item>
		<item>"Pink's favorite colors are green and pink."</item>
		<item>"Pink attended Central Bucks West High, graduating in the class of 1997."</item>
		<item>"Pink got engaged to Carey Hart on June 26th, 2005, but their marriage unfortunately broke up in 2008."</item>
		<item>"Pink follows a strict vegan lifestyle."</item>
		<item>"Pink dislikes horror movies."</item>
		<item>"Pink owns the piano that Linda Perry (of the 4 Non Blondes) composed all her music on."</item>
		<item>"Tattoos: on her shoulder (the guardian angel), on her wrist (what goes around comes around), on her left ankle (Chinese/Japanese symbol), on her right ankle (an anklet), on her inner left thigh ("Mr. Pink" or "Pink"), and on her hand (a red star between her index and thumb) and a barcode for her album M!ssundaztood on back of her neck."</item>
		<item>"Pink got her stage name from her rosy complexion and the Steve Buscemi character "Mr. Pink" from the movie Reservoir Dogs."</item>
		<item>"Pink was grounded as a child for watching MTV. Her parents believed the channel was inappropriate for children."</item>
		<item>"Pink's parents are James Moore and Judy Kugel. James is a Vietnam Veteran. Pink also has an older brother named Jason and is the second cousin of actress/singer Mandy Moore."</item>
		<item>"She released her first album called Can't Take Me Home in 2000."</item>
		<item>"In 2001 she released M!ssundaztood."</item>
		<item>"In 2003 she released Try This"</item>
		<item>"In 2006 she released I'm Not Dead"</item>
		<item>"In 2008 she released Funhouse "</item>
		<item>"Pink participates in the \"Speak No Evil\" ads in the fight to raise awareness for youth to fight AIDS."</item>	
		<item>"She was born as Alecia Moore, 8th September 1979, in Pennsylvania USA"</item>
		<item>"She is married to motocross rider Carey Hart."</item>
		<item>"She wrote her first song when she was 14."</item>
		<item>"Pink has sold over two million albums worldwide."</item>	
		<item>"Pink gets her name from, you guessed it, the colour of her hair."</item>
		<item>"When she was young, she used to sing 4 Non Blondes songs at open mike nights."</item>
		<item>"She has sung gospel in an all-black church."</item>
		<item>"She has worked at Pizza Hut, McDonald's, Wendy's, and a gas station."</item>
		<item>"That Pink doesn't know what the French words in 'Lady Marmalade' actually mean. \"I just know they're dirty\", she apparently said to Beyonce Knowles when asked!"</item>
		<item>"Pink donated the orange crocheted top and pink bra she wore in the video for her new single, "Get the Party Started," to a charity to be auctioned off, along with an outfit she wore to the MTV Video Music Awards in September."</item>
		<item>"Pink's name does not just refer to her hair, it was a childhood nickname before she dyed it!"</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
