<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"A fan of hers has been accused of stalking her parents and violating a court order by trying to contact her. (August 30, 2004)"</item>
		<item>"ASCAP Film and Television Music: Most Performed Song from a Motion Picture, Bruce Almighty, single I'm With You, 2004."</item>
		<item>"Avril and Deryck started dating since March 2004."</item>
		<item>"Avril and Deryck Whibley (of Sum 41) tied the knot on July 17 in Montecito, California."</item>
		<item>"Avril began skateboarding ever since she was 14 years old."</item>
		<item>"Avril calls Hilary Duff \"a goody two shoes\"."</item>
		<item>"Avril co-wrote Kelly Clarkson's song \"Breakaway\"."</item>
		<item>"Avril cried when she knew that she was punk'd by Ashton Kutcher. She said that they were all so mean to her."</item>
		<item>"Avril describes her first album as a pop album with 'a couple of rock songs on it,' and has indicated a desire to write more rock-oriented songs in the future."</item>
		<item>"Avril dropped out of school at grade 11."</item>
		<item>"Avril got the most awards in the MTV Asia 2003 awards show."</item>
		<item>"Avril had passion to do music since she was a very young girl."</item>
		<item>"Avril has a Condo in Toronto."</item>
		<item>"Avril has been immortalized with her very own computer virus -- the so-called Avril e-mail virus."</item>
		<item>"Avril has now 9 tatoos."</item>
		<item>"Avril has played hockey since she was a kid."</item>
		<item>"Avril is #35 in Maxim Hot 100 list of 2006."</item>
		<item>"Avril is 5'4" tall."</item>
		<item>"Avril is a Canadian."</item>
		<item>"Avril is a Christian."</item>
		<item>"Avril is in Butch Walker's video for his song Bethamphetamine."</item>
		<item>"Avril is signed to Arista Records."</item>
		<item>"Avril Lavigne broke a record set by Madonna. Her song \"Complicated\" held the number one spot on the Contemporary Hit Radio chart."</item>
		<item>"Avril Lavigne has made it to the list of FHM 100 Sexiest Women in the World for three consecutive years, 2003, 2004 and 2005."</item>
		<item>"Avril Lavigne Stays fit by doing 50 Push-Ups and 100 Sit-Ups everyday."</item>
		<item>"Avril lived in NYC for 6 months when she was sixteen."</item>
		<item>"Avril lived with Chantal Kreviazuk and Raine Maida for 7 months, while working on her new album, Under My Skin. Chantal also co-wrote 7 of the new songs."</item>
		<item>"Avril once admitted to never having heard of the Sex Pistols."</item>
		<item>"Avril owns over a 100 pairs of Converse sneakers."</item>
		<item>"Avril racked up multi-platinum sales with her debut disc, Let Go, and has already developed a fervent, mostly female following."</item>
		<item>"Avril recently dyed her hair blonde and has two tattoos."</item>
		<item>"Avril refuses to do lip-sync, she always sings live."</item>
		<item>"Avril said that she played hockey better than some guys when she was back in high school."</item>
		<item>"Avril says that the most important thing to a successful hotel is the room service."</item>
		<item>"Avril started playing guitar when she was about 10 years old."</item>
		<item>"Avril was in Treble Charger's video, Hundred Million."</item>
		<item>"Avril was not born in Napanee but she grew up there."</item>
		<item>"Avril was the winner for "Favorite Female Singer" at the Kids Choice Awards in 2005."</item>
		<item>"Avril went to Cornerstone Christian Academy when she was in Napanee, Ontario and she excelled in track and field."</item>
		<item>"Avril will do the voice of Heather in the upcoming movie Over the Hedge."</item>
		<item>"Avril won the 'New Artist in a Video' award for her song 'Complicated' at the 2002 VMA."</item>
		<item>"Avril won Video Music Awards: New Artist in a Video, Complicated, 2002."</item>
		<item>"Avril wrote a song for her grandpa who passed away, the song called Slipped Away, it's in her second album Under My Skin."</item>
		<item>"Avril's dad worked at the phone company."</item>
		<item>"Avril's debut album Let Go has gone double platinum."</item>
		<item>"Avril's dog's name is Samuel. Sam for short."</item>
		<item>"Avril's ex bandmates are Evan Taubenfeld and Jesse Colburn."</item>
		<item>"Avril's eye color is blue. "</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite actor is Tobey Maguire."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite actress is Sandra Bullock."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite bands are Pennywise, Green Day, the Distillers, Linkin Park."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite candy is Pixe Stix."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite colors are black and red."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite food is pizza with a lot of olives."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite movies are Miss Congeniality and 8 Mile."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite musicians are Sum 41, Beach Boys, Alanis Morissette, Goo Goo Dolls, Matchbox 20, System of a Down."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite song from her second album, Under My Skin is Together."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite song in Let Go, her first album is Losing Grip."</item>
		<item>"Avril's favorite song is Iris by Goo Goo Dolls."</item>
		<item>"Avril's first music video, Complicated, cost over a million dollars."</item>
		<item>"Avril's first single is Complicated."</item>
		<item>"Avril's hobbies are writing songs, skateboarding, and singing. "</item>
		<item>"Avril's name is taken from a French word which means April."</item>
		<item>"Avril's song, I'm With You is featured on Ultimate Smash Hits. (June 3, 2003)"</item>
		<item>"Avril's younger sister appeared in her Sk8er Boi video."</item>
		<item>"Became engaged to Deryck Whibley on June 25, 2005."</item>
		<item>"Birthday: 09/27/1984."</item>
		<item>"Birthplace: Napanee, Ontario, Canada"</item>
		<item>"Common Sense Media: Excellence in Family Entertainment, 2004."</item>
		<item>"Donates many items to Rocky Stone to be given to less fortunate kids as part of the Toy Mountain Campaign 2004."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Brands of clothes : Dickies, Osiris (shoes). "</item>
		<item>"Favorite music videos : Her own video \"Sk8er Boi\" , another one \"Complicated\", and Blink 182's \"All The Small Things\" and \"Rock Show\"."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Place To Tour : New Zealand, Sardinia, Amsterdam."</item>
		<item>"Hair color : Brown (now blonde) "</item>
		<item>"Has a pizza named after her at a restaurant in her home town."</item>
		<item>"Has an older brother named Matt and a younger sister named Michelle."</item>
		<item>"Her wedding dress was designed by Vera Wang."</item>
		<item>"If Avril wasn't a singer, she'd be a police officer."</item>
		<item>"In late 2004, she had a small pink heart-shaped tattoo featuring the letter D applied to her right wrist and thought to be a reference to boyfriend Deryck Whibley. "</item>
		<item>"In the Maxim October 2004 edition which has Avril pic as the cover it was actually written Rocktober 2004 not October."</item>
		<item>"Is at the center of a row with bosses at MTV after she stuck her middle finger up live on air on Total Request Live. (May 29, 2004)"</item>
		<item>"Lavigne has a star tattooed on the inside of her left wrist, applied at the same time as friend and musical associate Ben Moody's identical tattoo."</item>
		<item>"MTV Asia: Favorite Female Artist, Favorite Breakthrough Artist and The Style Award, 2003."</item>
		<item>"MuchMusic Awards: People's Choice Favourite Canadian Artist (Don't Tell Me) (2004) "</item>
		<item>"Named to Teen People's list of Hottest Stars Under 25."</item>
		<item>"People call her \"Av\"."</item>
		<item>"Piercings: Navel (Inny), 2 in one ear, one in the other."</item>
		<item>"Plays the Guitar, Piano and Drums."</item>
		<item>"Real Name: Avril Ramona Lavigne "</item>
		<item>"She says she misses Canada a lot when she is away from home, and she said she's really proud to be Canadian. "</item>
		<item>"She taught herself to play guitar using her dad's guitar. "</item>
		<item>"She was a middle child and she tried to get attention when it wasn't on her."</item>
		<item>"She was kind enough to donate many items to Rocky Stone to be given to less fortunate kids as part of the Toy Mountain Campaign 2004."</item>
		<item>"Sign: Libra "</item>
		<item>"The first magazine to have Avril Lavigne on it is What Magazine."</item>
		<item>"The position Avril plays in hockey: right wing and center."</item>
		<item>"The way you pronounce her last name is \"lah-veen\"."</item>
		<item>"Two hours before a show in Dublin, Avril found out that her Grandpa passed away."</item>
		<item>"While in a hockey game Avril went around the net and punch the goalie and they started to fight."</item>
		<item>"Sing a song in the upcoming movie \"Rick Hansen: Heart of a Dragon\"."</item>
		

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
