<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"The one bad bitches call super duper lame, now super duper fame, gets me super duper brain."</item>
		<item>"The ones that make it complicated never get congratulated."</item>
		<item>"Maybe if I was a jerk to girls, instead of being nice and speakin kind words, then maybe it would be ok to say then....I wasn't the good guy to begin with."</item>
		<item>"Ive got some issues that nobody can see and all of these emotions are pouring out of me."</item>
		<item>"I got 99 problems and they all bitches."</item>
		<item>"The moon will illuminate my room and soon I'm consumed by my doom."</item>
		<item>"The devil in the hot pink dress tryna ask me for one dance, he think he slick but my guardians protect me from his wrath."</item>
		<item>"Sir you look high...I know but I prefer my eyes low"</item>
		<item>"I am the lone wolf go where I wanna"</item>
		<item>"I am happy, thats just the saddest lie"</item>
		<item>"Please save a kid that needs some help, I can't see ahead of me so I move in stealth."</item>
		<item>"What a world that im livin in, when do rain storms ever end?"</item>
		<item>"I hit her up, I say what up? She says the sky. I say whats good? She say McDonalds apple pie."</item>
		<item>"The one bad bitches, call super duper lame, now super duper fame , gets me super duper brain."</item>
		<item>"Why cant everyone get a bong?"</item>
		<item>"Ive got some issues that nobody can see. And all of these emotions are pouring out of me."</item>
		<item>"It don't really matter just where you from, All that really matter is where you're goin'."</item>
		<item>"And I try to piece the puzzle of the universe, Split an eight of shrooms just so I could see the universe!"</item>
		<item>"The moon will illuminate my room and soon i'm consumed by my doom."</item>
		<item>"And the devil in the hot pink dress tryna ask me for one dance, he think he slick but my guardians protect me from his wrath."</item>
		<item>"This is just the first step, God walks with me, but I'm still vexed"</item>
		<item>"Imma do just what I want.. looking ahead, no turning back."</item>
		<item>"I have my life and I will live it Shut your mouth before I fuck it Ha, my jokes they will love it"</item>
		<item>"I know it's easy to imagine, But it's easier to just do, See, if you can't do what you imagine, then what is imagination to you?"</item>
		<item>"Your fate shall be whatever it shall be (be, be, be,be) We'll fight no more, I let these just things be (be, be, be,be)"</item>
		<item>"Gettin' brain in the library cause I love knowledge. When you use your Medulla Oblongata And give me scoliosis until I comatoses And do it while I sleep yeah a little osmosis"</item>
		<item>"And if I die before I wake, I pray the lord my soul to take But please don't cry, just know that I have made these songs for you"</item>
		<item>"Ignorance to cope, man ignorance is bliss, ignorance is love and i need that shit"</item>
		<item>"I am happy, thats just the saddest lie."</item>
		<item>"I was late damn near every day, But Imma be on time when the stars align When my soul was happy."</item>
		<item>"Maybe if I was a jerk to girls, instead of bein nice and speakin kind words, then maybe it would be ok to say then....I wasnt the good guy to begin with"</item>
		<item>"I keep my girls short, sweet, thick and petite."</item>
		<item>"Why must it feel so wrong, when I try and do right, do right?"</item>
		<item>"Soaring through paradise when I'm closing my eyes."</item>
		<item>"I guess if I was simple in the mind, everything would be fine"</item>
		<item>"Weird itself, even in the dictionary, is just something that is different and unexplainable. A weirdo is someone who follows their heart. Im definitely weird, aint nothing wrong with that."</item>
		<item>"Girls that I dated, it's ok I am not mad yo Unless you stabbed me in the heart, no love ho."</item>
		<item>"Gotta terminate the hate spread the positive, without it bein whack and cheesy to the little kids."</item>
		<item>"Dim them lights get it in pimp tight do wat i do i lace up my own nikes."</item>
		<item>"Who gives a shit what people talkin bout fam, Haters shake my hand but i keep the sanitizer on deck!"</item>
		<item>"I'ma say some shit that make you think I lost my mind I'm the only nigga that could watch the sun and don't go blind."</item>
		<item>"Feelin' like im peter pan, minus the tights and the fairies."</item>
		<item>"I get in their head.. they dont even see my bread.. Oh sooo, Oh so fly.. cool as i wana be, one hell of a guy."</item>
		<item>"In my mind... its sounds like oooooouuuuu!! when im goone.. it feels like oooooouuu!! when im zoned. . . im feelin alright!!!!! i forget about it alll...."</item>
		<item>"I'm a cancerous lump in the throat of the game, any hatin nigga's kemo flow can never intervene."</item>
		<item>"I'm walkin with the heart of a lion. . . yeahh!!"</item>
		<item>"Feel so cursed cuz i cant stop a curse from spitting, without feeling like im phony, cuz i speak my thoughts everytime i think them up.. i gaurantee you i will win.. if i was ever wrong, this moment aint it."</item>
		<item>"Cuz IM super-cut-lery-alistic-leaner-allidoscious.. in rap ferocious, i be coachin the league...blood sweat and tears homie im made of it"</item>
		<item>"Wised up, now i want a dame.. nice butt, rollin in the range.. love me, even when im broke.. stay wit me, n never let me go"</item>
		<item>"Soaring through.. paradise.. when im closing my eyes.. Im.. MR. SOLO DOLO."</item>
		<item>"Your cool, your cool, Fuck you!... and to the bitch that. Oh yea fuck you too!!"</item>
		<item>"Play it back from the top if you recognize real."</item>
		<item>"Take a bit, Little bit, Roll it up, Take a hit, feeling lit, feeling right, 2AM Summer night."</item>
		<item>"And if i die before i awake i pray to the lord my soul to take but please dont just know that i have made these songs for you."</item>
		<item>"But Man Ol' Girl Gotta Phat Ol' Ass....Yea The Type To Make You Tell A Bitch Just Dance."</item>
		<item>"Step up in the place, just me nd my budddy.. everywhere i go they screamin out KID CUDI!!!!!"</item>
		<item>"The girl he wants dont seem to want him too, it seems the feelings that she had are through.. through."</item>
		<item>"Do you wana be him? think twice, you'll commit suicide tryna read my mind."</item>
		<item>"People tell me slow my roll.. im screamin out.. FUCK THAT!!"</item>
		<item>"I be posted with my blunt and a brew my dude"</item>
		<item>"Im so gone man im never alert, but it feels so good... no more hurt."</item>
		<item>"In my place no hate shall enter, ivin high up there up there, loatin floatin hopin i can find peace somewhere."</item>
		<item>"Of course im gonna sound suicidal when damn near everything else sounds like cheese balls."</item>
		<item>"Girls stay a mile away, do the single lady dance by them otha motha fcukas, not me."</item>
		<item>"I could find peace somewhere."</item>
		<item>"I'm somethin different in all aspects, Don't want a woman just to love her assets, I Still wife her up even with her flat chest, The type to get hurt, But that's the past tense."</item>
		<item>"People told me slow my roll I'm screaming out fuck that, Imma do just what I want lookin ahead no turnin back, if I fall if I die know I lived it to the fullest, if I fall if I die know I lived and missed some bullets."</item>
		<item>"For even in hell i still have faith ,to one day be free with my father at the gates."</item>
		<item>"People tell me slow my role am yelling out fuck that, am do just what i want."</item>
		<item>"I got 99 problems, nd they all b*tches, feelin' like jigga man, care free livin'."</item>
		<item>"Struggle is the enemy, but weed is the remedy."</item>
		<item>"They can't comprehend, or even come close to understandin him. I guess if I was borin they would love me more, guess if I was simple in the mind everything would be fine."</item>
		<item>"I'm cooler than a polar bears toes, cleveland is the reason."</item>
		<item>"What can be better than this right now? You know what Im saying? Cafe, con leche in hand, money in my pocket. Life is good my friend-kid cudi as domingo dean."</item>
		<item>"Puff puff pass wit cha b*tch ass, Back in High School smoke week when I cut class, And now I'm an addict."</item>
		<item>"I was high when I finally had the chance to see, Everything thats pretty aint always good for me."</item>
		<item>"In my zone, I'm feelin' alright, I'm Feelin' Alright, I forget about it all."</item>
		<item>"Time to terminate the hate spread the positive!"</item>
		<item>"Dope, Mr. Solo Dolo."</item>
		<item>"Maybe a little weed to intensify the scene, To provide a solid answer to the question why I lean? A boneafide fiend that be taking by the beams of light, Man on the moon aint a name, its a way of life."</item>
		<item>"Ignorance to cope man, Ignorance is bliss, Ignorance is love, and I need that shit."</item>
		<item>"Imma be gone way past November, even stay up there, up there, floatin', Floatin', hopin' I will find peace somewhere."</item>
		<item>"Dream as if you'll live forever, live as if you'll die today."</item>
		<item>"Living life is a choice, making a differences in someone else's isn't."</item>
		<item>"The first step I ever took alone made me realize the prince was made for the throne."</item>
		<item>"I'm psychic in the end, I fake my thoughts and reality lets them in."</item>
		<item>"A whole new Cudder for the new class."</item>
		<item>"Smoking so much weed I am better off alone, I'm in my own zone."</item>
		<item>"I guarantee you I will win if I was ever wrong this moment ain't it."</item>
		<item>"I can't disappear the stress my life's way beyond yo mama knows best."</item>
		<item>"I never gave a FUCK. I never gave a FUCK about what people thought about me. I mean I did, but FUCK it you know what I'm sayin'?"</item>
		<item>"Greetin' my niggas wit' dap and pounds, So if I fall I won't hit the ground, These are the things that'll make me smile, Knowin' this blunt might burn a while."</item>
		<item>"Only things that calm me down is pussy and some cali trees!"</item>
		<item>"I be low, when i see that im a different dude."</item>
		<item>"Remember your not strange, but your not the same man."</item>
		<item>"Girls that I dated, it's ok I am not mad yo Unless you stabbed me in the heart, no love ho."</item>
		<item>"My mind runs I can never catch it even if I got a head start."</item>
		<item>"(Sir you look high) i know, but i prefer my eyes low."</item>
		<item>"The moon will illuminate my room and soon i'm consumed by my doom."</item>
		<item>"Red Rum them tryin to figure out him, baptize myself in a river hennessy."</item>
		<item>"I never was the shoulda coulda woulda type, I am in control of what the people say they like."</item>
		<item>"Life is short and filled lots of grief and doubt so I just pull that bag of colorful frosty leaves on out and free my scalp."</item>
		<item>"Can't believe how I had the dream of Martin King, but they ain't takin me out on no balcony."</item>
		<item>"After LeBron, I'm what's next."</item>
		<item>"If I die today the last thing you remember won't, Be about some apple bottom jeans with the boots with the fur, Baby how I dream of being free since my birth."</item>
		<item>"Remember you're not strange, but you are not the same."</item>
		<item>"I'll never get why the earth is a puzzle that i'll never fit."</item>
		<item>"Once upon a time nobody gave a fuck."</item>
		<item>"Embrace the Martian, embrace the Martian."</item>
		<item>"Knock knock Cudi open up it's Chip, gotta kush pack shells and some Henny would could sip."</item>
		<item>"So if I slip away, if I die today, the last thing you remember won't be about some apple-bottom jeans with the boats with the fur..."</item>
		<item>"These are the things that make me smile, knowing this blunt might burn for a while..."</item>
		<item>"Haters shake my hands but I keep that sanitizer on deck."</item>
		<item>"If I fall, if I die, know I lived it to the fullest If I fall, if I die, know I lived and missed some bullets."</item>
		<item>"I keep my self so lifted I am a custom to new height."</item>
		<item>"People told me slow my road, im screaming out fuck that, ima do just what i want lookin ahead no turnin back."</item>
		<item>"Tell 'em motherfuckers that somebody once told me if you get high still strive to be somebody."</item>
		<item>"Feelin like im peter pan, minus the tights and the fairies."</item>
		<item>"I've got some issues that nobody can see, and all these emotions are pouring out of me."</item>
		<item>"You don't really care about the trials of tomorrow, rather lay awake in a bed full of sorrow."</item>
		<item>"'ma say some shit that make you think I lost my mind, I'm the only nigga that could watch the sun and don't go blind."</item>
		<item>"I never let a motherfucka break me dogg who gives a fuck if a nigga don't like your steez tell em to buzz off your n-u-tz."</item>
		<item>"It don't matter your race just take a blunt to the face."</item>
		<item>"All i do is make it simple, the ones who make it complicated never get congratulated."</item>
		<item>"It's like I playin all my stuff for everybody, all the people givin me feedback, and they be like Why you shit sound so different like its a bad thing, and I say, Why not.....nigga haha."</item>
		<item>"Guess If I was simple in the mind everythin would be fine."</item>
		<item>"Salutations to all, You can call me Cudi. Or Mr. Extravagant, cause I'm keepin' my money."</item>
		<item>"Dim them lights get it in pimp tight do wat I do I lace up my own nikes."</item>
		<item>"Shut your mouth before I fuck it."</item>
		<item>"Please save me lord, my life is such a chore. But I, I need this to be ok, be ok. what, what they think of me it aint no thing. my heart, heart is broke completely."</item>
		<item>"They can't comprehend or even come close to understanding him. I guess if i was boring they would love me more. Guess if i was simple in the mind everything would be fine."</item>
		<item>"So a red bull and a blunt would be fine, just wanna feel fine, just wanna kill time, just wanna relax and think of a rhyme."</item>
		<item>"The pain is deep. A silent sleeper you won't hear a peep, peep. The girl he wants don't seem to want him too. It seems the feelings that she had are through, through."</item>
		<item>"I like when you talk because your voice is angel-ess, I want to kiss you on your space below the navel at the place that you keep me so moist like a towelet."</item>
		<item>"People told me slow my roll, I'm screaming out fuck that! imma do just what I want, lookin' ahead no turnin' back."</item>
		<item>"It don't matter your race just take a blunt to the face."</item>
		<item>"Sing along lil' mama you ain't gotta worry bout no drama no. I'll provide for friends and fam and fans cleveland city grinding man stay at flow the kids hope."</item>
		<item>"I've got some issues that nobody can see, and all these emotions are pouring out of me."</item>
		<item>"You don't really care about the trials of tomorrow rather lay awake in a bed full of sorrow."</item>
		<item>"You can look all over but you'll never find.. Hot shit like mine."</item>
		<item>"I keep myself so lifted , i am accustomed to new heights."</item>
		<item>"Way very far away. To another universe where all people say,Its a new new place for the special to embrace, like a martian who is seemingly wondered out of place."</item>
		<item>"Split an eighth of shrooms just so I could see the universe. I tried to think about myself as a sacrifice.Just to show the kids they ain't the only ones who up at night."</item>
		<item>"The moon will illuminate my room and soon I'm consumed by doom. Once upon a time nobody gave a fuck but when it's all said 'n' done my cocks been sucked."</item>
		<item>"But see i'll never get, why da earth is a puzzle that i'll never fit im outta their world."</item>
		<item>"What a world that Im livin in, will the rain storms ever end?"</item>
		<item>"Haters suck my balls, two time, I never say goodbye because Im on mine, All my life, wanna do something major, Now every little thing I do might make it in the paper."</item>
		<item>"People told me slow my road, im screaming out fuck thaat, ima do just what i want lookin ahead no turnin back."</item>
		<item>"Until you meet a kid like K I niggas thought i was crazy my momma knw i stay high we gettin money mom."</item>
		<item>"Please keep the bapes on my feet, so i can watch the devil ice grill me."</item>
		<item>"All the crazy shit I did tonight, Those'll be the best memories, I just wanna let it go for the night, That will be the best therapy for me."</item>
		<item>"And the weed is guranteed to be just what i need."</item>
		<item>"And now my face book poppin, cuz I told all the girls I would be the hot shit. One day, this will be my world."</item>
		<item>"You don't understand I don' need you honey, I beat my dick like it owe me money."</item>
		<item>"I'm cooler than a polar bears toes."</item>
		<item>"Dont give a shit what people talk about fam haters shake my hand but i keep the sanitizer on deck."</item>
		<item>"Why must it feel so wrong when I try and do right."</item>
		<item>"They say easy friend, there he go talking about weed again, probably cuz of all that weed in him."</item>
		<item>"New new place for the special to embrace, like a martian who seemingly wonder outta place, take what you need from the valley the hope."</item>
		<item>"But i was high, when i finally had the chance to see, everything thats pretty aint' always good for me."</item>
		<item>"I want to kiss you on your space below your navelette, that space that you keep neat, so moist like a towelette."</item>
		<item>"Wanna know really, really, really who I'm dating, Is she civilian or super duper famous? Is she African American, Caucasian, or Asian? Or maybe Spanish, it doesn't matter my nigga, I love them all."</item>
		<item>"I've been feelin some type of way about her, wanna wife her, borderline I don' really like her, cuz she like to play around nd she kno she got it."</item>
		<item>"Have just one more cap babe (babe), have just one more stem babe!"</item>
		<item>"Why Big Bro Take All The Hot Bitches..?! Dear God Me Too I Like The Hot Bitches..!"</item>
		<item>"I aint gotta wait for no one. If I want to fly, Ill fly for freedom, hey!"</item>
		<item>"So I cuss like a sailor and I smoke weed. I'm exactly what an older rapper's kid will be!"</item>
		<item>"Don't critique me b'. What i do doesnt reflect you."</item>
		<item>"My mind runs i can never catch even if i got a head start."</item>
		<item>"Have you ever heard of some shit so real? Beyond from the heart, from the soul you can feel."</item>
		<item>"I guess if I was borin they would love me more. Guess if I was simple in the mind, Everything would be fine."</item>
		<item>"People told meto slow my roll, I'm screamn out FUCK THAT. I'm a do just what I want looking forward no turning back!"</item>
		<item>"I smoke to get high becuz the world is so low."</item>
		<item>"I know its easy to imagine, but it's easier to just do. See if you cant do what you imagine, then what's imagination to you?"</item>
		<item>"Starrin' like a creeper cuz' you gotta keeper."</item>
		<item>"Imma show you how I be livin', from a long time ago, a young nigga, he was timid, now I'm in the zone, seein' things so vivid, Hide my soul?, nah homie, not even, Imma zone out till I lose feeling."</item>
		<item>"Super Duper K-I-D, I'm on another planet b."</item>
		<item>"Why yo shit so different?"</item>
		<item>"I'll be up up and away. up up and away, cause in the end they'll judge me anyways, so whatever."</item>
		<item>"Just a waste of space in your brain, to take the place of hate for things all the same."</item>
		<item>"Focus baby don't look at me, see right through me, understand my heartbeat murmurs to mock your rhythm,Yeah, my nuts, the other girls want em, But they can't have."</item>
		<item>"I cant feel the left side of my face stressful thoughts have been replaced with henny and coke and Jaeger."</item>
		<item>"Ignorance the coke man, ignorance is bliss, ignorance is love and I need that shit."</item>
		<item>"I am not a role model but i am the blueprint."</item>
		<item>"I'm on the pursuit of happiness and I know everything that shines ain't always gonna be gold. I'll be fine once I get it, I'll be good."</item>
		<item>"In the end they'll judge me anyway, so whatever."</item>
		<item>"Dont call me a rapper, I'm an artist. Update your minds. I 'INCORPORATE' hip hop elements because I am part MC, but I am all things musical. All things melodically beautiful."</item>
		<item>"They tell me all good things must end well those muthafucka's ain't have this friend"</item>
		<item>"Gentle with the drugs, heavy with the love"</item>
		<item>"I dont smoke weed anymore. Ill leave it to the kids. Im 27 with a business to run and I need to be alert and focused with my mind strong. For those who still get it on, smoke one in my memory as your favorite lonely stoner."</item>
		<item>"They trying to make me look like the poster boy for violence and ignorance, I tell motherfuckers I'm the poster boy for honesty, realness, anarchy, I don't give a fuck about this business."</item>
		<item>"The only three things a guy should want change to about his girl is her last name, address, and her viewpoint on men."</item>
		<item>"Every hit and every kick is rapid fire and my thoughts is sour if I feel there is no lighter."</item>
		<item>"Im aiming to break some bones. Im focused and overdosed on adrenaline and I strengthen them with confidence."</item>
		<item>"Pow Pow Pow I knock em down. I am flawless in every round."</item>
		<item>"Battle be strong the new kid. Dont matter my scars were leaking Ill be standing still demanding, Ill be winner. Rapid punches delivered."</item>
		<item>"I look into you toothless I tell you know whats your past. To try it, it would be stupid, your choice of technique is foolish."</item>
		<item>"No, no, no, I wont get bodied. My heart is powered with power from cowards."</item>
		<item>"I wont runaway. Cowards runaway."</item>
		<item>"Dont cry for me. It is my destiny to be where I am. I said listen to tick go tock on the bomb Waiting."</item>
		<item>"Seen things. Things that I wish I had not. No worries It is my destiny to be where I am. I said listen to tick go tock on the clock."</item>
		<item>"Perfect is the word. Its the main thing that the lost souls want."</item>
		<item>"Ballin so low most fools couldnt price me silently stunt, with a blunt full of p.e"</item>
		<item>"Wish I could tell my brother something for some motivation and get him out that gutter."</item>
		<item>"I can never let this be the end of days the end of dreams so sure Ill be ok my mind is stronger than yours, wait quicker no lie."</item>
		<item>"No lie some days are better days walking with my mind my heart will know the way."</item>
		<item>"Ive come to find out coming up my senses say to hide out so many alone insecurities see that checking in the mirror. Im a maniac I admit it, do you get it?"</item>
		<item>"I cant lie sometimes Im feeling low please get outta my mind. Imma find out which way to go I need to take control."</item>
		<item>"Maybe Im not exactly what you want me to be, maybe you need not worry bout me, baby."</item>
		<item>"Oooh, if youre looking for real love dont come around here."</item>
		<item>"No more chances if you blow this, you bogus I will never ever let you live this down, down, down."</item>
		<item>"Here, summon every single bit of courage. Im a Lion heart. They start it then I finish it."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
