<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Britney Spears was born Dec. 2, 1981 and is a Sagittarius.".</item>
		<item>"Her middle name is Jean."</item>
		<item>"She has one brother, Bryan, and one sister, Jamie Lynn."</item>
		<item>"She studied for three summers at the famous Professional Performing Arts School in New York."</item>
		<item>"Spears landed a spot on The New Mickey Mouse Club at age 11 and appeared on the show for 2 years."</item>
		<item>"Her first album, ...Baby One More Time, debuted in 1999 and sold more than 20 million copies."</item>
		<item>"Spears' first Grammy win came in 2003 for "Toxic," which was named the Best Dance Recording."</item>
		<item>"Spears is a Louisiana native and, in 2005, auctioned off many personal items and donated the proceeds to help victims of Hurricane Katrina."</item>
		<item>"She dated Justin Timberlake for several years before a very publicized breakup in 2002."</item>
		<item>"Spears married a childhood friend, Jason Alexander, in Las Vegas in 2004, but the marriage was annulled just a few days later."</item>
		<item>"In November of 2004, Spears married dancer Kevin Federline and they had two boys, Sean Preston (born in 2005) and Jayden James (born in 2006)."</item>
		<item>"The year 2006 marked the beginning of a series of erratic and dangerous behavior, from shaving her head to checking in and out of rehab. She lost custody of her children in 2007."</item>
		<item>"Her mother Lynne Irene Spears, is a former elementary school teacher."</item>
		<item>"Her father Jamie Lynn Spears, is a former building contractor and chef."</item>
		<item>"She was an accomplished gymnast, and attended classes until she was nine."</item>
		<item>"She has appeared in off-Broadway Productions."</item>
		<item>"In 1997, Spears was in the all-female group called Innosense."</item>
		<item>"Before the shaving head episode, Britney's aunt Sandra Bridges Covington, died of ovarian cancer, this was January 21, 2007. She is said to have been very close to her aunt."</item>
		<item>"Spears has a light soprano vocal range."</item>
		<item>"In 2008, Bronx's John Phillip Sousa Middle School, named their music studio after her. She was present during the ceremony and also donated $10,000 to the school's music program."</item>
		<item>"During the late 90's, Britney was known as the "Pop Princess" for all her hit singles including \"...Baby One More Time\"."</item>
		<item>"She has published four books, seven DVDs, and her self-produced reality series \"Britney and Kevin: Chaotic\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney has used the alias \"Alotta Warmheart\" when checking into hotels."</item>
		<item>"In her first starring role in film, Britney's character was supposed to swear. Britney ordered that the curse words be taken out so not to tarnish her image for the younger pre-teen viewers of her movie. "</item>
		<item>"In April 2007, Britney attended an LA Lakers game in disguise, but was caught by the paparazzi. She was wearing a giant Kobe Bryant jersey, a blonde wig and a giant pair of sunglasses."</item>
		<item>"Britney wrote the theme song to her sister Jamie Lynn's, Nickelodeon TV series Zoey 101."</item>
		<item>"When Britney was a child, she used to lock herself in the bathroom and sing to her dolls. After each song, she practiced smiling and blowing kisses to her doll audience."</item>
		<item>"Britney has an obsession with the late Princess Diana, and has started spending up on memorabilia."</item>
		<item>"Britney Spears shaved her head in 2007 at Esther’s Haircutting Studio in Tarzana."</item>
		<item>"For the 2000 MTV Video Music Awards she wore a nude colored outfit during her performance that sparked up controversy."</item>
		<item>"Spears also had a multi-million dollar deal with Pepsi."</item>
		<item>"Britney's favorite song is \"Toxic\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney Spears posed for her first major magazine publication, Rolling Stone in April 1999."</item>
		<item>"Britney has grossed over $185 million in merchandise from her tours, the most ever grossed by a performer (male and female)."</item>
		<item>"Britney has grossed over US$350 million from tour ticket sales."</item>
		<item>"Britney Spears has earned over US$370 million from her many, multi-million dollar advertisement and endorsement deals all around the World."</item>
		<item>"Britney won Best Female Video, Best Pop Video, and Video of The Year on the 2008 VMA. It was her first VMA win, after being nominated 16 times."</item>
		<item>"Although Britney was born in Louisiana, she went to Parklane Academy, a high school in McComb, Mississippi."</item>
		<item>"When Britney guest starred on an episode of How I Met Your Mother, on March 24, 2008, it gave the show it's highest ratings ever."</item>
		<item>"On February 23rd, 2008, Britney was reunited with her kids after not being able to seem then since January 3rd."</item>
		<item>"Many of Britney's fans call her \"Queen B\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney spent $3,000 on a Yorkie puppy she has named \"London\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney wears size six shoes."</item>
		<item>"Britney's first single, \"Baby One More Time\" was initially offered to TLC. TLC declined the song. The song was written by Martin Karl \"Max Martin\" Sandberg."</item>
		<item>"In January 2007, Britney launched a new fragrance called, \"Midnight Fantasy\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney checked out of Promises Rehab Center on March 21, 2007, after completing their month long treatment program."</item>
		<item>"As of February 2007, Britney has two new tattoos on her body: a pink pair of lips on her wrist and a black-and-white cross on her hip."</item>
		<item>"Britney has sold over eighty-three million records worldwide."</item>
		<item>"Britney and Paris Hilton topped Mr. Blackwell's 47th Annual Worst Dressed list."</item>
		<item>"In 2001, Britney turned down an offer from PETA to pose nude for their anti-fur campaign ad."</item>
		<item>"Britney lists Madonna and Mariah Carey as her idols."</item>
		<item>"Britney's trademarks are showing her midriff during performances and lip-synching and synthesizing vocals."</item>
		<item>"Britney's nicknames are Brit and Pinky."</item>
		<item>"In a close race, Britney beat out Paris Hilton in an Assoicated Press Poll for the Worst Role Model of 2006."</item>
		<item>"In December 2006, Britney got a new tattoo of a small black star inked on her right hand."</item>
		<item>"A day after Britney filed divorce papers, Kevin counter-filed papers, asking for spousal support and sole custody of the couple’s two children."</item>
		<item>"Britney asked Christina Aguilera and ex-boyfriend Justin Timberlake to be god parents to her second son, Jayden James."</item>
		<item>"Britney posed nude while she was pregnant for the August 2006 cover of Harper's Bazaar magazine."</item>
		<item>"Britney shares her birthday with Nelly Furtado, Lucy Liu and Gianni Versace."</item>
		<item>"In Britney’s Baby One More Time video, her love interest is played by her cousin."</item>
		<item>"Britney’s name is an anagram of \"Presbyterians\"."</item>
		<item>"When Britney gets angry and yells, Britney calls this alter-ego 'Mona Lisa'. Mona Lisa is credited as director for the music video Do Somethin'."</item>
		<item>"Britney auditioned to play Allie Nelson in The Notebook, but lost the part to Rachel McAdams."</item>
		<item>"In early 2006, Britney came under fire for driving when her son Sean Preston was pictured sitting in her lap while she was driving."</item>
		<item>"Britney hates flying on airplanes."</item>
		<item>"During her marriage to Kevin Federline, Britney would sometimes sign autographs as \"Britney Federline\", rather than \"Britney Spears\"."</item>
		<item>"Britney is 5' 5" (1.65 m) tall."</item>
		<item>"Britney is a believer in Kabbalah, a religion that has gained popularity in recent years, particularly with celebrities."</item>
		<item>"Britney enjoys shopping at Kitson, a trendy L.A. boutique. She enjoys their outrageous t-shirts."</item>
		<item>"When Britney was a child, she used to lock herself in the bathroom and sing to her dolls. After each song, she practiced smiling and blowing kisses to her doll audience."</item>
		<item>"In 2003, Britney was honored with a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame."</item>
		<item>"Britney set the record as the only solo female artist to have four consecutive albums debut at #1 on the Billboard Top 200 Album Charts."</item>
		<item>"Britney was spotted drinking and smoking on several occassions during her pregnancy."</item>
		<item>"Before Sean Preston was born, Britney spent more than $100,000 on the nursery for him."</item>
		<item>"Justin finally broke it off after Britney supposedly cheated on him. His hit song "Cry Me a River" is rumored to be about his feelings for Britney."</item>
		<item>"Britney Spears sang Naomi Judd's "Love Can Build a Bridge" on Star Search in 1992. She won the first round but lost in the second."</item>
		<item>"Britney Spears kept a tanning bed on her Baby One More Time tour bus."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
