<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Bitch I'm living everyday month yearly, yell until you motherfuckers hear me. We made it."</item>
		<item>"Fast girls, faster whip, big chains master shit."</item>
		<item>"See broads over niggas but business over broads. See business equals money and money's over all."</item>
		<item>"Used to ride escorts now I get escorted."</item>
		<item>"I need less friends more bread, less talk more head."</item>
		<item>"Hoes and passionate night gowns, but you the only one I imagined in white gowns, so with your left hand you should let me add a ring to it. Since mr and mrs anderson just has a ring to it."</item>
		<item>"Our relationship is not the only thing that's out of hand, she even called my momma like 'you need to get your man.'"</item>
		<item>"Bitch, I'm who they want be, want see, want see. Used to tell me everything I want be. You gon be, fucking with piranha's and they want eat. But somehow I just turn the tide like laundry."</item>
		<item>"See me I'm into hoes that's into hoes, So now I'm in two hoes."</item>
		<item>"I have been the realest since the doc came out umbilical, hundred inch dick yep and twenty pound genitals. So you gon have to stay there til my secretary tell you enter hoe."</item>
		<item>"Yeah this was meant to be, I came in the world knowing nothing was for free. So you gon pay for her and she gon pay for me. My life is the shit I guess that this was meant for me."</item>
		<item>"Getting money niggas think I joined Illuminati. Throwing West Side up I'm feeling like Killuminati. Now isn't it ironic that I'm in a big body ? Paranoid cause every rapper named Big got bodied."</item>
		<item>"Line after line after line after line.... barcode."</item>
		<item>"Workin grave yard shifts, cause we finna make a killin."</item>
		<item>"Paranoid because every rapper named Big got bodied and my bitch got body but she sitting in the back cuz my nigga called shotty."</item>
		<item>"I'm in love with tree, im an avatar."</item>
		<item>"All up in my room but I aint tryna roommate her, She all up in my drawers like like its room raiders."</item>
		<item>"If money equals power I'm a fuckin generator."</item>
		<item>"I'm smokin up on that tropical jolly green yea galopogos, rainbow chain on my neck look like a pot of gold."</item>
		<item>"100 inch dick, yup, and 20 pound genitals."</item>
		<item>"They say sky's the limit, how bitch? i'm moonwalking."</item>
		<item>"Tell a friend to tell a friend, to tell a bitch, to tell a hoe."</item>
		<item>"I fell asleep getting brain, that's a head rest!"</item>
		<item>"Big shit poppin, And Big's My first name."</item>
		<item>"I rise more than juries this is my story."</item>
		<item>"Pressure, pain, ache, struggle..This is my hustle."</item>
		<item>"Watch a nigga pull more strings than Lenny Kravitz."</item>
		<item>"Man, I'm so tired for praying for this free shit, And being broke as some weak shit. But thank god for that Micky D's, One dollar double cheese, Or something nice I don't wanna eat shit."</item>
		<item>"I'm grabbin' the fattest asses, just to see 'em shake. I swear I'm too real to be, I'm too real to be livin' so fake."</item>
		<item>"They say I'm too fake, fuck it I'm paid."</item>
		<item>"If you like my tattoos LA ink is in my closet. Got some haters in my closet and we just use them as targets. I be sparking cause we got a gun range all in my closet."</item>
		<item>"Gotta a zoo all in my closet yes I do yes, I do I got some gators, buffalo's, minks too, minks too."</item>
		<item>"Headaches every night a nigga get it from the drama, man if she don't make that money, she gon' take that money not from you, yeah she get it from your Honor."</item>
		<item>"I swear I goes to work on that pussy like she paid me to, d-d-dick her up and now she walkin' like she 82."</item>
		<item>"Man I break her heart everytime I change hoes. I make a new style every time I change clothes. Man they jock my rhymes every time I change flows."</item>
		<item>"Boy, priceless is affordable."</item>
		<item>"Nigga you on the side lines praying for an audible. Cause when your legendary everything is quotable."</item>
		<item>"All I think about is money and sex, fuckin and checks."</item>
		<item>"I hit you with an AMC, my nigga that's a full clip. And you could be like me if you just quit with all the bullshit."</item>
		<item>"I put it in her mouth and now that bitch look like a conehead."</item>
		<item>"I guess they on somthin cause my neck look like horizon. Just a million people behind me and I don't have verizon."</item>
		<item>"I glisten and shine with miss's fine model chick, Big behind, bad enough to skip the line. But to me she just a nine. I hop up out that double o you can call me Mr Bond."</item>
		<item>"Bitch I am a monster I belong on district 9."</item>
		<item>"You don't understand man I came from nothing. This what I dreamed about. This what we dreamed about."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I feel I'm working just to work harder. And then work harder then who worked the hardest. Man the life of a workeraholic .You either on your work or just workin on it."</item>
		<item>"I got a dream that's worth more then my reality. And pride that's worth more then a salary."</item>
		<item>"Went from intern to the owner of the building. Bussin nuts counting money like owe what a feelin."</item>
		<item>"All fucking hundreds so what's that like a zillion? Working grave yard shifts cause were fitten to make a killin."</item>
		<item>"See me as a meal ticket, but I'm no lunch line."</item>
		<item>"Whoever said the sky's the limit looking dumb, cause I'm 22 moon walking on the sun."</item>
		<item>"Are you willing to give up what you love, for who you love? Or lose your girlfriend to groupie love."</item>
		<item>"Everywhere I go I get a group of hugs, that's what happens when they need connections and you the plug."</item>
		<item>"Oh, that's your girl?"</item>
		<item>"Man, the realest nigga I know is inside the mirror bro. And these fools be trippin' like a suitcase, a shoelace, they too fake."</item>
		<item>"He ain't no hometown hero, he on that LeBron James shit."</item>
		<item>"What I got? everything! you was straight gassin, I put that on kerosine I just give her dick dog, you give her a wedding ring you need her at the alter now that is just embarassing."</item>
		<item>"Ay, now every time I stepped in you could tell I stepped out. I saw your girlfriend only from the chest down Im so dressed up but I pull her dress down, by the time she wake up, Im in the next town."</item>
		<item>"How my checks look, stupid as hell so tell me how my ex look, stupid as hell."</item>
		<item>"I-I Dont think they want it brand new whip but I push it like its stolen. 7-11 a n-gga keep rollin Im headed to the top bitch and I dont think you going."</item>
		<item>"I-I Dont think they want it your girls on my dick and she trying to sit up on it she hopped on my lap even took a pick up on it and I passed her to my n-ggas cause I dont really want it."</item>
		<item>"Killing sh-t lights on, lights on, lights off on my job bitch, no nights off and on my nights off, it still might cost."</item>
		<item>"I saw you perform yeah, you put on a light show. I walk up in this bitch looking like a light show got a team but Im by myself ISO."</item>
		<item>"I-I Dont think they want it. Soon as I walk in all the bad bitches on it."</item>
		<item>"Ay for real though, the number one question is: why is your girlfriend always where the sexing is?"</item>
		<item>"Flyer than a carry on, sipping on Perignon gripping on derriere, gripping off Derrion."</item>
		<item>"F-ck that, reflectin on the last chain I bought. They on my tracks, waitin on the next train of though."</item>
		<item>"Yall niggas make me realize how good almost isnt. Would hate to look back on my life and say I almost did it"</item>
		<item>"Man, Im chillin wit Jays, Yes, and Common Senses. Its crazy when legends are peers and your competition."</item>
		<item>"Boss player, collectin every single check thats owed out. Puttin on a show until everything is sold out."</item>
		<item>"Killin niggas at rap, but being the mans my specialty. I love shitting on all my exes especially."</item>
		<item>"Now, I cant tell whats a better accessory. My new watch, or the chick thats standin right next to me."</item>
		<item>"See, I done seen nights turn to day.s Love turn to hate, hugs turn to laids. Niggas turn to sirs, Andre to Spades. Cause when it turns real, thats when everybody turns fake."</item>
		<item>"Youre now rockin wit somebody on they f-ckin bidness. Watch me do it big, no pun intended."</item>
		<item>"I be up in the air, more than I do on the ground. My city is on my hat, and Im wearin it like a crown."</item>
		<item>"I hustle hard like Im finna lose the crib and party hard like Im finna do it big."</item>
		<item>"She put that thong on my groin groin and then it go boing! Got my fronter on her bumper does it look like she towing."</item>
		<item>"This looks like a job for Captain Planet Nah, nah, good lordy, wowdy, I just took more shot than Kobe. The realest niggas is reppin The baddest bitches promoting."</item>
		<item>"Woah, Im sipping on whatever I get handed. Throwing house parties so crazy that my crib look like a campus."</item>
		<item>"Oh boy you had your chance, and blew it, you blew it. Stand aside and watch a real n-gga do it."</item>
		<item>"I love girls that Arabian, Albanian, caucasian. I ride around gettin cranium cause my dick is hard as titanium."</item>
		<item>"Rose I sippity-sip-it. Im Quagmire I f-ck hoes. My cashflow I giggity-giggity it."</item>
		<item>"You bordo like Enrique, Im toupee, Im three-pee. Im looking like Imma sweep stakes but I treat ya girl like a cheap skate. Cause I need a crib, a big estate."</item>
		<item>"Oh, thats your girl? Well I dont give a massa two shits Massachusets. Okay Im westside, westside till Im riding underneath them tulips."</item>
		<item>"Man these hoes, take your money and I take their virginity Im high, I split an O in half, now its a parenthesis."</item>
		<item>"Big ass bottles, Big Ice buckets. I work too hard to be ballin on a budget. Me and my people do it big out in public cause. Cause if you dont do it big, you aint doing nothing."</item>
		<item>"Man I just ended up on everybody guestlist. Im just doing better than what everybody projected."</item>
		<item>"Since I signed to Kan, Im Louie Vuitton Sean. Up in Benny Han Han eating all the Wonton. Rose rose over a little Chandon. Put her hands down my pants now she rocking Sean John."</item>
		<item>"Im gone, cant remember where I am but she forget about her man when they tell her who I am."</item>
		<item>"Grind hard but a got a lot to show for it Always had drive like I had to chauffeur it."</item>
		<item>"See you look like Beyonce so do it like BeyonDo it like Beyonce and put it on Sean."</item>
		<item>"See I just walked in fresher than the shirts off in this muthf-cka. Ima need a bad broad to twirk off in this muthaf-cka. Imma go hard till it hurts off in this muthaf-cka. Imma ball so you gotta work off in this muthaf-cka."</item>
		<item>"She a 7 in the face, but a 10 in the ass. She even look better by the end of my glass."</item>
		<item>"My chains is pow on pow on pow."</item>
		<item>"Consider yourself lucky to see a legend before the prime, a killer before the crime, a BIG before the Dime. Greet me with a middle finger when you see me... it's cool, 'cause I can't see yo' ass from this side of the TV muthafucker."</item>
		<item>"Does he sound like 'Ye, Jay, or Drizzy Drake? meanwhile, I'm chilling with all these niggas, counting all this money you ain't."</item>
		<item>"I'm just a Westside lover, I leave females in my sheets and all my feelings in a rubber."</item>
		<item>"Fuck a hotel, my nigga we rent houses. My nigga, we rent houses. So many wedding rings lost in them couches."</item>
		<item>"I'm in, that no-smoke sec' rolling motherfucking ounces marijuana mountains, drinks you're not pronouncing three chains on, I don't need no bouncers nothing less than a G stack's in my trousers."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I dream bigger than I live. Sometimes I think better when I'm lit. So gone and light it. Roll it up, ignite it. One time for all my niggas that dreamed it then real life'd it!"</item>
		<item>"Ima dick her down...you gon pick her up...yup."</item>
		<item>"I put that weed in da air..Pass it, yup dats alley-oopin."</item>
		<item>"They say im fake, fuck it im paid, i cant even find a empty spot up in my safe."</item>
		<item>"Im shitting on every statistic that said ill be dead or fucking broke."</item>
		<item>"Shrimp Steak Liqour and Pasta...Real Shit Boy Dese Niggas Impostas."</item>
		<item>"Tell me how my checks look stupid as hell. Tell me how my ex look- stupid as hell."</item>
		<item>"I ride around getting cranium cause my dick hard as titanium..."</item>
		<item>"I need my girl to look badder than my girlfriend. You know, the one that looks badder than her girlfriends."</item>
		<item>"I just drop lines like a nigga gon' fishing."</item>
		<item>"They all got they hands up cuz they fux wit me hands down."</item>
		<item>"I be running thru them trees, niggas call me Tarzan."</item>
		<item>"Im living out my dream, dont you dare hit that alarm clock."</item>
		<item>"I aint tryna rock no shirts thats saying memories...are you feeling me?"</item>
		<item>"Are u willing to give up what u love for who u love? Or lose your girlfriend to groupie love?"</item>
		<item>"Rippin life from the plastic turning every song to platinum."</item>
		<item>"Tryna see whats in common but my dick whats between us."</item>
		<item>"Man the life of a workaholic...You either on ya work or just workin on it."</item>
		<item>"Polo lookin like a got kentucky derby in my closet."</item>
		<item>"It breaks my heart when all the kids be yellin u the man big...he aint the hometown hero he on that lebron james shit."</item>
		<item>"Bitch I am a monster, I belong in District 9."</item>
		<item>"I'll fuck yo bitch with a Louis Vuitton condom."</item>
		<item>"Feeling like I got the cheat code to life."</item>
		<item>"100 thousand worth of ice on me now, but it don't feel half as good as granda saying she proud."</item>
		<item>"Going broke... no sir!"</item>
		<item>"Bitch I'm a rap game stylist, cause I gave the rap game style bitch."</item>
		<item>"Ya niggas don't have to ask how the top feels when they standing right next to you."</item>
		<item>"I'm a rap game stylist, cause I gave the rap game style bitch."</item>
		<item>"You can't hold a real nigga down that's why I keep real niggas round."</item>
		<item>"I got signed to my idol, seen some of my favorite rappers turn rivals. 'Ye told me kill em so a nigga gotta drop 'em."</item>
		<item>"Livin' the life niggas told me was a myth, same niggas try an' get up on my list."</item>
		<item>"Used to want a chain, now I got 6. Used to want a Rollie like Pac now it's on my wrist, woah."</item>
		<item>"Yo niggas don't ask how the top feel when you keep em right beside you."</item>
		<item>"My team's so true we should get a camera crew. To follow us around and make a show for us."</item>
		<item>"Even if we fucked you still ain't fucking with me."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
