<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Haters keep on hating cause somebody’s gotta do it."</item>
		<item>"Follow your dreams, just make sure you have fun too."</item>
		<item>"Everywhere that I’ve been, the only thing I see is beautiful people."</item>
		<item>"Ooops, I said on my d-ck. I aint really mean to say on my d-ck. But since we talking about my d-ck, all of you haters say hi to it."</item>
		<item>"Look at me now. I’m getting paper!"</item>
		<item>"I get what you get in 10 years, in two days."</item>
		<item>"Can I visit all those spots you like ? Your neck, your back, your sexy lips, booty and thighs."</item>
		<item>"Girl you heard what I said. I’m gonna make you wet the bed."</item>
		<item>"I ain’t afraid to drown if that means I’m deep up in your ocean."</item>
		<item>"How do you let it go when you… you just don’t know… what’s on the other side of the door? Talk about it…"</item>
		<item>"There’s never a right time to say goodbye. But I gotta make the first move ’cause if I don’t you’re gonna start hating me."</item>
		<item>"Never meant to crush your world and I never thought I would see the day we grew apart."</item>
		<item>"Listen to your heart. Girl you know we should be apart. Baby I just can’t do it, and sometimes it makes me wanna cry."</item>
		<item>"There’s never a right time to say goodbye."</item>
		<item>"I really don’t feel the way I once felt about you. Girl it’s not you, it’s me. I kinda gotta figure out what I need."</item>
		<item>"I don’t wanna see you cry, but I don’t wanna be the one to tell you a lie..."</item>
		<item>"I work too hard to be ballin’ on a budget."</item>
		<item>"Me and my people do it big out in public, ’cause if you don’t do it big, you aint doing nothing."</item>
		<item>"She says she wanna see what it feels like to be Ms. Breezy!"</item>
		<item>"I’m gon’ still buy gifts til she won’t turn none of them down. But she don’t want nothing from me and she gon’ change her last name. She can’t wait to be Mrs. Brown."</item>
		<item>"Wave to the haters like nanananana."</item>
		<item>"Ain’t got no competition ’cause shawty you the bestest."</item>
		<item>"Body is a blessing; ain’t no second guessing."</item>
		<item>"Your clothes look good but they look great on the floor, so hurry up and take ‘em off. Don’t act like we aint did this before so baby let’s go and bring your body over here."</item>
		<item>"I know you love it when I’m inside."</item>
		<item>"I don’t know your name but excuse me miss, I saw you from across the room. And I got to admit that you got my attention."</item>
		<item>"I know you’re trying to leave but excuse me miss, I saved the last dance for you."</item>
		<item>"How I love to keep you here with me oh baby."</item>
		<item>"I can definitely show you things that’s gon have you sayin I can’t be 16."</item>
		<item>"I’m fly and I know it."</item>
		<item>"I love it when you talk that sh*t."</item>
		<item>"F*ck ‘em all like I’m fresh out."</item>
		<item>"Call me Commando ’cause I’m going all balls out."</item>
		<item>"Do ‘em like Gwen Stefani; give ‘em no doubt."</item>
		<item>"Pause so the fans can applause."</item>
		<item>"N*gga I’m cold, but that don’t mean I’m chillin."</item>
		<item>"I like my broads top missin’."</item>
		<item>"I got that cash flow; n*gga I just be the safe."</item>
		<item>"She might say yo name, but she yelling mine."</item>
		<item>"Fresh up off the stove, I’m hotter than a b*tch!"</item>
		<item>"Shawty let me cut; call me Mr. Chainsaw."</item>
		<item>"My tattoos complement my attitude."</item>
		<item>"Light skinned but I’m not an average dude."</item>
		<item>"Baby we don’t need no script for this. Baby we don’t need no actresses."</item>
		<item>"I’ma throw a couple thousand, baby strip for this."</item>
		<item>"Let me pull my camera out and make a movie starring you and me."</item>
		<item>"Let me see what I’m working with, I’ma break your back with this."</item>
		<item>"Rollin round, up and down, up in this bed. I don’t want you to forget."</item>
		<item>"Before I leave I’m a give you bragging rights."</item>
		<item>"I love it when you tell me "Come get it I’m alone"."</item>
		<item>"One o’clock, two o’clock, three o’clock, four. Hope you come back for more."</item>
		<item>"All dat bullsh*t for the birds… You ain’t nothing but a vulture."</item>
		<item>"I’ma have you run from this D like a crook from the police."</item>
		<item>"I call her Madusa; she the type of girl that can seduce ya."</item>
		<item>"Everywhere I go I be followed by six h**s."</item>
		<item>"Call me bang bang ’cause I go so hard."</item>
		<item>"Shawty when I do my thang, it ain’t gon’ stop. Wanna hear my name when you on top ’cause you know I’m too freaky!"</item>
		<item>"I use my tongue; yeah I’m a cookie monster. You an amazon so you can take this anaconda."</item>
		<item>"I got that long money, so is my d*ck."</item>
		<item>"They be like “why you sh*tting on ‘em”? Cause I’m an a**hole."</item>
		<item>"Whip so sick you can call it bird flu."</item>
		<item>"I’m a shark, you can’t catch me on a fishing pole."</item>
		<item>"You know I’m balling; I ain’t talking about genitals."</item>
		<item>"Girl you can get all of me if you let me do it."</item>
		<item>"Ain’t no turning me down, ’cause I’m way too turned up now!"</item>
		<item>"I’m on some new sh*t, I’m chunkin my deuces up. I’m moving on to something better; no more trying to make it work."</item>
		<item>"You’ll regret the day when I find another girl."</item>
		<item>"I’ma make you feel like a virgin again."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
