<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"His grandma was a great piano player."</item>
		<item>"He is not into blink-blink."</item>
		<item>"He was born on March 1st, 1994."</item>
		<item>"His first CD came in November 17th, 2009."</item>
		<item>"His favorite slang word is /"Shawty"/."</item>
		<item>"He likes a good smile."</item>
		<item>"His Dad remarried."</item>
		<item>"His most embarrassing moment is when he broke his foot on stage during a song (he stayed and finished the song, didn't even miss a note!)"</item>
		<item>"He prefers MACs over PCs."</item>
		<item>"His shoe size is 7 and a half."</item>
		<item>"He likes captain crunch (with berries)."</item>
		<item>"His favorite colors are blue and purple."</item>
		<item>"His father's name is Jeremy Bieber."</item>
		<item>"Justin Bieber's full name is Justin Drew Bieber."</item>
		<item>"He can count to 10 in German."</item>
		<item>"His two best friends are Ryan Butler and Chaz Somers."</item>
		<item>"He started dating when he was 13."</item>
		<item>"He has a half sister named Jazmine &amp; brother Jaxon."</item>
		<item>"He can play trumpet, guitar, piano and drums."</item>
		<item>"His first kiss was when he was 13."</item>
		<item>"He is a lefty."</item>
		<item>"His celebrity crush is Beyonce."</item>
		<item>"He speaks fluent French."</item>
		<item>"He once dated Caitlin Beadles (Christians Beadles sister) ."</item>
		<item>"His favorite pie is apple."</item>
		<item>"He likes playing soccer."</item>
		<item>"His favorite food is spaghetti."</item>
		<item>"His favorite TV show is smallville."</item>
		<item>"He raised 150,000 lbs of food for food Bank, with the help of his fans."</item>
		<item>"His favorite number is 6."</item>
		<item>"He is claustrophobic - fear of being in narrow or enclosed spaces (eg. elevators, closet)."</item>
		<item>"His mother name is Pattie Mallette."</item>
		<item>"He is pals with Taylor Swift."</item>
		<item>"His favorite music are R&amp;B and Pop."</item>
		<item>"His favorite drink is orange juice."</item>
		<item>"His favorite video game is NBA 2k."</item>
		<item>"His favorite music artists are: Usher, Michael Jackson, BoysIImen, Stevie Wonder."</item>
		<item>"His nicknames are: J-Beebs, Justin, JB, Biebs, Beebs."</item>
		<item>"He is very protective for his little sister."</item>
		<item>"He likes sporty, active, nice, and down to earth girls."</item>
		<item>"He likes to skateboard and is very good at it."</item>
		<item>"His dad plays guitar, and his mom sings."</item>
		<item>"He likes sour patch kids."</item>
		<item>"He is signed by Usher. Justin Timberlake was reportedly in the running to sign Bieber."</item>
		<item>"He got his first plaque at YTV's The Next Star at Canadas wonderland."</item>
		<item>"He would date anyone he falls in love with."</item>
		<item>"He likes vitamin water."</item>
		<item>"He wanted to buy a house for his mom when he has $1,000,000."</item>
		<item>"He once asked out Rihanna and Alexa Chung (got rejected)."</item>
		<item>"He likes tacos."</item>
		<item>"He grew up in Canada (Stratford Ontario)"</item>
		<item>"He loves his fans!"</item>
		<item>"He loves Tim Hortons (very Canadaian)."</item>
		<item>"His label is Island def jam."</item>
		

	</string-array>
</resources>
