<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Tupac was named after Tupac Amaru II who was an Emperor of the Inca Empire in Peru and led an uprising against Spanish soldiers in his country in 1780."</item>
		<item>"The track \"Something Wicked\" from 2Pac’s debut 2pacalypse Now album was a direct quote from Shakespeare's Macbeth (i.e. \"Something Wicked This Way Comes\".)"</item>
		<item>"Tupac was engaged to Quincy Jones’ daughter Kidada at the time of his passing."</item>
		<item>"Tupac had to take an HIV test before kissing Janet Jackson in "Poetic Justice," where he played opposite of the singer in the role of post office worker Lucky."</item>
		<item>"Tupac’s last video before his death was “I Ain’t Mad At Cha” and featured actor Bokeem Woodbine. The video also shouted out Mutulu Shakur and Geronimo Pratt, his stepfather and godfather respectively." </item>
		<item>"The acronym of his 2nd album title Strictly For My N.I.G.G.A.Z. stood for \"Never Ignorant Getting Goals Accomplished\"."</item>
		<item>"In Africa, Tupac is considered an iconic figure and is thought to be the greatest rapper that ever lived by many on the continent."</item>
		<item>"Tupac recorded The Don Killuminati: The 7 Day Theory album over the course of seven days in August 1996. It was released posthumously."”</item>
		<item>"While in jail, 2Pac became pen pals with popular Who’s the Boss sitcom actor Tony Danza."</item>
		<item>"In 2004, Pac was given the title of the highest selling rap/hip-hop artists of all time in the Guinness Book of Records – at that point he had sold 67 million records."</item>
		<item>"Tupac's official cause of death was respiratory failure and cardiopulmonary arrest."</item>
		<item>"Tupac's birth name is Lesane Parish Crooks according to birth records. His mother had his name changed much later due to problems with Pac’s father."</item>
		<item>"Tupac auditioned for the role of Bubba in \"Forrest Gump\"."</item>
		<item>"Tupac wrote Shock G's verse on his 1992 single \"I Get Around\"."</item>
		<item>"Pac originally rhymed under the name MC New York when he was a teen in Baltimore."</item>
		<item>"Tupac's 1995 album Me Against the World became a #1 album when it was released, making Pac the first artist in history to have a LP debut at the top of The Billboard 200 while in prison."</item>
		<item>"Tupac once made an appearance on the sitcom \"A Different World\"."</item>
		<item>"Tupac was originally set to star in "Menace To Society" in the role of O-Dog, who was portrayed by Larenz Tate."</item>
		<item>"Tupac was housed in the Clinton Correctional Facility, the same prison that rapper Shyne also served time in."</item>
		<item>"Tupac signed his recording contract with Death Row Records on toilet paper while serving a sentence in an upstate New York prison."</item>
		<item>"Tupac was out on bail from a sexual assault case at the time of his death."</item>
		<item>"Tupac Shakur was once married to Keisha Morris. The marriage was annulled shortly after."</item>
		<item>"Tupac was slated to act in the movies \"Cool Runnings\", \"Higher Learning\" and \"How To Be A Player\"."</item>
		<item>"Tupac's Death Row debut album, All Eyez on Me, was rap's first double disc CD."</item>
		<item>"Boot Camp Clik and Tupac recorded an unreleased record One Nation in the summer of 1996 to help squash the East Coast vs. West Coast beef."</item>
		<item>"Tupac's first appearance ever was on Digital Underground's “Same Song” where he raps wearing West African war garb in the video."</item>
		<item>"Tupac began his career in 1990 on Public Enemy’s Fear Of A Black Planet tour, as a roadie and dancer for one of the tour’s opening acts, Oakland-based rap group, Digital Underground."</item>
		<item>"Tupac Shakur’s very first film appearance was in 1991’s \"Nothing But Trouble,\" starring comedian Chevy Chase and Demi Moore."</item>
		<item>"Tupac recorded 6 studio albums while he was alive and released 9 posthumous album following his untimely death."</item>
		<item>"In the Fall of 1997, the University of California at Berkeley offered \"History 98: Poetry and History of Tupac Shakur\" and became the first accredited school to develop a course based on the rapper’s music, life and lyrics."</item>
		<item>"Shakur's hit song \"Dear Mama\" is one of 25 songs that was added to the National Recording Registry in 2010."</item>
		<item>"In January of 2000, Tupac’s Changes was nominated for a Best Rap Solo Performance Grammy, marking the first time a Hip-Hop artist’s posthumously created work has been nominated for the award."</item>
		<item>"Tupac studied ballet and dance while in high school."</item>
		<item>"His mother, Afeni Shakur, buried some of Tupac's ashes in Lumberton, North Carolina on her farm there. The rest of his ashes were divided up between other family members and friends."</item>
		<item>"Tupac once dated global pop icon Madonna."</item>
		<item>"Tupac stayed at the home of actor Jasmine Guy while recuperating from gunshot wounds."</item>
		<item>"Tupac was a Versace model."</item>
		<item>"When Tupac was 12 years old, his mother enrolled him in Harlem’s 127th St Ensemble. He played Travis in the play "A Raisin in The Sun" in his first acting role."</item>
		<item>"In 1999, 2Pac’s book of poetry \"The Rose That Grew From Concrete\" was released. It featured work from the rapper and poet written between 1989 and 1991, some in his original handwriting."</item>
		<item>"Renamed Tupac Amaru Shakur in 1972 by his mother after Tupac Amaru, an Inca who was sentenced to death by the Spaniards. Tupac Amaru, in the Inca language, means \"shining serpent\"."</item>
		<item>"Son of black panther Afeni Shakur; grew up in Harlem, Baltimore, and Marin County, California."</item>
		<item>"Was engaged to Kidada Jones"</item>
		<item>"He had the words "thug life" tattooed across his abdomen."</item>
		<item>"Was going to play the role of Malik in Higher Learning (1995)"</item>
		<item>"Died on a Friday the 13th."</item>
		<item>"More of his music has been released since his death than was while he was alive."</item>
		<item>"Appeared in the Salt-N-Pepa video, \"Whatta Man\"."</item>
		<item>"Founding Member of the Outlawz"</item>
		<item>"Used the name Makaveli which is an altered spelling of Machiavelli, about whom he read while in prison."</item>
		<item>"In the song \"Life Goes On\" from the \"All Eyez on Me\" album, he rhymes about his own funeral."</item>
		<item>"As a young man, Tupac also studied dance, including ballet."</item>
		<item>"Tupac is listed as the most successful gangsta MC in the \"Guinness Book of World Records\"."</item>
		<item>"Grew up in Baltimore, Maryland, USA."</item>
		<item>"Jim Carrey was his favorite actor."</item>
		<item>"Was cast in the movie Woo (1998), but was shot five days before principal photography began."</item>
		<item>"He was offered a record contract at the age of 13. However, his mother refused to let him sign anything at such a young age. She felt he had a lot to learn about the world before joining the music industry."</item>
		<item>"He read for the part of \"Bubba\" in Forrest Gump (1994)."</item>
		<item>"10 albums have been released after his 1996 death; all have gone platinum."</item>
		<item>"He was voted the 86th Greatest Rock 'n Roll Artist of all time by Rolling Stone."</item>
		<item>"In November 1994, he was robbed and shot five times by a pair of muggers in the lobby of a New York recording studio. Tupac survived the attack, and afterwards frequently boasted of his durability in his lyrics."</item>
		<item>"Was originally cast in Menace II Society (1993) but was fired after a physical altercation with director Allen Hughes."</item>
		<item>"As a teenager, he studied drama at Baltimore's School for the Arts, where he rhymed under the name MC New York."</item>
		<item>"When he was 12 years old, his mother enrolled him in Harlem's 127th St Ensemble. He played Travis in "A Raisin in The Sun" in his first acting role."</item>
		<item>"Started his career on Tommy Boy/Warner Bros. Records with Digital Underground."</item>
		<item>"As a young man, he also studied ballet and dance"</item>
		<item>"His 1996 song \"Ghetto Gospel\" was released in 2005, with some vocals by Elton John, and went to #1 in the UK, despite the fact he had been dead for eight years."</item>
		<item>"Was a good friend of fellow hip-hop MC M.C. Hammer, who also was from Oakland, California, USA."</item>
		<item>"His albums have sold 38 million copies in the USA alone."</item>
		<item>"Had been rapping since he was 18 years old (1989)."</item>
		<item>"According to Guiness Book of Records 2004, he is the highest selling rap/hip-hop artist selling over 67 million copies worldwide."</item>
		<item>"In a 2005 Rolling Stones Magazine Vote, Tupac was named #6 of the '100 immortal artists of all time' behind the likes of Elvis and Lennon."</item>
		<item>"He is the first rap/hip-hop artist in history to have a wax model of himself set to be placed in Madamme Tussaud's in Las Vegas."</item>
		<item>"Appeared on Forbes' \"Top Earning Dead Celebrities\" list in 2002, 2003 and 2004 with earnings of $7 million, $12 million and $5 million in each respective year."</item>
		<item>"Wrote a song, but died before he could finish it. Rap artist Eminem finished the song with his own lyrics and released it shortly afterwards."</item>
		<item>"First music artist to have a #1 LP while being in jail."</item>
		<item>"Biological Father Is Billy Garland."</item>
		<item>"The harmonica in \"So Many Tears\" is a sample from Stevie Wonder's song \"That Girl\", which spent 9 weeks at number one on the RnB charts in 1982."</item>
		<item>"His song \"Hit 'Em Up\", which Shakur considered a \"classic battle record\" is scathing attack on one-time friend Notorious BIG, Bad Boy Records, and Puff Daddy. In addition, Shakur claimed that he slept with Faith Evans (Notorious BIG's wife) in the song's lyrics."</item>
		<item>"Was a fan of actor Tim Roth and was delighted to learn he would work with him on \"Gridlock'd\", released after Shakur's death."</item>
		<item>"Read the article in "Entertainment Weekly" about his \"Me Against The World\" album's debut at number one, while incarcerated. The album's title song also appeared in Michael Bay's 1995 film \"Bad Boys\", which opened in March-- while Shakur was behind bars."</item>
		<item>"Cited Prince as an inspiration and sampled his music on the \"All Eyez On Me\" album. Shakur mentioned in an MTV interview that \"he [Prince] loves women like I love women\"."</item>
		<item>"Used an interpolation of the 1984 El Debarge song \"A Dream\" for his hit \"I Ain't Mad At Ya\". Tupac's version, however, is at a faster tempo than the original."</item>
		<item>"His first album, \"2Pacalypse Now\" was released November 12, 1991 and was certified gold. It contains 13 songs and reached number 13 on the RnB/Hip-Hop albums."</item>
		<item>"Shakur was shot in Las Vegas on September 7, 1996 at approximately 11:15pm, at the corner of Flamingo and Koval streets."</item>
		<item>"Shakur renamed his publishing company to \"Joshua's Dream\" in honor of a young, terminally ill child whose dying wish was to meet him."</item>
		<item>"His number one single, \"California Love\" was certified at sales of 2 million copies in 1998."</item>
		<item>"Tupac used the Roland D70 synthesizer for his album \"All Eyez On Me\" (as seen in an interview with MTV in 1996)."</item>
		<item>"Moved out of his mother's house when he was 17."</item>
		<item>"Along with friends, he founded the \"Junior Black Panthers\" in his youth."</item>
		<item>"His favorite singer was Prince."</item>
		<item>"Mentioned in the rap-rock song \"Mope\" by Bloodhound Gang, along with personalities like Luciano Pavarotti, The Notorious B.I.G., Falco, Tori Spelling, Bo Jackson and Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart."</item>
		<item>"Ranked #3 on VH1's 50 Greatest Hip Hop Artists."</item>
		<item>"Tupac died with less than $100,000 in the bank."</item>
		<item>"Is portrayed by Anthony Mackie in Notorious (2009)."</item>
		<item>"His godfather was Geronimo Ji Jaga, a member of Black Panther Party for Self Defense, a radical group advocating violence in obtaining civil rights for African-Americans. Shakur's parents, Afeni Shakur and Billy Garland, were also members of the group."</item>
		<item>"Born in New York City, Tupac grew up primarily in Harlem."</item>
		<item>"Lesane Parish Crooks is Tupac birth name."</item>
		<item>"Nicknames- 2Pac, Makaveli, Pac "</item>
		<item>"In 1984, his family moved to Baltimore, Maryland where he became good friends with Jada Pinkett Smith."</item>
		<item>"His family moved again in 1988 to Oakland, California."</item>
		<item>"His first breakthrough in music came in 1991 as a member of the group Digital Underground."</item>
		<item>"His solo movie career began  with Juice (1992), and in 1992 he co-starred with Janet Jackson in Poetic Justice (1993)."</item>
		<item>"But law confrontations were soon to come: a 15-day jail term in 1994 for assault and battery and, in 1995, a conviction for sexual assault of a female fan. He was released after serving eight months pending an appeal."</item>
		<item>"Following the Tyson vs Seldon fight in Las Vegas, Nevada, he was hit by four bullets while riding in a car driven by Death Row Records chief executive Marion Suge Knight"</item>
		<item>"His right lung was removed in emergency surgery and, after six days in a medical coma, he died."</item>
		<item>"2 Pac is 5'11" (1.80 m)."</item>
		<item>"Shakur was inducted into the Hip-Hop Hall of Fame in 2002."</item>
		<item>"Janet Jackson demanded 2Pac take an HIV test before she would do any kissing scenes for the film Poetic Justice."</item>
		<item>"2Pac didn't have a criminal record before he became a rap star."</item>
		<item>"In 1992, Vice President Dan Quayle said 2Pac's 2Pacalypse Now \"has no place in our society\"."</item>
		<item>"2Pac wrote his first rap at 15."</item>
		<item>"At 15, 2Pac also attended Baltimore School for the Arts where he studied ballet and acting."</item>
		<item>"2Pac's Death Row debut album, All Eyez on Me, was rap's first double CD."</item>
		<item>"While he was in jail, 2Pac's 1995 album, Me Against the World, debuted at No. 1. It went double platinum in 7 months."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
