<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"When you love someone so deeply they become your life, it's easy to succumb overwhelming fears inside. Blindly I imagined I could keep you under a glass. Now I understand to hold you I must open my hand and watch you rise."</item>
		<item>"Never, never listen to anybody that tries to discourage you..."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don't ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me!"</item>
		<item>"I'm really fortunate. I'm really happy, and I'm really really lucky to be where I am."</item>
		<item>"Music is what I love and it's what I feel and it's in me and to know that I can do something that I enjoy and hopefully bring some enjoyment to other people through what I do is an incrediable felling and I am just really thankful for it."</item>
		<item>"If critics have problems with my personal life, it's their problem. Anybody with half a brain would realize that it's the charts that count."</item>
		<item>"I always felt like the rug could be pulled out from under me at anytime. And coming from a racially mixed background, I always felt like I didn't really fit in anywhere."</item>
		<item>"Forget the image, forget the ensemble, forget the rumours, forget the short skirts, the big hair, whatever! I owe this to the fans and I will never forget you so I want to accept this award on behalf of all of you."</item>
		<item>"Butterflies are always following me, everywhere I go."</item>
		<item>"Basically, I started singing when I started talking. Music has just been my saving grace my whole life."</item>
		<item>"A lot of people are singing about how screwed up the world is, and I don't think that everybody wants to hear about that all the time."</item>
		<item>"Whatever you're going through in your life, don't ever give up."</item>
		<item>"There is a light at the end of the tunnel... hopefully its not a freight train!"</item>
		<item>"One day I promised God that if he would give me my voice back I would never smoke again. I got three octaves back after quitting."</item>
		<item>"Never, never listen to anybody that try to discourage you."</item>
		<item>"My mother is Irish, my father is black and Venezuelan, and me - I'm tan, I guess."</item>
		<item>"My heart has never been broken, I've never broken anyone else's."</item>
		<item>"It's hard to be someone that people talk about and write about, you know? They don't know me."</item>
		<item>"In this world, I call the shots and I think I know best."</item>
		<item>"If you see me as just the princess then you misunderstand who I am and what I have been through."</item>
		<item>"I'm not one of those people that goes into details of my personal life on national TV to get attention. Some things are better left unsaid."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather be onstage with a pig - a duet with Jennifer Lopez and me just ain't going to happen."</item>
		<item>"I hope to be around past the 90's. I don't want to just be categorized as one of this era. My goal is to have a career that stands."</item>
		<item>"I don't think anyone knows as much about what's right for me as I do."</item>
		<item>"I don't mind being compared to Whitney, there are people miles worse to be compared to."</item>
		<item>"I do not think I reinvent myself. Wearing my hair differently or changing my style of dress is playing dress-up. I don't take it too seriously."</item>
		<item>"I always felt like the rug could be pulled out from under me at anytime. And coming from a racially mixed background, I always felt like I didn't really fit in anywhere."</item>
		<item>"I do not think I reinvent myself. Wearing my hair differently or changing my style of dress is playing dress-up. I don't take it too seriously."</item>
		<item>"I don't mind being compared to Whitney, there are people miles worse to be compared to."</item>
		<item>"My heart has never been broken, I've never broken anyone else's."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather be onstage with a pig - a duet with Jennifer Lopez and me just ain't going to happen."</item>
		<item>"I hope to be around past the 90's. I don't want to just be categorized as one of this era. My goal is to have a career that stands."</item>
		<item>"If critics have problems with my personal life, it`s their problem. Anybody with half a brain would realize that it`s the charts that count."</item>
		<item>"What I write is all from my imagination. Fact is, I haven't had time to experience all that, but that doesn't mean to say that I don't write from the heart, because I do. I put myself in other women's shoes, I can feel their pain and joy when I think about it. It's all the same, we're all women."</item>
		<item>"Heartbreaker, you got the best of me , but I just keep on coming back incessantly. Oh why, did you have to run your game on me? I should have known right from the start, you'd go and break my heart."</item>
		<item>"There was a time when all I was allowed to do was go to gay clubs, because my quote-unquote husband was so afraid of me being around straight people."</item>
		<item>"I don't know why, but everybody thinks that I'm short. When they see me for the first time, women are always surprised to be obliged to raise their head. - on her height."</item>
		<item>"There is a light at the end of the tunnel...hopefully it's not a freight train."</item>
		<item>"It's hard to be someone that people talk about and write about, you know? They don't know me."</item>
		<item>"Gotta make that move for somebody who appreciates all the love I give."</item>
		<item>"Music is what I love and it's what I feel and it's in me and to know that I can do something that I enjoy and hopefully bring some enjoyment to other people through what I do is an incredible feeling and I am just really thankful for it."</item>
		<item>"People all of a sudden just see me and hear me having hit records and it seems to have come out of the blue. But really I have been working towards this my whole life, and this is what I say when people say I haven't paid my dues."</item>
		<item>"Someone said I never paid any dues. I feel my whole life was struggling, because we were poor. We were alone, we had nothing--no security. I feel I have paid my dues. I've been paying my dues all my life."</item>
		<item>"I'm not one of those people that goes into details of my personal life on national TV to get attention. Some things are better left unsaid."</item>
		<item>"I gotta shake you off. Cause the lovin' ain't the same and you keep on playin' games, like you know I'm here to stay."</item>
		<item>"I rarely go to bed before 5 or 6 am. I am a girl of the night. I hate getting up before 2pm. And when I get up, I don't have breakfast, just a slice of pizza. I'm composing my songs in bed, because I'm getting inspired when I'm about to sink into sleep. The night inspires me."</item>
		<item>"I'm not vain, I'm insecure."</item>
		<item>"They went through some very hard times before I was born. They had their dogs poisoned, their cars set on fire and blown up. It put a strain on their relationship that never quit. There was always this tension. They just fought all the time."</item>
		<item>"There's never been anything else in my life that inspired me at all. It's crazy, but I've always loved music and I've always known this was what I wanted to do. I can't remember a time when I didn't want to be a singer."</item>
		<item>"I've always said that my father is half black and half Venezuelan and my mother is Irish. But people don't understand. They can't fathom that I'm African American, Venezuelan and Irish."</item>
		<item>"And maybe there are some people out there who think a quarter Venezuelan is not a lot... Well, I may be only one quarter, but it's a strong quarter."</item>
		<item>"I'd humbly like to become an inspiration to the biracial kids, who are the population of the new millennium. I'm everything and nothing at the same time: white, black and Latino. If I've managed to be accepted, the others can do it, too."</item>
		<item>"I don't think anyone knows as much about what's right for me as I do."</item>
		<item>"A lot of people are singing about how screwed up the world is, and I don't think that everybody wants to hear about that all the time."</item>
		<item>"Whatever you're going through in your life, don't ever give up."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don't ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me."</item>
		<item>"If you don't know me at this point. Then I highly doubt you ever will. I really need you to give me that unconditional love I used to feel. It's a mistake, if we just erase it, from our hearts and minds."</item>
		<item>"I'm just speaking from experience, nothing can compare to your first true love."</item>
		<item>"Don't forget about late nights, playing in the dark. And waking up inside my arms, boy you'll always be in my heart."</item>
		<item>"Now everytime I see you, I pretend I'm fine. When I wanna reach out to you."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don't ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me."</item>
		<item>"If critics have problems with my personal life, it's their problem. Anybody with half a brain would realize that it's the charts that count."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don't ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me!"</item>
		<item>"I'm really fortunate. I'm really happy, and I'm really really lucky to be where I am."</item>
		<item>"I gotta shake you off. Cause the lovin' ain't the same and you keep on playin' games, like you know I'm here to stay."</item>
		<item>"Music is what I love and it's what I feel and it's in me and to know that I can do something that I enjoy and hopefully bring some enjoyment to other people through what I do is an incredible feeling and I am just really thankful for it."</item>
		<item>"It's hard to be someone that people talk about and write about, you know? They don't know me."</item>
		<item>"There is a light at the end of the tunnel...hopefully it's not a freight train!"</item>
		<item>"I don`t know why, but everybody thinks that I`m short. When they see me for the first time, women are always surprised to be obliged to raise their head."</item>
		<item>"Heartbreaker, you got the best of me , but I just keep on coming back incessantly. Oh why, did you have to run your game on me? I should have known right from the start, you'd go and break my heart."</item>
		<item>"What I write is all from my imagination. Fact is, I haven't had time to experience all that, but that doesn't mean to say that I don't write from the heart, because I do. I put myself in other women's shoes, I can feel their pain and joy when I think about it. It's all the same, we're all women."</item>
		<item>"I hope to be around past the 90's. I don't want to just be categorized as one of this era. My goal is to have a career that stands."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather be onstage with a pig - a duet with Jennifer Lopez and me just ain't going to happen."</item>
		<item>"My heart has never been broken, I've never broken anyone else's."</item>
		<item>"I don't mind being compared to Whitney, there are people miles worse to be compared to."</item>
		<item>"I do not think I reinvent myself. Wearing my hair differently or changing my style of dress is playing dress-up. I don't take it too seriously."</item>
		<item>"I always felt like the rug could be pulled out from under me at anytime. And coming from a racially mixed background, I always felt like I didn't really fit in anywhere."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don`t ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me! (Madison Square Garden, 1995)"</item>
		<item>"Now everytime I see you, I pretend I'm fine. When I wanna reach out to you."</item>
		<item>"Don't forget about late nights, playing in the dark. And waking up inside my arms, boy you'll always be in my heart."</item>
		<item>"I'm just speaking from experience, nothing can compare to your first true love."</item>
		<item>"If you don't know me at this point. Then I highly doubt you ever will. I really need you to give me that unconditional love I used to feel. It's a mistake, if we just erase it, from our hearts and minds."</item>
		<item>"This is for all of you out there tonight, reaching for a dream - don't ever give up! Never ever listen to anyone, when they try to discourage you, because they do that, believe me!"</item>
		<item>"A lot of people are singing about how screwed up the world is, and I don't think that everybody wants to hear about that all the time."</item>
		<item>"Whatever you're going through in your life, don't ever give up."</item>
		<item>"I don't think anyone knows as much about what's right for me as I do."</item>
		<item>"I've always said that my father is half black and half Venezuelan and my mother is Irish. But people don`t understand. They can't fathom that I'm African American, Venezuelan and Irish."</item>
		<item>"There's never been anything else in my life that inspired me at all. It`s crazy, but I`ve always loved music and I`ve always known this was what I wanted to do. I can`t remember a time when I didn`t want to be a singer."</item>
		<item>"They went through some very hard times before I was born. They had their dogs poisoned, their cars set on fire and blown up. It put a strain on their relationship that never quit. There was always this tension. They just fought all the time. [On her parents' divorce]"</item>
		<item>"You really have to look inside yourself and find your own inner strength, and say, \"I'm proud of what I am and who I am, and I'm just going to be myself\"."</item>
		<item>"I'm not one of those people that goes into details of my personal life on national TV to get attention. Some things are better left unsaid."</item>
		<item>"If you see me as just the princess then you misunderstand who I am and what I have been through."</item>
		<item>"Whenever I watch TV and see those poor starving kids all over the world, I can't help but cry. I mean I'd love to be skinny like that, but not with all those flies and death and stuff."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
