<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Call the crib, same number, same hood, and it's all good."</item>
		<item>"When I die I wanna go to hell, cause I'm a piece of shit, it ain't hard to fucking tell. Crime after crime, from drugs to extortion. I know my momma wish she got a f***** abortion."</item>
		<item>"Shit, don't ask me, I went from ashy to nasty to classy."</item>
		<item>"Don't you know a killing is thrilling? All the blood spilling is all a part of drug dealing."</item>
		<item>"If you don't love yourself, I'll make you see your own heart."</item>
		<item>"I got techniques drippin' out my butt cheeks. Sleep on my stomach so I don't f*** up my sheets."</item>
		<item>"Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, when I was dead broke man I couldn't picture this."</item>
		<item>"Excellence is my presence. Never tense, never hesitant."</item>
		<item>"Girls pee pee when they see me. Navajos creep me in they tee-pees."</item>
		<item>"I never wish death on nobody, cause there ain't coming back from that."</item>
		<item>"We just sittin here tryna win, tryin not to sin."</item>
		<item>"Ima tell you like a nigga told me, cash rules everything around me."</item>
		<item>"Armed and dangerous, ain't too many can bang wit us."</item>
		<item>"I grew up a fuckin screw up, got introduced to tha game, got an ounce and fuckin blew up."</item>
		<item>"I was a terror since the public school era. Bathroom passes, cutting classes, squeezing asses."</item>
		<item>"We can't change the world unless we change ourselves."</item>
		<item>"I'm a soldier, ready for whatever."</item>
		<item>"I'm stuck living the life of a ghetto nigga."</item>
		<item>"I love it when ya call me Big Poppa."</item>
		<item>"We used to fuss when the landlord dissed us. No heat, wonder why Christmas missed us. Birthdays was the worst days."</item>
		<item>"I'm living everyday like a hustle. Another drug to juggle. Another day, another struggle."</item>
		<item>"Everything you get. You got to work hard for it."</item>
		<item>"This instant, rappers too persistant, quick to spit Biggie name on shit."</item>
		<item>"The Underboss of this holocaust."</item>
		<item>"No aspiration to quit the game."</item>
		<item>"Fuck it I didnt wanna go to heaven anyway."</item>
		<item>"It's on *****, fuck all that bickerin beef. I can hear sweat trickling down ya cheek."</item>
		<item>"Don't you know a killing is thrilling? All the blood spilling is all a part of drug dealing."</item>
		<item>"It was all a dream..."</item>
		<item>"Relax and take notes while i take tokes of the marijuana smoke."</item>
		<item>"Birthdays was the worst days, now we sip champagne when we thirsty."</item>
		<item>"Run from the police picture that, niggga I'm too fat, I fuck around and catch a asthma attack, That's why I bust back, it don't phase me, When he drop, take his glock, and I'm Swayze."</item>
		<item>"Dangerous, we good fellas, *****s can't bang with us."</item>
		<item>"Take they cheese, take they spot, take they keys, make my faculty live happily ever after in laughter."</item>
		<item>"I spit phrases that'll thrill you, your nobody til somebody kills you."</item>
		<item>"I don't give a fuck about you or your week crew, what ya gonna do when big poppa come for you?"</item>
		<item>"Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my paper."</item>
		<item>"The more weed smoke I puff, the more dangerous."</item>
		<item>"I never wish death on nobody. 'Cause they ain't coming back from that."</item>
		<item>"I'm a soldier, ready for whatever."</item>
		<item>"I'm stuck living the life of a ghetto n!gga."</item>
		<item>"If you don't love yourself. I'll make you see your own heart."</item>
		<item>"I'm living everyday like a hustle. Another drug to juggle. Another day, another struggle."</item>
		<item>"We can't change the World. Unless we change ourselves."</item>
		<item>"I'd rather go toe-to-toe with all a ya'll, runnin' ain't in my protocol."</item>
		<item>"Biggie be Richie like Lionel."</item>
		<item>"Just grab the fucking keys and cruise up the block.... if the bitch acts shot; gettin shot on the spot!"</item>
		<item>"As I grab the glock, put it to your headpiece One in the chamber, the safety is off release Straight at your dome homes, I wanna see cabbage Biggie Smalls the savage, doin your brain cells much damage."</item>
		<item>"All I want is bitches, big booty bitches. Used to sell crack so I could stack my riches."</item>
		<item>"Don't they know my nigga gutta, fuckin' kidnap kids? Fuck 'em in the ass, throw 'em over the bridge."</item>
		<item>"I got nines in the bedroom, glocks in the kitchen. A shotty by the shower if you wanna shoot me while I'm shittin."</item>
		<item>"The thrill is gone, the black Frank White is here to excite and throw dick to dykes. Bitches I like em brainless. Guns I like em stainless steel. I want the fuckin Fortune like the Wheel."</item>
		<item>"I got techniques drippin out my buttcheeks. Sleep on my stomach so I don't fuck up my sheets."</item>
		<item>"I was a terror since the public school era. Bathroom passes, cutting classes, squeezing a--es."</item>
		<item>"Remember Rappin' Duke, duh-ha, duh-ha. You never thought that hip hop would take it this far. Now I'm in the limelight 'cause I rhyme tight."</item>
		<item>"Beatin' motherfuckers like Ike beat Tina."</item>
		<item>"I see the gimmicks, the wack lyrics."</item>
		<item>"I'm sick of niggas lying, I'm sick of bitches hawking. Matter of fact, I'm sick of talking."</item>
		<item>"Doctors say I need about three weeks of recovery. All the nurses is lovin' me, sayin' 'The best part of the day is my half'. Feedin' me breakfast and giving me a sponge bath."</item>
		<item>"Biggie Smalls is the wickedest Niggaz say I'm pussy? I dare you to stick your dick in this If I was pussy I'd be filled with syphillis Herpes, gonorrhea, chlamydia, gettin rid of ya."</item>
		<item>"Run from the police picture that, nigga I'm too fat."</item>
		<item>"I perform like Mike Anyone - Tyson, Jordan, Jackson, action."</item>
		<item>"I can hear sweat trickling down your cheek. Your heartbeat sounds like sasquatch feet Thundering, shaking the concrete."</item>
		<item>"Who the fuck is this? Pagin me at 5:46 in the mornin crack a dawnin Now Im yawnin, wipe the cold out my eye See whos this pagin me and why."</item>
		<item>"As I leave my competition repirator style, climbed the ladder to success escalator style, hold ya'll breath, I told ya'll, death controls ya'll, BIG don't fold ya'll. I spit phrases that'll thrill you, your nobody till somebody kills you."</item>
		<item>"Hoes is irritating like the hiccups, excuse me, flows just flow through me, like trees to branches , cliffs to avalanches."</item>
		<item>"Biggie Smalls is the illest, your style is played out like, 'What you talkin bout Willis?'"</item>
		<item>"After realizin, the master enterprisin, I ain't have to be in school by 10, I then began to encounter, with my counter... parts, on how to burn the block apart."</item>
		<item>"Talk slick, you get your neck slit quick, 'cause real street n***** ain't havin' that shit."</item>
		<item>"If I wasn't in the rap game. I'd probably have a key (kilo) knee-deep in the crack game. Because the the streets is a short stop. Either you're slinging crack rock or you got a wicked jump shot."</item>
		<item>"Motherfucker please, it's my block with my rock, fuck the hip-hop, them one-two's and you don't stop."</item>
		<item>"If Faith had twins, she'd probably have two Pacs, Get it, Tu-Pac's?"</item>
		<item>"It was all a dream, I used to read Word Up magazine. Salt'n'Pepa and Heavy D up in the limousine. Hangin' pictures on my wall. Every Saturday Rap Attack, Mr. Magic, Marley Marl, I let my tape rock 'til my tape popped."</item>
		<item>"Man n***** come through I'm taking high school rings too. Bitches get stripped down for they earrings and bangles. And when I rock her and drop her I'm takin her door knockers. If she's resistant then...baka! baka! baka!"</item>
		<item>"If you didn't know, now you know."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
