<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Beauty is only skin deep. I think what's really important is finding a balance of mind, body and spirit."</item>
		<item>"If you kiss on the first date and it's not right, then there will be no second date. Sometimes it's better to hold out and not kiss for a long time. I am a strong believer in kissing being very intimate, and the minute you kiss, the floodgates open for everything else."</item>
		<item>"You laugh it off, you get upset for a little while, you're human and you let it go."</item>
		<item>"You get what you give. What you put into things is what you get out of them."</item>
		<item>"They're making me out to be a serial marrying person or something. I'm laughing at that." </item>
		<item>"There are certain people that are marked for death. I have my little list of those that treated me unfairly."</item>
		<item>"People equate sexy with promiscuous. They think that because I'm shaped this way, I must be scandalous - like running around and bringing men into my hotel room. But it's just the opposite."</item>
		<item>"It's a shame to call somebody a 'diva' simply because they work harder than everybody else."</item>
		<item>"I WANTED to do my hair (on her curly hair at the Oscars) like that. Sometimes people just don't get things until months later."</item>
		<item>"Men really disgust me if they don't have a nice smile, nice lips and nice teeth...They have too many disgusting habits - like scratching themselves all the time."</item>
		<item>"And it's really weird how guys think that passing gas is the funniest thing in the world. They love to do that thing in front of girls and laugh about it."</item>
		<item>"I could serve coffee using my rear as a ledge."</item>
		<item>"Somebody said to me not too long ago, Until you're twenty, you have the face you are born with, and after that you have the face you deserve, and I really loved that - the idea that you wear who you are on your face."</item>
		<item>"I have the stardom glow."</item>
		<item>"Can you piss off a Puerto Rican and live to tell about it?"</item>
		<item>"I was always a singer and a dancer, and I always wanted to be an actress. For me, it's all just one thing."</item>
		<item>"It's hard for them (partners) to live in my shadow, knowing that they will never make the money I do."</item>
		<item>"I thought she'd [her mother] offer me some sympathy. Instead, she said, 'Don't you ever call me crying again! You wanted to be in this business, so you better toughen up!' And I did."</item>
		<item>"My parents wanted me to be a lawyer. But I don't think I would have been very happy. I'd be in front of the jury singing."</item>
		<item>"It used to bother me being portrayed as this bitchy person, but now I feel that the public understands me better than some writer. There are people who know who I really am, and that's good enough for me."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes journalists try to create a persona that's not really there."</item>
		<item>"I don't get anything for free. I pay for all my beauty treatments."</item>
		<item>"In Hollywood, she's revered, she gets nominated for Oscars, but I've never heard anyone in the public or among my friends say, 'Oh, I love her [Winona Ryder]."</item>
		<item>"People assume I'm out there having this great life, but money doesn't erase the pain."</item>
		<item>"When you're young you barrel through life, making choices without thinking of repercussions. A few years down the line, you wake up in a certain place and wonder how the hell you got there."</item>
		<item>"If you love someone, don`t wait till tomorrow to tell him/her. Maybe that next day will never come at all."</item>
		<item>"The bear is what we all wrestle with. Everybody has their bear in life. It's about conquering that bear and letting him go."</item>
		<item>"I judge people on how they smell, not how they look."</item>
		<item>"We have only one thing to do: Let's shop!"</item>
		<item>"You can't take life for granted."</item>
		<item>"I try to block this stuff out a little bit 'cause it's the only way to kind of live."</item>
		<item>"I'm not mad if people call me the modern-day Liz Taylor,"</item>
		<item>"I just observed -- like when a female cop is standing with a male cop, people talk to the male cop. So women find ways to demand respect. They don't let men one-up them in anything. They banter with them line for line. They shoot with them shot for shot."</item>
		<item>"If You Want My Love..."</item>
		<item>"No babies went into that bottle!"</item>
		<item>"Men want to take care of themselves but they don't want to look like they have had anything done."</item>
		<item>"An Unfinished Life..."</item>
		<item>"I liked the days when our stars had a mystery to them... You had this illusion. And when you watched the movies, they had so much more impact because you didn't know who these stars were dating, or if they were married or what was happening in their lives."</item>
		<item>"Your Honor, I committed the crime of being on the cover of Us magazine with Ben Affleck 100 times too often. My lips were too shiny. I made horrible movies. For my penalty I accept five months in Alderson jail in West Virginia."</item>
		<item>"On Madonna: Do I think she's a great performer? Yes. Do I think she's a great actress? No."</item>
		<item>"He was my mother's favorite actor of all time,"</item>
		<item>"This is the man my mother lived for. My career means something now because I've worked with Robert Redford."</item>
		<item>"What's Eating Gilbert Grape."</item>
		<item>"This is worse than the Oscars."</item>
		<item>"This film [the Cell] certainly is not meant for the girls who sing along with my songs."</item>
		<item>"A lucky model who's been given a lot of opportunities I just wish she [Cameron Diaz] would have done more with."</item>
		<item>"He [Wesley Snipes] wouldn't talk to me for two months. I was like, 'What an ass**le.' Actors are used to getting their way and to treating women like objects."</item>
		<item>"[Asked to name the bigger diva, herself or Stone, Lopez noted Stone's humanitarian work.] She's just lovely, ... She's a powerful actress who stands up for what she believes in. And she helps people. That's a beautiful way to use your power."</item>
		<item>"They told me that dress was very next season. I'm so ahead."</item>
		<item>"Forget the glam nights out, apparently she would Much rather stay at home and watch TV."</item>
		<item>"It was scary and fun, ... Elizabeth Taylor of the hip-hop generation."</item>
		<item>"I am honored to partner with Warnaco, an industry leader, to produce JLO by Jennifer Lopez Lingerie as an extension of my fashion company,"</item>
		<item>"I never thought I'd be here next to such greats as [salsa star] Willie Colon and with the mayor of New York City here at City Hall, ... It's a real honor for me."</item>
		<item>"A little of both is not bad, Every girl does come on girls, don't lie!"</item>
		<item>"There's only one person in this world I'm in competition with - MYSELF."</item>	
		<item>"I am a young Hispanic woman, so is Janet. I could empathize with her situation so much."</item>
		<item>"I just love Stefano and Domenico."</item>
		<item>"It's rare, but not as rare as people think."</item>
		<item>"She is so smart. But she is trapped in her body."</item>	
		<item>"With the Latino community, I am theirs, I do belong to them."</item>
		<item>"My manager says, 'Are you sure? You should test-drive it and see how it feels.' I know how it will feel. It will feel like I just wasted $80,000."</item>
		<item>"At the beginning, when I first started doing music and movies, I had this attitude that I didn't have to be like anyone else,"</item>
		<item>"Nobody writes books about how to deal with it or anything like that. Maybe I'll do that next. No. I'll make no money, it's not worth it."</item>
		<item>"It's always great to see Jennifer Lopez in a classy, understated number like that."</item>
		<item>"I see this opportunity as a way to connect to the Spanish-speaking audience in a different and more profound way than I've been able to do in the past. I want to tell the stories of Latinos who grow up here and live the American Dream."</item>
		<item>"And the doctor was like, 'No, you're fine. You need to rest, that's all.' I stayed in bed the whole weekend just relaxing, and people came over and cooked for me. I was back that Monday and was fine."</item>
		<item>"I'm so excited, ... Thank you so much for your support. I wish I could have been there."</item>
		<item>"Cris and I had a lot of time to do what we both like, ... That really relaxed us both, to say the least. Sometimes it tired us out and we slept to get our energy levels back. I'll let your imagination do the rest."</item>
		<item>"I swear to God, I don't remember anything [Gwyneth Paltrow] was in. Some people get hot by association. I heard more about her and Brad Pitt and I ever heard about her work."</item>
		<item>"It makes me laugh when she says she [Salma Hayek] got offered Selena, which was an outright lie. If that's what she does to get herself publicity than that's her thing."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
