<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"God bless the child that can hold his own."</item>
		<item>"Slim nigga, lyrically though my limbs bigger than a nigga hittin' the gym regular. Bench pressin' the bar ten steps from ya'll."</item>
		<item>"I'm so live, you motherfuckas gotta kill me twice!"</item>
		<item>"Go hard like I just seen some nipple on Beyonce, no disrespect to Hov but if i didnt i'd be beyond gay."</item>
		<item>"Pardon me, whats your name, don't mistake me for no lame."</item>
		<item>"If they don't know your dreams, then they can't shoot 'em down."</item>
		<item>"You better get yours before I reach mines cause then I'm throwing peace signs."</item>
		<item>"I'm quarterbacking tryna get'cha open like receivers."</item>
		<item>"To tell the truth, I'm only fucking with a few niggas, if that!"</item>
		<item>"I could give a fuck long as there's something that's behind her."</item>
		<item>"So here we are... It's funny how so close can seem so far.."</item>
		<item>"Somebody told me that it's only one shot, so I'll be God damn if I'm ever gon stop..."</item>
		<item>"Do you love me like you use to? Even though I ain't that nigga that you're use to to?"</item>
		<item>"Seems like I always had crushes on chicks I couldnt have... And then I end up effin' with someone I shouldn't have."</item>
		<item>"Promise to my momma I'ma make it ta the Top.. So I'ma keep climbing til my heartbeat drop."</item>
		<item>"Just a small time nigga, big city hustle Glued to the TV, Jigga, Diddy, Russell."</item>
		<item>"Yea, this is where the fathers ain't living At least not with us Might see em round the city and won't even say wassup."</item>
		<item>"One minute I'm over-rated, next minute I'm the saviour You hate it before you played it, I already forgave ya."</item>
		<item>"Talk is cheap, it's like ya'll grew up in a Jewish home!"</item>
		<item>"I'm a beast when my shit hits the streets these niggas seize to exist."</item>
		<item>"We never tattle, let God handle that Or let the mob handle that, No soprano Half Black, half white I'm a piano."</item>
		<item>"Cause either you gonna whine or climb, I choosed the ladder Know you haters is pissed, hold your bladder though Before you get tossed like a forward lateral."</item>
		<item>"I never crack, I got that chapstick."</item>
		<item>"The best bachelor since Bruce Wayne with his Bachelors Remasterd this rap shit you hear the words coming from my lips, bastards."</item>
		<item>"Like, bobby had Whitney we were cooking up crack! But them 15 credits had a nigga off track Picture that!"</item>
		<item>"Lord please forgive me for my sinning, I ain't saying that I'm finished but I'm praying in advance Cause they way her eyes glance like they playing in my pants."</item>
		<item>"And I need a fast car, bad broads, fast forward, passport, I'm a fuckin rap star."</item>
		<item>"What they taught us, man them bad bitches only want the ballers. To start us, We hoopin, now them hoes want to guard us."</item>
		<item>"In the city where the skinny niggas tryin to be the ballers. Ain't no fathers, but the skinny niggas tryin hit they daughters."</item>
		<item>"I'm a star, Converses conversin with them girls with them curves like cursive."</item>
		<item>"I never change, I'm like a corpse in a coffin."</item>
		<item>"The hoes is librarians, they lookin me up. She got a Jones like Marion, she lickin me up."</item>
		<item>"Gravitate to real shit, stay away from phonies. These niggas heard about me now they actin like they know me."</item>
		<item>"My money like a senior, watch it graduate."</item>
		<item>"I was like a young Simba, couldn't wait to be the king. Now a nigga is the prince."</item>
		<item>"Them pretty boys had them gals, spend their time flirting. All they wanted was some waves like they fuckin surfin."</item>
		<item>"I got a dolla in a dream But its all a nigga got so its about that green."</item>
		<item>"Yo I'm in a league of my own so what the fuck would I play for?"</item>
		<item>"If they dont know your dreams, then they cant shoot em down."</item>
		<item>"Pedal to the metal, feeling like a puppet and the devil is geppetto."</item>
		<item>"Believe In God, like the Sun up in the sky Science can tell us how, but the can tell us why."</item>
		<item>"It's funny how chains and whips make me feel free."</item>
		<item>"I know you wanna change the world but for the night please, just reach over and hit the lights please."</item>
		<item>"Ima kill the game and invite witnesses No death penalty, Im givin out life sentences."</item>
		<item>"My dick took over, it ain't never felt this wet before."</item>
		<item>"I should be steppin wit Priests, the way I'm blessin' the streets."</item>
		<item>"Cause that old shit fake, and this new shit real, j.cole not jay z witness that blueprint feel!"</item>
		<item>"Cole World, no blanket son!"</item>
		<item>"Ey tell me am I wrong for visualizing material shit I neva had? Waving gats instead of flags."</item>
		<item>"Hit the club she drop it low, lower than my credit score Account overdraft what I got this debit for."</item>
		<item>"Ducking bill collectors like Jehova's witness, When they showed up at your door at Christmas."</item>
		<item>"The broke me couldn't buy you meals, not even a value meal And now I pay for everything, how you feel?"</item>
		<item>"I'm a kill the game and invite witnesses, No death penalty, I'm givin' out life sentences."</item>
		<item>"Am I changing right before your eyes? Becoming someone you don't recognize?"</item>
		<item>"Watch the season nigga no re-runs The devil buying soul's nigga no refunds."</item>
		<item>"Alot of niggas getting older but they never grow up And do they son's like they fathers did and never show up."</item>
		<item>"Heal a nigga from all this pain, momma smoking cocaine as it rains out Am I to blame, try to stay sane so I came out-side Where they rock with them thangs out."</item>
		<item>"You play whatever cards he deal no matter how peculiar They tell me that it's God's will, I'm asking God will ya."</item>
		<item>"It seems like niggas either feel ya or they try and kill ya."</item>
		<item>"You heard me say I was ballin' I probably make tears, I'm trying to get clear, I'm tryna quit fear."</item>
		<item>"No chain around his neck but better watch out for the charm."</item>
		<item>"Better leave him alone/Malone like Stockton."</item>
		<item>"These n*ggas ain't playin in NY like the Giants."</item>
		<item>"Will they tarnish, will they taint? glorify me, overthink, say they know me, say Im great say Im phoney, I was fake say the things about me they never told me to my face."</item>
		<item>"When she talk she so closed minded, all she want to do is shop she so clothes minded, Wanna cop the latest before them other hoes find it. Material girl yet somehow I don't mind it."</item>
		<item>"They say anythings possible, You gotta dream like you never seen obstacles. Chasing obscene profits so we aint stoppin for redlights. Lookin in my rearview all I see is n*ggas headlights."</item>
		<item>"His flow cold as a shoulder of a broke diggin hoe, as a broke n*gga approaches, told ya I'm focused man, I let you motherf*ckers soak it in."</item>
		<item>"Talk is cheap, it's like y'all grew up in a Jewish home Pardon the stereotype, but y'all be giving me mixed feelings like I married a white woman."</item>
		<item>"Oh no he will not fold you will not see a crease on him, He will not slip or lose his grip he got them cleats on him, and Never Will he run Unless you call Police on Him."</item>
		<item>"I'm not as fast I'm not tall but before I pass I gotta ball."</item>
		<item>"I gotta make a move I gotta do this know, If They dont know your dreams Then they cant shoot em down."</item>
		<item>"What good is being the one if your the only one who knows it?"</item>
		<item>"I seen a baby cry seconds later he laughs...the beauty of life pain, pain never lasts."</item>
		<item>"I'm asking you if you can hold me down lord..be my umbrella-ella-ella, in this down pour."</item>
		<item>"The flow cold as a shoulder of a gold digging hoes when a broke nigga approaches."</item>
		<item>"Lil wayne is the best rapper alive, and I don`t fux with him, cause he would murder my ass."</item>
		<item>"Even white girls tryin' to be my princess, But i only eff with sistas like incest."</item>
		<item>"Yall talkin hard but you still aint push me They say you are what you eat and I still aint pussy."</item>
		<item>"She know me like a book, its too easy to read my ass, unhappy stressed, yelling dont mislead my ass."</item>
		<item>"Remember back when I was broke you would fix me Do you prefer the broke me or the rich me?"</item>
		<item>"Bitches always on my dick, I wear a condom when i shit!"</item>
		<item>"We rock alot of ice because we got alot of pain."</item>
		<item>"Try not to call them ladies Bs but them hoes swarmin Now honey, Ay is it destiny or is it money your feelin'."</item>
		<item>"Just one of them days A nigga feel like flossin' A Stone Cold Stunna, victim Steve Austin Cool as Drew Breeze, I'm blowing a few G's Just to hear them hoes say he's awesome."</item>
		<item>"I mean you kinda like that girl that's in the US Open. I mean I got this hidden agenda that you provoking, I got bath water that you can soak in, things I could do with lotion."</item>
		<item>"Baby you summertime fine, I let you get on top, I be the underline I'm trying to get beside you like the number 9, dime."</item>
		<item>"I'm just a nigga from around the way, told my mama I'd make it happen and I found a way. Pour out some liquor for my niggas at the crossroads. And may the Lord give guidance to the lost souls."</item>
		<item>"Feel like I'm riding on a chartered plane of broken hearted pain. Turbulence is constant my pilot has gone insane."</item>
		<item>"Fayattenaaaam! nigga yea!, Carolina all day!"</item>
		<item>"They calling you the saviour, so much pressure but you deal with it The weight of the world on your shoulders but you still lift it."</item>
		<item>"Ay, look heaven or hell you choose. Freedom or jail, you lose, I can't stop em as hot as the devils shoes."</item>
		<item>"I'd climb that motherfucker to the top and never let it go!"</item>
		<item>"Try not to show stress I guess the flow is protested like a sit in."</item>
		<item>"Some next niggas almost slide in but didn't fit in. Naw I ain't Maury Povich but who the fuck is you kid-in? These big weight niggas throwing their bid in."</item>
		<item>"It's J. Cole, set of horns and a halo And all these hoes ? wanna text-us like Waco."</item>
		<item>"Nevermind dwelling in the past, your listening to the future. Them flows get tighter, them hoes get looser. Then they wanna seduce you like medusa be cool. I said I got a girl, she told me me too."</item>
		<item>"My name aint james, my word is bond."</item>
		<item>"Aint that about a bitch this nigga on his own his dick. They say I'm like the human body I produce my own shit. And I toot my own horn, a star when I was born My name aint james, my word is bond."</item>
		<item>"They talking gangsta, without no data, they frontin Jackie chan, jean claude van dam straight stuntin, I wish a nigga would say something."</item>
		<item>"Ah I'm goin be here for a while so I smile hatas. I'm on that green like a flower like a alligator. Now or laters, I'm serving niggas Imma sound waiter Just tell me what you want, I bring that back an hour later."</item>
		<item>"Wassup girl, don't mean to interrupt But in the city I done met a lot of women But you from my dreams, ay will you come true? I know about a show that we can catch, Some RnB and rap, ay you should come thru."</item>
		<item>"Good Lord, didn't know what I was in for! You can be my cuddy buddy - baby what are friends for."</item>
		<item>"Anything you can do I can do better. Any chick you can screw I can get wettterrrr"</item>
		<item>"Baby you summertime fine, I let you get on top, I'll be the underline."</item>
		<item>"Pussy my passion, never been a fan of flashing. Probably cuz I never could so if I had it, never would."</item>
		<item>"My kicks like my chick, I dont need to know the numbers. You just need to know Im comin, Ill kill you niggas this summer."</item>
		<item>"Now we livin much better, nigga, pay whatever. Rock them bitches once then forgot about em forever."</item>
		<item>"Im slowly roastin, heatin up, so you know we toastin. Fuck hoes wit no emotion, fade away like Kobe postin."</item>
		<item>"Im oviedosin, ay, homie, Kobe smokin. Then put my ashes on you niggas, bet you gon need lotion."</item>
		<item>"How you figga? You fuckin wit me? I hope he jokin. Im witcha girl, you home alone, bitch you Macauley Culkin."</item>
		<item>"I digress, boy you bout as G as a f-cking tie dye vest and your wifey is a bird even in her Prada dress."</item>
		<item>"When Im all alone these words just flow out of my chest. Turn em into poems, they worship, Im the best."</item>
		<item>"Theres so much pain on my brain I gotta jot it out but as of late nigga, it aint been shit to pout about."</item>
		<item>"We living better guess God felt he owed us one. Closets barely had no clothes in them."</item>
		<item>"Mommas youngest getting paper like the oldest one We living better guess God felt he owed us one."</item>
		<item>"Yeah Cole World, make way for the chosen one. Aint nobody else Id rather be, not even Oprahs son."</item>
		<item>"Fuck it, everybody can get it. When you're this high everybody's a critic, but when you're this high everybody's a midget."</item>
		<item>"Ima be here for a while. None of these clowns can hurt me."</item>
		<item>"Money can't buy you love cuz it's overpriced."</item>
		<item>"She like them bar with the big old chains. Ride around town in the big old Range."</item>
		<item>"Im here for one night, how far would you go?"</item>
		<item>"I know whats on your brain. Youre probably hoping never would end. Like is it the real thing. Or is it just a one night stand."</item>
		<item>"Move slow, cause you wanna live fast. Up late so you probably skip class."</item>
		<item>"She bad and you know it, some niggas save Hoes. Im not that heroic."</item>
		<item>"They be starting shit, but its your world. On my Martin shit, you go girl!"</item>
		<item>"Carolina blue kicks, fresh on the scene. Hottest nigga on the block, damn girl you mean."</item>
		<item>"Hey, we got a good thing. Dont know if Imma see you again, see you again but is that a good thing?"</item>
		<item>"Take a chance roll a dice. Money cant buy you love cause its over priced."</item>
		<item>"Man that thing in them jeans too fat for her. It rebounds so I caught it off the backboard."</item>
		<item>"You dressing sexy and your mama is a cougar. So she let you do the grown folks thang. Let you hang with them boys and they play you like a fool girl."</item>
		<item>"Well, Straight up I tell ya I just really wanna cut when were together."</item>
		<item>"I'm going under and as I'm headed to the front door. She said she proud of me and I wonder what for..."</item>
		<item>"My own mother, yeah I love her but things I heard as a child under my covers. Left me with scars, it was hard to see her suffer. Blocking my heart and I don't know if Ill recover."</item>
		<item>"Feel like Im stuck here, that's why I won't give the fuck here. There's no luck here! No body to trust here."</item>
		<item>"Ask whats the matter but you can't relate. Living the life that you hate but you can't escape."</item>
		<item>"Hey, am I hopeless? Raised with rats and roaches. Never like them teachers, couldn't stand my coaches."</item>
		<item>"Your mind dont match what your ass got but cheer up, you gotta be your own mascot."</item>
		<item>"Now girl you is fine, ain't no doubt about it but why else you think he hit it and forgot about it?"</item>
		<item>"You got your new hair, it look so good. You write the same niggas name in your notebook."</item>
		<item>"Money can't buy you love cause it's overpriced."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
