<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"When you`re comfortable with someone you love, the silence is the best. And, that`s how me and J. are. When we`re in a room together, we don`t have to say anything. It`s for real.".</item>
		<item>"I would really, really, really like to be a legend like Madonna. Madonna knows what to do next, and when she`s performing, the audience is just in awe of her."</item>
		<item>"Onstage I`m the happiest person in the world."</item>
		<item>"I`ve never really wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don`t like eating fish. And I know that`s very popular out there in Africa."</item>
		<item>"My views on virginity have not changed. I want to wait to have sex until I`m married. I do. I want to wait, but it`s hard. I just want to live my life."</item>
		<item>"When I look into a mirror, I am very critical of myself. I see a goofy girl."</item>
		<item>"Just because I look sexy on the cover of \"Rolling Stone\" doesn`t mean I`m naughty."</item>
		<item>"Chocolate for me is just like an orgasm."</item>
		<item>"I would really, really, really like to be a legend like Madonna. Madonna knows what to do next, and when she`s performing, the audience is just in awe of her."</item>
		<item>"[on being photographed without panties] Anyway, thank God for Victoria`s Secret`s new underwear line!"</item>
		<item>"Performing is what I like most. I find the studio very confining. You can do a lot in there, and you get the opportunity to try again and again. But on stage you have the adrenalin going and you`ve got one shot and the energy is so intense."</item>
		<item>"It feels like I`ve been dreaming this forever and then it happens and it feels like a whirlwind. I`m constantly traveling and I miss my friends."</item>
		<item>"When I`m under stress, I do yoga. It`s when I`m happiest that I have a problem with junk food."</item>
		<item>"England is one of my favorite places. The fans are just so crazy."</item>
		<item>"f I was to pick a cartoon character I am most like, I would say Daisy Duck, because she is very stubborn, she has a very feminine sense and she knows what she likes."</item>
		<item>"There are so many teenagers out there that dress more provocatively than I do, and no one says anything about them."</item>
		<item>"I find it so funny that people find me so interesting. And, I hate when they`re like \"Define your image.\" I don`t know what my image is. I just do my thing."</item>
		<item>"Bottom line: If you love yourself, it will all work out."</item>
		<item>"[about Deborah Gibson at the 2001 American Music Awards] She`s the original bubble-gum diva."</item>
		<item>"Would you go into a CD store and steal a CD? It`s the same thing, people going into the computers and loggin` on and stealing our music."</item>
		<item>"Christina and I are friends no matter what the media makes up."</item>
		<item>"I`ve got an amazing group of people around me and my family at home. If I don`t make my bed and wash the dishes at home, I`m in trouble."</item>
		<item>"Tony Blair? I`ve never heard of him either. Who is he?"</item>
		<item>"This is my dream come true. I can`t believe this is happening right now. I can`t believe I even have a movie. I feel very blessed to be where I am right now."</item>
		<item>"Justin Timberlake was my first kiss. We were playing \"Truth or Dare\" and listening to Janet Jackson. I was 12. His friend dared him to kiss me, so that was my first kiss."</item>
		<item>"Marry Prince William Windsor? I`d love that. Who wouldn`t want to be a princess?"</item>
		<item>"[about her visit to the Playboy mansion] All I remember is seeing a bunch of naked girls and thinking, \"I got to get out of here\"."</item>
		<item>"I dress the way I want. I don`t pretend to be someone I`m not."</item>
		<item>"Who really cares if I`ve had sex? It`s nobody`s business. Trust me, I`m not going to have a press conference to announce it. If I mess up, I`m human. If I have a drink or I`m with someone, I`m human. I`m no different than anyone else my age."</item>
		<item>"I`m not the type of person that can be cooped up in the hotel room being served all the time. I can`t deal with that. I`ve got to do normal things."</item>
		<item>"I feel like a totally different person than I was two years ago. I feel like so much of my innocence is gone. I`m still me, but this business makes you grow up so fast."</item>
		<item>"I can`t sing the same kind of thing all the time. That would bore me."</item>
		<item>"I would like to be called an inspiration to people, not a role model--because I make mistakes like everybody else. When I`m offstage, I`m just like everybody else."</item>
		<item>"My prerogative right now is to just chill and let all the other overexposed blondes on the cover of Us Weekly (magazine) be your entertainment."</item>
		<item>"With love, you should go ahead and take the risk of getting hurt... because love is an amazing feeling."</item>
		<item>"I still have a lot to learn - about the business, about music, and about myself. Its exciting."</item>
		<item>"Onstage I`m the happiest person in the world."</item>
		<item>"Do I like my voice? Umm... Oh I be completely honest, I think my voice is okay. I like the feeling that I get when I sing, It's not so much my voice. It's a state that I go in when I sing."</item>
		<item>"(in 2009) I don't like going out. I hate clubs. I hate being around too many people. I love my home and staying in bed and watching Dancing With the Stars, or reading a Danielle Steele novel. I'm kind of boring."</item>
		<item>"I would rather start out somewhere small, like London or England."</item>
		<item>"(in her documentary Britney: For The Record) Do I know my life is werid? (pause) It's all I've ever known."</item>
		<item>"When I was a kid, my favorite thing to do--and I know this sounds really retarded--but my favorite thing to do was go and pick out all my new school supplies for the year. That was so much fun when I was younger."</item>
		<item>"I used to know so many girls who hated their mothers, and that used to make me so sad. I wished everyone could have a mother like mine."</item>
		<item>"I can't go anywhere without someone judging me."</item>
		<item>"You just try to keep on doing what you do... and as long as you know what's up and you know what's true, that's all that really matters, you know?"</item>
		<item>"I truly hit rock bottom... I don't think that it was alcohol or depression... I confess, I was so lost."</item>
		<item>"I probably did take my new-found freedom a little too far."</item>
		<item>"I know I’m a good mom."</item>
		<item>"I don't allow anybody to change me. I still walk outta my house in rollers and I take walks. I do not care what people think."</item>
		<item>"Sundance is weird. The movies are weird--you actually have to think about them when you watch them."</item>
		<item>"My stomach looked like a road map, there were so many lines and creases on it."</item>
		<item>"To be a good mom, I feel your child needs to be your full-time job."</item>
		<item>"I always like performing overseas. Like Canada."</item>
		<item>"(on her dog Lucky): Lucky is so cute. And you know how the Pharaohs used to get buried with the things they loved? I want to do that with Lucky. She should be laid to rest with me when the time comes."</item>
		<item>"I always listen to *NSYNC’s Tearin’ Up My Heart. It reminds me to wear a bra."</item>
		<item>"I'm rich, freakin' rich. It's crazy."</item>
		<item>"I would like to be called an inspiration to people, not a role model - because I make mistakes like everybody else. When I'm offstage, I'm just like everybody else."</item>
		<item>"I wish my hair was thicker, and I wish my feet were prettier. My toes are really ugly. I wish my ears were smaller. And my nose could be smaller too."</item>
		<item>"The cool thing about being famous is travelling. I have always wanted to travel across seas, like to Canada and stuff."</item>
		<item>"I know not everyone will like me, but this is who I am so if you don't like it, tough!"</item>
		<item>"I don't like defining myself. I just am."</item>
		<item>"Every night, I have to read a book, so that my mind will stop thinking about things that I stress about."</item>
		<item>"Don't treat me like a little girl."</item>
		<item>"I like to poo."</item>
		<item>"I did not have implants, I just had a growth spurt."</item>
		<item>"I'm probably writing about sex because I don´t have that right now."</item>
		<item>"“I want to be an artist that everyone can relate to, that's young, happy and fun."</item>
		<item>"I'm usually all about the tight jeans and little T-shirt, but sometimes I want to put on a black, sequined dress and be a freaking girl."</item>
		<item>"I always wanted to be a singer, it's what I wanted to do since I was little. I'm doing it now and I couldn't be happier."</item>
		<item>"I don't really have time to sit down and write. But when I think of a melody, I call up my answering machine and sing it, so I won't forget it."</item>
		<item>"It was this really bizarre video idea, this animated Power Ranger-y thing. I said, This is not right. If you want me to reach four-year-olds, then OK."</item>
		<item>"I always call my cousin because we're so close. We're almost like sisters, and we're also close because our moms are sisters."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to pierce anything. I think it's outdated. Belly rings and all are, like, old."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
