<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I also try to read all of my fan mail. A lot of them send me candy, which I'm not allowed to eat 'cause my mom says it might be poisonous."</item>
		<item>"I want my world to be fun. No parents, no rules, no nothing. Like, no one can stop me. No one can stop me."</item>
		<item>"I'm just a regular 16 year old kid. I make good grilled cheese and I like girls."</item>
		<item>"It's kind of hard to balance school and work sometimes. But sometimes, like, if I'm going to the White House and I'm in there doing a tour and stuff, that's like school."</item>
		<item>"I'd like to be an architect. That would be cool. I like drawing."</item>
		<item>"I think she’s cute. And, no, she’s not too old for me. Above 40 is a little too old for me."</item>
		<item>"Eating too much candy. I like Sour Patch Kids."</item>
		<item>"Now I'm really glad that I speak French, because, let's face it, girls dig it when a guy speaks French. They call it the language of love, and that ain't no coincidence. Plus, I love my French fans! Tres jolie!"</item>
		<item>"No matter how talented you are, not everybody is going to like you. But that's life, just stay strong."</item>
		<item>"I got up there and sang my little eighth-grade butt off, thinking this was possibly the greatest moment of my entire life -- of anyone's life -- better than hockey, better than Star Wars, better than Grandma's turkey and gravy."</item>
		<item>"I'm a really claustrophobic person to begin with. I hate elevators, especially crammed elevators. I get really scared. So I think that it's very definitely scary when girls are all around me and I can't go anywhere. At the same time, I guess I got to get used to it, you know what I mean?"</item>
		<item>"I definitely want to buy my mom a house once I get enough funds. I think that's definitely something that I want to do. I think that any person, it's their dream to buy their mother a house."</item>
		<item>"I have a house in Stratford and I got a house in Atlanta but I don't really live anywhere. I live on the road. I'm kind of like living in a suitcase, travelling so much."</item>
		<item>"Uggs. I think they're ugly. And I think big sunglasses are kind of overrated. I like big sunglasses but not those huge, round ones."</item>
		<item>"I would like to have a second album out and be touring, and hopefully have my own charity by then."</item>
		<item>"Just landed back in LA!! Weather is awesome.. IN AND OUT BURGER HERE WE COME!"</item>
		<item>"I have crushes, but they're all too old. Like Beyonce -she has a husband, I might get shot. I went up to give Beyonce a hug at the Grammys and Jay-Z said, watch out buddy! He was kidding, but you know.."</item>
		<item>"I sang to Nicole [Scherzinger] from the Pussycat Dolls. That was an amazing moment...It was hard to take my eyes off of her because she's so gorgeous."</item>
		<item>"My mom said I wasn't allowed to date until I was sixteen, but I broke that rule. She found out and said, I'm disappointed in you."</item>
		<item>"It would be a shame to go out with a hot girl you can't have a decent conversation with!"</item>
		<item>"I have my romantic moments - for sure."</item>
		<item>"A girl has to have a beautiful smile, beautiful eyes and she should have a good sense of humor. She should be honest, loving and trustworthy."</item>
		<item>"There's more people that like me than there are who hate me, so I kind of brush it off."</item>
		<item>"I still [use Twitter] as much as before. People write to me and say, I'm giving up, you're not talking to me. I just write them a simple message like, Never give up, you know? And it changes their life."</item>
		<item>"Singers aren't supposed to have dairy before a show, but we all know I'm a rule breaker. Pizza is just so good."</item>
		<item>"The day I was born, March 1, 1994, Celine Dion was solid at #1 on the Billboard Hot 100 with \"The Power of Love.\" Not a bad song to start your life on."</item>
		<item>"Dare to be a sucky skateboarder or a lousy video editor or a completely crappy golfer. If we do only the stuff we're good at, we never learn anything new."</item>
		<item>"I'd just gotten the ugliest haircut of my life the day before. My trademark swoosh was hacked off into this squarish situation that kind of reminded me of Bart Simpson."</item>
		<item>"If I can do just one-tenth of the good Michael Jackson did for others, I can really make a difference in this world."</item>
		<item>"My foot was broken. In the middle of a song. In front of twelve thousand people. And Taylor Swift. I won't tell you the words that went through my head."</item>
		<item>"I definitely want to buy my mom a house once I get enough funds. I think that’s definitely something that I want to do. I think that any person, it’s their dream to buy their mother a house."</item>
		<item>"I have one person that I’ll be sending flowers to and that’s my mom. She’s been there since the beginning and has given up a lot for me, I’m very blessed to have her. She likes roses, so I think I might send her the One Less Lonely Girl bouquet."</item>
		<item>"I haven’t been able to be as romantic as probably I will be able to be, but I think that being a gentleman is what matters; taking them out to a nice dinner, open the doors, stuff like that. Flowers are great, but love is better ? you know what I mean?"</item>
		<item>"Baby when you’re with me, it’s like an angel came by, and took me to heaven."</item>
		<item>"Baby know for sho’, I’ll never let you go"</item>
		<item>"A minute with you is worth more than A thousand days without your love."</item>
		<item>"I'm running out of time, Where is my runaway love? "</item>
		<item>"I'd face a thousand years of pain for my girl."</item>
		<item>"How many torn photographs saw you taping back?"</item>
		<item>"At first, I didn't know if this is what I wanted. But I really love to be in the spotlight, and just be the center of the attention."</item>
		<item>"I put videos of the competition on YouTube for them to see, and it just kind of blew up."</item>
		<item>"I'm telling you, people. Everyday we wake up is another blessing. Follow your dreams and don't let anyone stop you. Never say never."</item>
		<item>"Two people can look at the same thing and see it differently..."</item>
		<item>"never say never that's my favorite quote"</item>
		<item>"I think older people can appreciate my music because I really show my heart when I sing, and it's not corny. I think I can grow as an artist, and my fans will grow with me."</item>
		<item>"I'm looking forward to influencing others in a positive way. My message is you can do anything if you just put your mind to it."</item>
		<item>"Keep Going Strong!"</item>
		<item>"Someone once told me to never dream. I said NEVER SAY NEVER!!!"</item>
		<item>"I want my world to be fun- like no one can stop me!"</item>
		<item>"You guys are evil. Canada's the best country in the world. We go to the doctor and we don't need to worry about paying him, but here, your whole life, you're broke because of medical bills."</item>
		<item>"Use them lips for kissing, girl.. if you wanna ride with me."</item>
		<item>"Although I might not agree with her at the time, she's always right."</item>
		<item>"I felt like a baby bunny smelling like a spring flower. i felt good... llike salt or freshly baked bread. "</item>
		<item>"To all the haters out there I wish you the best. You cant bring me down. I wake up everyday grateful for the opportunity and grateful to the fans."</item>
		<item>"I'm in pieces, so come fix me"</item>
		<item>"I'm crazy, I'm nuts. Just the way my brain works. I'm not normal. I think differently. My mind is always racing."</item>
		<item>"Singers aren't supposed to have dairy before a show, but we all know I'm a rule breaker. Pizza is just so good!"</item>
		<item>"I really don’t believe in abortion. It’s like killing a baby?"</item>
		<item>"My first date has been sort of mythologized as \"Bieber’s Dating Disaster.\" I took her to King’s a buffet restaurant. Yes, I wore a white shirt. Yes, I got spaghetti."</item>
		<item>"There are lots of things I really like besides girls. Like pizza. And pranking. And CHUCK NORRIS."</item>
		<item>"It was like I opened my eyes one day and noticed that the world was full of beautiful girls. And I’ve had a hard time hard time thinking about anything else since then."</item>
		<item>"I'm looking forward to influencing others in a positive way. My message is you can do anything if you just put your mind to it."</item>
		<item>"I've got my eye on a few things to spend my money on. I've got my own bank card but I am really good with money. I don't spend too much at all."</item>
		<item>"For you, I would have done whatever. And no i can’t believe we’re not together."</item>
		<item>"Flowers are great, but love is better."</item>
		<item>"Baby take my open heart and all it offers ’cause this is as unconditional as it?ll ever get."</item>
		<item>"Can't make up your mind, please dont waste my time; Not trying to rewind."</item>
		<item>"I really don't believe in abortion. It's like killing a baby?"</item>
		<item>"We're trying to set up a movie for me in the near future. It's going to be similar to the story of how I got discovered. Kinda like my own version of '8 Mile.'"</item>
		<item>"I'm looking forward to influencing others in a positive way. My message is you can do anything if you just put your mind to it."</item>
		<item>"Before you criticize someone, walk a mile in their shoes. That way, you're a mile away and you have their shoes."</item>
		<item>"If you don't dream big, there's no use of dreaming. If you don't have faith, there's nothing worth believing."</item>
		<item>"So remember, this is bieber's world. you're just living in it. Bieber or Die."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes this is the most fun ever. other times its really hard and there's so much pressure."</item>
		<item>"To all the haters out there I wish you the best. You cant bring me down. I wake up everyday grateful for the opportunity and grateful to the fans."</item>
		<item>"Baby when you're with me, it's like an angel came by, and took me to heaven."</item>
		<item>"Baby know for sho', I'll never let you go."</item>
		<item>"When I met you girl my heart went knock knock, Now them butterflies in my stomach won't stop stop."</item>
		<item>"She's got everything I need, and I'ma tell her one time. Give you everything you need down to my last dime."</item>
		<item>"I'm kind of like living in a suitcase, travelling so much."</item>
		<item>"I think that being a gentleman is what matters; taking them out to a nice dinner, open the doors, stuff like that."</item>
		<item>"Flowers are great, but love is better."</item>
		<item>"Baby take my open heart and all it offers 'cause this is as unconditional as it'll ever get."</item>
		<item>"You know you love me, I know you care, and I would never not be there."</item>
		<item>"For you, I would have done whatever. And no i can't believe we're not together."</item>
		<item>"While I'm losin you.... Shake me til' you can wake me from this bad dream, I'm goin down."</item>
		<item>"I'm in pieces, so come fix me."</item>
		<item>"Eenie meenie miney mo', Catch a bad chick by her toe, If she holla (if, if, if she holla) let her go."</item>
		<item>"Cant make up your mind, please dont waste my time; Not trying to rewind."</item>
		<item>"I felt like a baby bunny smelling like a spring flower. i felt good... llike salt or freshly baked bread."</item>
		<item>"Although I might not agree with her at the time, she's always right."</item>
		<item>"You ready? Are you ready? I was born ready!"</item>
		<item>"I want my world to be fun. No parents, no rules, no nothing. Like, no one can stop me. No one can stop me."</item>
		<item>"I won't stop until I find, My runaway love."</item>
		<item>"I'm running out of time, Where is my runaway love?"</item>
		<item>"The sweet love of mine."</item>
		<item>"I'm just trying to be cool, cool, cool. What you expect me to do?"</item>
		<item>"Ou see my baby over here hit the road, Where she's going that's what nobody knows."</item>
		<item>"I can't imagine life without your touch, And every kiss that you give, You fill me up."</item>
		<item>"Out of all things in life that I could fear. The only thing that would hurt me is if you weren't here."</item>
		<item>"Between me and love, You're the common denominator."</item>
		<item>"I'd face a thousand years of pain for my girl."</item>
		<item>"You're the light that feeds the sun In my world."</item>
		<item>"Baby, baby, baby oooh. Like baby, baby, baby nooo."</item>
		<item>"There's gonna be one less lonely girl"</item>
		<item>"Me, plus you...I'ma tell you one time."</item>
		<item>"She makes me happy, I know where I'll be. Right by your side cause she is the one."</item>
		<item>"Many have called but the chosen is you. Whatever you want shawty I'll give it to you."</item>
		<item>"You look so deep. You no that it humbles me."</item>
		<item>"You'll be my number one girl. Always making time for you."</item>
		<item>"One love, My one heart, My one life for sure."</item>
		<item>"Your world, is my world, And my fight, is your fight."</item>
		<item>"When I met you girl my heart went knock knock. Now them butterflies in my stomach wont stop stop."</item>
		<item>"I don't need nothing else, I promise girl I swear."</item>
		<item>"I just need somebody to love"</item>
		<item>"Whenever you knock me down I will not stay on the ground."</item>
		<item>"I will never say never! I will fight till forever!"</item>
		<item>"Just shake me til' you wake me from this bad dream."</item>
		<item>"And I just can't believe we ain't together"</item>
		<item>"We're just friends, what are you saying?"</item>
		<item>"My first love broke my heart for the first time and I was like..."</item>
		<item>"I'm going down, down, down, down."</item>
		<item>"We will never ever ever be apart."</item>
		<item>"No matter how talented you are, not everybody is going to like you. But that's life, just stay strong."</item>
		<item>"You can't please everyone. You need to stick up for yourself, but you can always be kind."</item>
		<item>"I've had a few gigs where things have got out of hand and there has been a huge crush with my fans. They are important and I don't want them being hurt. They are a mad crowd."</item>
		<item>"I wish we had another time. I wish we had another place."</item>
		<item>"This is so wrong, I can't go on. Till you believe that...That should be me."</item>
		<item>"That should be me, feelin' your kiss. That should be me, buyin' you gifts."</item>
		<item>"That should be me, holdin' your hand. That should be me. Makin' you laugh. That should be me, this is so sad."</item>
		<item>"Did you forget all the plans that you made with me? 'Cause baby I didn't!"</item>
		<item>"Do you do what you did when you did with me? Does he love you the way I can?"</item>
		<item>"Everybody's laughing in my mind. Rumors spreading 'bout this other guy."</item>
		<item>"Nothing will ever come between us, Ill be standing right next to you...Right next to you."</item>
		<item>"One day when the sky is falling, Ill be standing right next to you...Right next to you."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, you are my dream, theres not a thing I wont do. Ill give my life up for you, cos you are my dream."</item>
		<item>"I dont wanna be so old and gray. Reminiscing bout these better days but convince just telling us to let go. So well never know."</item>
		<item>"See we both fightin every inch of our fibers. Cuz aint no way its gonna end right but we are both too foolish to stop."</item>
		<item>"See like Adam abd Eve Tragedy was our destiny. Like Sonny and Cher I dont care I got you baby."</item>
		<item>"Everything we have is stuck in the moment and theres nothing my heart can do. To fight with time and space cause Im still stuck in the moment with you."</item>
		<item>"Now we dont wanna fall but were trippin in our hearts and its reckless and clumsy. Cause I know you cant love me here."</item>
		<item>"Now you dont wanna let go and I dont wanna let you know. That there might be something real between us two Who knew?"</item>
		<item>"You and I, both know it cant work. Its all fun and games. Til someone gets hurt and I dont, I wont let that be you."</item>
		<item>"Bonnie and Clyde Never had to hide like. We do...We do."</item>
		<item>"Now Romeo and Juliet. Bet they never felt the way we felt."</item>
		<item>"Baby I'm yo docta, I could be yo rocker, swaggin' I'm not braggin' but I swear that I could rock ya."</item>
		<item>"Baby I'm not crazy, I got swag like Patrick Schwayze ya know them haters never phase me that's not how my momma raised me."</item>
		<item>"Baby you just need to stop. I'm busy out performing and I'm going to the top. I got so much to lose, so I'm steady gettin gwap but them haters go down and we just get to watch."</item>
		<item>"Amazing, I'm blazing. Look over here, said that I'm amazing. Nobody's facing, what I'm facing. Set a pace, so I can race without pacing."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
