<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"And I want you to know, you’re far from the usual."</item>
		<item>"God knows that I’d do anything for a part two."</item>
		<item>"What she mean to me is what I mean to rap."</item>
		<item>"You had a lot of dreams that transformed to visions."</item>
		<item>"When you was just a youngin’, your looks were so precious. But now you’re grown up, so fly, it’s like a blessin’. But ya can’t have a man look at ya for five seconds without ya bein’ insecure."</item>
		<item>"Had a lot of moments that didn’t last forever, now you’re in the corner tryin’ to put it together – how to love."</item>
		<item>"You had a lot of crooks try to steal your heart, never really had luck – couldn’t never figure out how to love."</item>
		<item>"And I got the haters like when will he stop? Maybe a minute after never, so set your clocks."</item>
		<item>"She my motivation, I’m her transportation. ‘Cause I let her ride, while I drive her crazy. Then I just keep going, going like I’m racing. When I’m done she hold me like a conversation."</item>
		<item>"I put her on my plate, then I do the dishes."</item>
		<item>"Rain on my head, call that brainstorming."</item>
		<item>"Girl, I turn that thing into a rain forest."</item>
		<item>"More beautiful than the world, word. Matter of fact, beautiful ain’t the word. Unexplainable is the beauty of her. And I’ll be the race car, hitting her curves."</item>
		<item>"I’m in so much ice, they yell ‘Skate Wayne!"</item>
		<item>"Tell ‘em kiss my ass, call it kiss and tell."</item>
		<item>"I got through that sentence like a subject and a predicate."</item>
		<item>"And I call it like I see it and my glasses on. But most of y’all don’t get the picture ‘less the flash is on."</item>
		<item>"I beat the beat up, call it self defense."</item>
		<item>"Life is the bitch, and death is her sister."</item>
		<item>"So misunderstood, but what’s a world without enigma?"</item>
		<item>"Swagger down pat, call my shit Patricia."</item>
		<item>"Excuse my charisma, Vodka with a spritzer."</item>
		<item>"I think you stand under me if you don’t understand me."</item>
		<item>"Real G’s move in silence like Lasagna..."</item>
		<item>"Try to kick me while I’m down. I’ll break your leg."</item>
		<item>"Mind so sharp, I f*ck around and cut my head off."</item>
		<item>"And I don’t mind when we fall out as long as we fall back into it."</item>
		<item>"Smoke a lot of weed, but I could never forget ya."</item>
		<item>"We probably ain’t supposed to be together, but I wonder if my love of her could last forever."</item>
		<item>"And she ain’t sure about me, but can’t go without me."</item>
		<item>"Damn you the sh*t, and I’ll rip my heart out, and hand you the sh*t."</item>
		<item>"Appetite for lovin’, ma, I’m hungry like the scavenger."</item>
		<item>"I’m cruisin’ on the road of life, but I need a passenger."</item>
		<item>"Shawty I’m a pro and you are lookin’ like the prototype."</item>
		<item>"And with her brain – she should make the honor roll."</item>
		<item>"We at the pool and she lookin’ like a center fold."</item>
		<item>"I’m just sayin’ with my love, I could feed her soul."</item>
		<item>"Shawty badder than a 3 year old."</item>
		<item>"Me and shawty go together like chemicals."</item>
		<item>"Okay, you want me up in a cage, then I’ll come out in beast mode."</item>
		<item>"Put the d*** in they mouth, so I guess it’s f*** what they say."</item>
		<item>"I’m stickin to the script, you n*ggas skippin’ scenes."</item>
		<item>"I don’t go around fire expectin’ not to sweat."</item>
		<item>"Been to hell and back, I can show you vouchers."</item>
		<item>"Yeah, my life a bitch, but you nothin’ bout her."</item>
		<item>"But it’s f*ck the world, get a child out her."</item>
		<item>"Throw dirt on me and grow a wild flower."</item>
		<item>"I don’t like to stop. I believe when you stop, you die."</item>
		<item>"With the gun in this position, you could call it Kamasutra."</item>
		<item>"This is brain surgery. Ski masks on my bullets, let ‘em commit brain burglary. Emergency, it’s an emergency. Someone in all black left the whole scene burgundy."</item>
		<item>"You just see Jill on the hill, I knock Jack off."</item>
		<item>"Shoot you on the front porch and knock you to the back yard."</item>
		<item>"And I keep that hammer, do you wanna get nailed down?"</item>
		<item>"I take you farther than Zimbabwe."</item>
		<item>"Paper chasin’, money runnin’ like andale."</item>
		<item>"I school you n*ggas, but none of yous get A’s."</item>
		<item>"All you boys bustas, so soft, bet the wind blew ‘em."</item>
		<item>"I’ma call my guns jumpers, cause my bullets just leapin to ‘em."</item>
		<item>"Call me Mr. Kill Em All."</item>
		<item>"My word is my pride, the wisdom is weak, and that’s word from the wise."</item>
		<item>"Confidence is a stain they can’t wipe off."</item>
		<item>"Just hope you heaven sent and you’re hell proof."</item>
		<item>"The spot gets smaller and I get bigger tryin’ to get in where I fit in."</item>
		<item>"The top gets higher the more that I climb."</item>
		<item>"I search, but never find. Hurt, but never cry. I work and forever tired."</item>
		<item>"You keep the sunshine, save me the rain."</item>
		<item>"I seen nights full of pain, days of the same."</item>
		<item>"I got ice in my veins, blood in my eyes, hate in my heart, love in my mind."</item>
		<item>"Midnight cowboy. My flow is a dog, down boy."</item>
		<item>"I’m the cashier, I change girls."</item>
		<item>"And haters at an all-time high. Everybody got a hater like a f*ckin’ iPod."</item>
		<item>"Stuck in the hood, like they poured cement on us."</item>
		<item>"Hope you ain’t too tired to cry and I hope you know you ain’t never too alive to die."</item>
		<item>"And I’m seeing what you need and I’m thinkin’ it’s me."</item>
		<item>"And Weezy transform a good girl to a freak."</item>
		<item>"I transform smaller and she puts me in her pants."</item>
		<item>"I can turn you from a human to a Carter. Take you off the bench, turn you to a starter."</item>
		<item>"I can transform ya, like a transformer."</item>
		<item>"I can change your life, make it so new. Make you never want to go back to the old you."</item>
		<item>"I shoot you nine times like you was 50, but you won’t be as likely as 50."</item>
		<item>"I don’t need the Hot Boyz, I still keep my heat."</item>
		<item>"Even in the dungeon, I glow. Even if it ain’t sunny, I glow."</item>
		<item>"Life’s a b*tch, now die for her."</item>
		<item>"Elevator in my crib ’cause it’s 5 floors. I’m not expectin’ you to have one in yours."</item>
		<item>"We are not the same. I’m a martian, this is Space Jam."</item>
		<item>"Put me in the wild — I be there for a while."</item>
		<item>"If you’s a hater. I’m eatin’, you’s a waiter."</item>
		<item>"We the motha f*cka’s like M.I.L.F., my n*gga."</item>
		<item>"I love my baby mamas, they my highest honors."</item>
		<item>"B*tch, I go hard like the boy from 300."</item>
		<item>"Stop playin, I’m fresher than a Degree stick."</item>
		<item>"Well of course, I smoke mad weed, I’m on my high horse."</item>
		<item>"Money spread like germs, get sick n*gga."</item>
		<item>"Make the girls say my name like roll call."</item>
		<item>"Time to do the thing, that’s word to your wrist watch."</item>
		<item>"And everybody watch your back when you’re in the front."</item>
		<item>"The money keep calling, I hear this sh*t dialing, and they say money talks, you can hear my sh*t holler’n."</item>
		<item>"Crown fit me good, I ain’t even got to try on."</item>
		<item>"I look in the flames and see the hotter me."</item>
		<item>"I’m the bomb baby, watch me nuke this sh-t."</item>
		<item>"I pop like lolli’s, you drop like eyelids."</item>
		<item>"New Orleans coroner, his name is Frank Minyard, f-ck with me wrong, you’ll be waking up in his yard."</item>
		<item>"I still eat rappers. Mmm. Scrumptious."</item>
		<item>"Man I go crazy on the beat I go Nimrod. Man I act a ass, treat the beat like a hemorrhoid. Man I go to work on the beat, call it employ. Man I kicks it, b-tch get your shin guard."</item>
		<item>"Pump to your chest, I ain’t talking CPR."</item>
		<item>"Ran into a super woman, turned her to a super bitch, hit her with that super d-ck, she be cumming super quick."</item>
		<item>"My pockets too deep, I f-ck around and drown her. All we do is shop until we drop."</item>
		<item>"I take her to the vet, cause she a bad bitch."</item>
		<item>"Pockets too deep, shawty you gon’ have to climb out."</item>
		<item>"She wants to own me and I ain’t trying to fight it."</item>

	</string-array>
</resources>
