<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"When it comes down to it, I let them think what they want. If they care enough to bother with what I do, then I'm already better than them anyways."</item>
		<item>"It's better for the whole world to know you, even as a sex star, than never to be known at all."</item>
		<item>"They way it is the individual is the underdog, and with all the things a corporation has going for them the individual comes out banged on her head. The artist is nothing. It's really tragic."</item>
		<item>"Some people have been unkind. If I say I want to grow as an actress, they look at my figure. If I say I want to develop, to learn my craft, they laugh. Somehow they don't expect me to be serious about my work."</item>
		<item>"I'm going to be a great movie star some day."</item>
		<item>"The Seven Year Itch"</item>
		<item>"President Kennedy is very democratic and very penetrating."</item>
		<item>"I want to grow old without facelifts. I want to have the courage to be loyal to the face I have made."</item>
		<item>"I dont know who invented High heels but all women owe him a lot."</item>
		<item>"I dont mind living in a man's world as long as I can be a woman in it."</item>
		<item>"Fame is fickle and I know it. It has its compensations, but it also has its drawbacks and I have experienced them both."</item>
		<item>"It's nice to be included in people's fantasies, but you also like to be accepted for your own sake."</item>
		<item>"I've never been in a Hollywood fight or feud. I have the most wonderful memory for forgetting things."</item>
		<item>"I wanna guy I can look up to . . . I just gotta feel that whoever I marry has some real regard for me, aside from all that loving stuff."</item>
		<item>"They've said I want to direct pictures. I couldn't direct traffic."</item>
		<item>"I've fallen in love with Brooklyn. I'm going to buy a little house in Brooklyn and live there. I'll go to the coast only when I have to make a picture."</item>
		<item>"I've given pure sex appeal very little thought. If I had to think about it, I'm sure it would frighten me."</item>
		<item>"Ever notice that what the hell is always the right decision?"</item>
		<item>"You can't sleep your way into being a star. It takes much, much more. But it helps a lot of actresses get their first chance that way."</item>
		<item>"I was never used to being happy, so that wasn't something I ever took for granted. You see, I was brought up differently from the average American child because the average child is brought up expecting to be happy."</item>
		<item>"I think cheesecake helps call attention to you. Then you can follow through and prove yourself."</item>
		<item>"I am involved in a freedom ride protesting the loss of the minority rights belonging to the few remaining earthbound stars. All we demanded was our right to twinkle."</item>
		<item>"I restore myself when I'm alone. A career is born in public, talent in privacy."</item>
		<item>"I'm a failure as a woman. My men expect so much of me, because of the image they've made of me and that I've made of myself, as a sex symbol. Men expect so much, and I can't live up to it."</item>
		<item>"Dogs never bite me. Just humans."</item>
		<item>"I don't consider myself an intellectual. And this is not one of my aims. But I admire intellectual people."</item>
		<item>"A photographer once told me that my two best points are between my waist and my neck."</item>
		<item>"Isn't there any other part of the matzo you can eat?"</item>
		<item>"When you're a failure in Hollywood, that's like starving to death outside a banquet hall, with smells of filet mignon driving you crazy."</item>
		<item>"I like actors very much, but to marry one would be like marrying your brother. You look too much alike in the mirror."</item>
		<item>"Even though I was born there, I still can't think of one good thing to say about it. If I close my eyes, and picture LA, all I see is one big varicose vein."</item>
		<item>"I don't understand why people aren't a little more generous with each other."</item>
		<item>"He [Arthur Miller] wouldn't have married me if I had been nothing but a dumb blonde."</item>
		<item>"To a reporter: Please don't make me a joke."</item>
		<item>"If I play a stupid girl and ask a stupid question I've got to follow it through. What am I supposed to do - look intelligent?"</item>
		<item>"I don't want to make money, I just want to be wonderful."</item>
		<item>"A sex symbol becomes a thing. I just hate to be a thing."</item>
		<item>"Creativity has got to start with humanity and when you're a human being, you feel, you suffer."</item>
		<item>"The only person I know who is in worse shape than I am (on Montgomery Clift)."</item>
		<item>"Moscow Gatecrash: A Peer Behind the Curtain."</item>
		<item>"It stirs up envy, fame does. People feel fame gives them some kind of privilege to walk up to you and say anything to you - and it won't hurt your feelings - like it's happening to your clothing."</item>
		<item>"Why haven't I the right to grow and expand like everybody else?"</item>
		<item>"It isn't necessary to use your voice in any special way (to sound sexy). If you think something sexy the voice just naturally goes along."</item>
		<item>"You would think all other women kept their bodies in vaults."</item>
		<item>"Mv first contract with 20th Century-Fox was like my first vaccination. It didn't take."</item>
		<item>"People ask me if I am going on making cheesecake pictures now that I'm a star. My answer is that as long as there is a boy in Korea who wants a pinup of me, I'll go on posing for them."</item>
		<item>"Husbands are chiefly good as lovers when they are betraying their wives."</item>
		<item>"Everybody is always tugging at you. They'd all like a sort of chunk out of you. I don' think they realize it, but it's like 'grrr do this, grr do that...' But you do want to stay intact--intact and on two feet."</item>
		<item>"If I'd observed all the rules, I'd never have got anywhere."</item>
		<item>"My work is the only ground I've ever had to stand on. I seem to have a whole superstructure with no foundation but I'm working on the foundation."</item>
		<item>"Acting isn't something you do. Instead of doing it, it occurs. If you're going to start with logic, you might as well give up. You can have conscious preparation, but you have unconscious results."</item>
		<item>"People respect you because they feel you've survived hard times and endured, and although you've become famous, you haven't become phony."</item>
		<item>"Hollywood's a place where they'll pay you a thousand dollars for a kiss, and fifty cents for your soul. I know, because I turned down the first offer often enough and held out for the fifty cents."</item>
		<item>"(Joe) You've never heard such cheering."</item>
		<item>"I want to continue my growth in every way."</item>
		<item>"I feel wonderful. I'm incorporated!"</item>
		<item>"Every morning I walk across my apartment rolling an empty soda bottle between my ankles, in order to preserve my balance."</item>
		<item>"...If you can make a girl laugh - you can make her do anything..."</item>
		<item>"Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius, and it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely stupid."</item>
		<item>"Everyone's a star and deserves the right to twinkle."</item>
		<item>"I won't be satisfied until people want to hear me sing without looking at me."</item>
		<item>"I never intentionally mean to hurt anyone, but you can't be too nice to people you work with, else they will trample you to death."</item>
		<item>"With fame, you know, you can read about yourself, somebody else's ideas about you, but what's important is how you feel about yourself--for survival and living day to day with what comes up."</item>
		<item>"First, I'm trying to prove to myself that I'm a person. Then maybe I'll convince myself that I'm an actress."</item>
		<item>"I've never dropped anyone I believed in."</item>
		<item>"A sex symbol becomes a thing. I hate being a thing."</item>
		<item>"I think if other girls know how bad I was when I started they'll be encouraged. I finally made up my mind I wanted to be an actress ~and I was not going to let my lack of confidence ruin my chances."</item>
		<item>"I always sleep with my mouth open. I know because it's open when I wake up."</item>
		<item>"Blond hair and breasts, that's how I got started. I couldn't act. All I had was blond hair and a body men liked. The reason I got ahead is that I was lucky and met the right men."</item>
		<item>"Of the nude pictures: Sure I posed. I needed the money."</item>
		<item>"A career is born in public -- talent in privacy."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to play sex roles any more. I'm tired of being known as the girl with the shape."</item>
		<item>"[Crawford, who won an Academy Award for Mildred Pierce ,] had a gigantic orgasm and shrieked like a maniac ... another round."</item>
		<item>"What good is it being Marilyn Monroe? Why can't I just be an ordinary woman? A woman who can have a family ... I'd settle for just one baby. My own baby."</item>
		<item>"Remember now, cheers, no tears..."</item>
		<item>"You know who I always depend on? Not strangers, not friends. The telephone! That's my best friend. I seldom write letters, but I love calling friends, especially late at night, when I can't sleep."</item>
		<item>"She [Sadie Thompson] was a girl who knew how to be gay even when she was sad. And that's important--you know?"</item>
		<item>"I have never been very good at being a member of any group - more than a group of two, that is."</item>
		<item>"I never wear stockings or underclothes because I think it is important to breathe freely."</item>
		<item>"How to Be Very, Very Popular."</item>
		<item>"I don't want to make money. I just want to be wonderful."</item>
		<item>"Fame is fickle and I know it. It has its compensations, but it also has its drawbacks and I've experienced them both."</item>
		<item>"Gee, I never thought I had an effect on people until I was in Korea."</item>
		<item>"I've been on a calendar, but never on time."</item>
		<item>"There was my name up in lights. I said, 'God, somebody's made a mistake.' But there it was, in lights. And I sat there and said, 'Remember, you're not a star.' Yet there it was up in lights."</item>
		<item>"was a small-town girl."</item>
		<item>"Being a sex symbol is a heavy load to carry, especially when one is tired, hurt and bewildered."</item>
		<item>"Only the public can make a star. It's the studios who try to make a system out of it."</item>
		<item>"I have feelings too. I am still human. All I want is to be loved, for myself and for my talent."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I've been to a party where no one spoke to me for a whole evening. The men, frightened by their wives or sweeites...the ladies would gang up in a corner and discuss my dangerous character."</item>
		<item>"I've often stood silent at a party for hours listening to my movie idols turn into dull and little people."</item>
		<item>"It's all make believe, isn't it?"</item>
		<item>"That's the trouble, a sex symbol becomes a thing. But if I'm going to be a symbol of something, I'd rather have it sex than some other things we've got symbols of."</item>
		<item>"I feel as though it's all happening to someone right next to me. I'm close, I can feel it, I can hear it, but it isn't really me."</item>
		<item>"I've always felt those articles somehow reveal more about the writers than they do about me."</item>
		<item>"I am invariably late for appointments - sometimes as much as two hours. I've tried to change my ways but the things that make me late are too strong, and too pleasing."</item>
		<item>"If I'm a star, then the people made me a star."</item>
		<item>"If I'd observed all the rules, I'd never have got anywhere"</item>
		<item>"Wouldn't it be nice to be like men, just getting notches in your belt, having affairs with the most atttractive men . . . and not getting emotionally involved."</item>
		<item>"I used to say to myself, 'What the devil have you got to be proud about, Marilyn Monroe?' And I'd answer, 'Everything, everything,' and I'd walk slowly and turn my head slowly as if I were a queen."</item>
		<item>"It's woman's spirit and mood a man has to stimulate in order to make sex interesting. The real lover is the man who can thrill you by touching your head or smiling into your eyes or just staring into space."</item>
		<item>"I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot."</item>
		<item>"The thing I want more than anything else? I want to have children. I used to feel for every child I had, I would adopt another."</item>
		<item>"What do I wear in bed? Why, Chanel No. 5, of course."</item>
		<item>"Arthur Miller wouldn't have married me if I had been nothing but a dumb blonde."</item>
		<item>"You can't sleep your way into being a star, though. It takes much, much more. But it helps. A lot of actresses get their first chance that way."</item>
		<item>"I am not interested in money. I just want to be wonderful."</item>
		<item>"I don't forgive people because I'm weak, I forgive them because I am strong enough to know people make mistakes."</item>
		<item>"I always felt I was nobody and the only way for me to be somebody was to be... well, somebody else."</item>
		<item>"It's better to be unhappy alone than unhappy with someone - so far."</item>
		<item>"What I really want to say is that what the world needs is a feeling of kinship. Everybody: stars, laborers, blacks, Jews, Arabs - we're all brothers!"</item>
		<item>"My marriage brought me neither happiness nor pain. My husband and I hardly spoke to each other. This wasn't because we were angry. We had nothing to say."</item>
		<item>"The nicest thing for me is sleep, then at least i can dream."</item>
		<item>"It was like working with a little sister."</item>
		<item>"Dreaming about being an actress, is more exciting then being one."</item>
		<item>"ever since I became a movie star I've been really weird"</item>
		<item>"If I play a stupid girl, and ask a stupid question, I've got to follow it through. What am I supposed to do, look intelligent?"</item>
		<item>"To put it bluntly, I seem to have a whole superstructure with no foundation. But I'm working on the foundation."</item>
		<item>"I have too many fantasies to be a housewife. I guess I am a fantasy."</item>
		<item>"I knew I belonged to the public and to the world, not because I was talented or even beautiful, but because I had never belonged to anything or anyone else."</item>
		<item>"I've been on a calendar, but I've never been on time."</item>
		<item>"I restore myself when I'm alone."</item>
		<item>"An actress is not a machine, but they treat you like a machine. A money machine."</item>
		<item>"I'm very definitely a woman and I enjoy it."</item>
		<item>"I don't mind living in a man's world as long as I can be a woman in it."</item>
		<item>"Sex is a part of nature. I go along with nature."</item>
		<item>"Nights are not just for sleep."</item>
		<item>"Men are so willing to respect anything that bores them."</item>
		<item>"I don't mind making jokes, but I don't want to look like one."</item>
		<item>"Dogs have never hurt me. Only men have."</item>
		<item>"They think I'm crazy, ... But trust me, I'm 100 percent there."</item>
		<item>"The body is meant to be seen, not all covered up."</item>
		<item>"No one ever called me pretty when I was a little girl"</item>
		<item>"Everybody is always tugging at you. They'd all like a sort of chunk out of you. I don' think they realize it, but it's like 'grrr do this, grr do that...' But you do want to stay intact and on two feet."</item>
		<item>"An actor is supposed to be a sensitive instrument. Isaac Stern takes good care of his violin. What if everyone jumped on his violin?"</item>
		<item>"It's better to be unhappy alone than unhappy with someone."</item>
		<item>"Unfortunately, I am involved in a freedom ride protesting the loss of the minority rights belonging to the few remaining earthbound stars. All we demanded was our right to twinkle."</item>
		<item>"Everyone's just laughing at me. I hate it. Big breasts, big ass, big deal, Can't I be anything else ? Gee, how long can you be sexy?"</item>
		<item>"Men who think that a woman's past love affairs lessen her love for them are usually stupid and weak. A woman can bring a new love to each man she loves, providing there are not too many."</item>
		<item>"If you can make a girl laugh - you can make her do anything."</item>
		<item>"A career is wonderful, but you can't curl up with it on a cold night."</item>
		<item>"Beneath the makeup and behind the smile I'm just a girl who wishes for the world."</item>
		<item>"It's often just enough to be with someone. I don't need to touch them. Not even talk. A feeling passes between you both. You're not alone."</item>
		<item>"The trouble with censors is that they worry if a girl has cleavage. They ought to worry if she hasn't any."</item>
		<item>"Imperfection is beauty. Madness is genius and it is better to be absolutely ridiculous then absolutly boring."</item>
		<item>"A wise girl kisses but doesn't love, leaves before she is left and forgets before she is forgotten."</item>
		<item>"No one ever told me I was pretty when I was a little girl. All little girls should be told they're pretty, even if they aren't."</item>
		<item>"It stirs up envy, fame does. People...feel fame gives them some kind of privilege to walk up to you and say anything to you--and it won't hurt your feelings--like it's happening to your clothing."</item>
		<item>"A career is born in public, talent in privacy."</item>
		<item>"Some people have been unkind. If I say I want to grow as an actress, they look at my figure. If I say I want to develop, to learn my craft, they laugh. Somehow they don't expect me to be serious about my work."</item>
		<item>"It takes a smart brunette to play a dumb blonde."</item>
		<item>"Husbands are chiefly good lovers when they are betraying their wives."</item>
		<item>"I love to do the things the censors won't pass."</item>
		<item>"I used to think as I looked at the Hollywood night, 'there must be thousands of girls sitting alone like me, dreaming of becoming a movie star. But I'm not going to worry about them. I'm dreaming the hardest.'"</item>
		<item>"I am good, but not an angel. I do sin, but I am not the devil. I am pretty, but not beautiful. I have friends, but I am not the peacemaker. I am just a small girl in a big world trying to find someone to love."</item>
		<item>"Fame will go by and, so long, I've had you, Fame. If it goes by, I've always known it was fickle."</item>
		<item>"I learned to walk as a baby and I haven't had a lesson since."</item>
		<item>"There's only one sort of natural blonde on earth - albinos."</item>
		<item>"Hollywood is a place where they'll pay you a thousand dollars for a kiss and fifty cents for your soul."</item>
		<item>"I always felt insecure and in the way, but most of all I felt scared. I guess I wanted love more than anything else in the world."</item>
		<item>"Before marriage, a girl has to make love to a man to hold him. After marriage, she has to hold him to make love to him."</item>
		<item>"It's not true I had nothing on, I had the radio on."</item>
		<item>"A wise girl kisses but doesn't love, listens but doesnt believe, and leaves before she is left."</item>
		<item>"A woman can't be alone. She needs a man. A man and a woman support and strengthen each other. She just can't do it by herself."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
