<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"The world want a show... I'ma be the stage."</item>
		<item>"You can see a Scorpio sex drive in their eyes and often they bear a great sexual appearance."</item>
		<item>"We can admire what we see, but we can only love what we truly know."</item>
		<item>"Stay Loyal, Humble, and Hungry."</item>
		<item>"The More Real you get, The More Unreal Things will."</item>
		<item>"Live good, eat good."</item>
		<item>"I work hard, not for the results or your opinions, but because it's the only thing I know how to do."</item>
		<item>"I'ma make you feel like a virgin again."</item>
		<item>"Lil Homie. Stay focused got shit to do."</item>
		<item>"These bright lights turn me to a monster!"</item>
		<item>"Inspire the aspiring."</item>
		<item>"My heart big, but it beat quiet."</item>
		<item>"Miss me if you blink twice."</item>
		<item>"Uhh, sunshine like the brightest day. Momma do you remember the time, Michael J. When I seen the video I said hat's gon' be me. And I ain't have to dream, I made it reality"</item>
		<item>"I hate liars; fuck love I'm tired of trying."</item>
		<item>"Most of them girls I plan to never wife, but it's something about you that I like."</item>
		<item>"Ass up, legs up to the sky. I know this ain't your first time, so baby don't be... (acting shy up in this room like I make your nervous)"</item>
		<item>"Wanna give you that good love, fall in love me shorty you just might."</item>
		<item>"If I get it I'ma hit it right, I know you tired it's the middle of the night."</item>
		<item>"Let me taste between your legs, dang you got me so hard."</item>
		<item>"Let me kiss you to start it off, damn your lips so soft; make a playa wanna bite 'em off."</item>
		<item>"I sex harder; make you sweat sauna."</item>
		<item>"I'm in this bitch til my eyes white."</item>
		<item>"I don't ever feel like we vibing 'cause everytime we alone it's an awkward silence."</item>
		<item>"Can't take the heat, don't feel the fire."</item>
		<item>"Skip school, create my own lessons."</item>
		<item>"Young Money nigga, money longer than a lifespan."</item>
		<item>"More money to make, more pussy to smell."</item>
		<item>"Momma taught me well, Kush and the L. Paper everywhere like books just fell."</item>
		<item>"Leave the bitches, need the hoes. Life is a motherfuckin gamble, Peter Rose"</item>
		<item>"The best Rapper C.E.O. Fine as wine flow; Pinot Grigio."</item>
		<item>"150 on the dash can't even count; Keep fucking bitch, ain't shit to talk about."</item>
		<item>"Raise hell, boy hell yeah I'm hot hello Boy yellow, but my b-tch back from the ghetto."</item>
		<item>"Pedigree and swag is so cold, zero."</item>
		<item>"You can buy a person's hands but you can't buy their heart. The heart is where enthusiasm and loyalty is."</item>
		<item>"Success is simple. Do what's right, the right way, at the right time."</item>
		<item>"I'ma dog I'ma dog.. But that don't mean I'ma dog you out.... If i love when i love I'ma love everything around."</item>
		<item>"What you don't see with your eyes, don't witness with your mouth."</item>
		<item>"Is it better to be hated for who you are, than to be loved for someone you're not?"</item>
		<item>"You Cant hate/Love others without Loving/hating yourself first."</item>
		<item>"Y'all come first, it wouldn't be possible for me to get to the levels and goals I reach everyday and to achieve things without yall the fans."</item>
		<item>"Don't wanna live this world alone, loyalty is all i know."</item>
		<item>"Muthafuckas laughed at me, now everybody mad at me."</item>
		<item>"I didnt have to dream i made it my reality."</item>
		<item>"They can tell you how to do it but never did it."</item>
		<item>"You can tell more about a person by what they say about others than you can by what others say about them."</item>
		<item>"Don't be afraid to give up the good to go for the great."</item>
		<item>"To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment."</item>
		<item>"If I get it I'ma hit it right, I know you tired it's the middle of the night."</item>
		<item>"150 on the dash can't even count; Keep fucking bitch, ain't shit to talk about."</item>
		<item>"I didnt have to dream I made it my reality."</item>
		<item>"Let me kiss you to start it off, damn your lips so soft; make a playa wanna bite 'em off."</item>
		<item>"Cash stacking like tetris, his youthful effervescence."</item>
		<item>"He's next in line for the blessing, get your mind off mine, Hustle something and stop relying on mine, molding a lesson while u letting time fly by."</item>
		<item>"Diamond life, sugar baby we dynamite, Playboys and socialites, young n flyy flyy flyy."</item>
		<item>"Diamond life, Don't regret it now! and space joyriding! ChaCha away!"</item>
		<item>"Y'all ain't nothin' but cheap condoms."</item>
		<item>"She don't know me by my name, she just know my AIM."</item>
		<item>"All you gotta do is love me and be loyal."</item>
		<item>"Im into different broads, f-cking in foreign cars. Wizard of OZ, tear coloured Benz, I aint got a heart, No love shoot the cupid with a dart, danger in the park. Motherf-cker dont walk past dark."</item>
		<item>"Gambling cant rely on management. If its bout business Ima handle it. I see it all like an analyst."</item>
		<item>"Mutherf-ckers wanna take instead of give advice. N-ggas left me now Im living right. Trying to cheat death with a trick dice."</item>
		<item>"Looking at the murder rate never ask why. Colt 45, with a 4 5, the innocent die young cant judge life."</item>
		<item>"Hate lies, never truth when its televised. Devils on the screen, fire in their eyes."</item>
		<item>"I know my fault, I shouldve gave more. Now youre miles away and Im miles on tour."</item>
		<item>"It take time to realise what you really wanna know. You was ready for it all but your feelings I ignored."</item>
		<item>"I know feelings was hurt and you can blame me but Im sorry for the games that I played but now its too late."</item>
		<item>"Now your heart broken, tears in ya face. Ask myself why, looking at the sky If I could turn back Id make it all right."</item>
		<item>"Sittin on a plane Reminscing back when I made that mistake. I wish it never ended with a heartbreak."</item>
		<item>"Trying to win but the finish lines far, race against the odds. Race dont matter when you dead or start praying to the gods."</item>
		<item>"Last king living, give me space like a movement. Cream get the money, whip icy like cool whip."</item>
		<item>"Man you n-ggas aint balling in the bull pen. Riding on the black mag Im a cool kid."</item>
		<item>"Take a step as the world spin. Rumors come and go faster than a whirlwind."</item>
		<item>"Got a sign on my dick, bad bitches only."</item>
		<item>"Next day we in paradise promise to be loyal when honest, help out your family with a couple dollars."</item>
		<item>"Let me show you why tunnel of love lets float inside girl grab my hand now hold your ride take a chance for life, roll the dice."</item>
		<item>"I aint trying to hurt you now but I think Im in love for the first time."</item>
		<item>"Used to be a player but Im retired, ugh, as I lay down right beside ya."</item>
		<item>"Money is my pet peeve, give me hourly if there is none at all, than Im pissed off. I listen to Rick Ross and I know Ricky Ross."</item>
		<item>"My b-tch aint got no tatts I hit her from the back. I spend south of France all that other sh-t is wack."</item>
		<item>"All you n-ggas copycats doing sh-t I used to, oh you tatted too, n-gga f-ck you!"</item>
		<item>"Cherry red Rover roof, crips to confuse you, you can say I blues you, better than I bruised you."</item>
		<item>"I know you aint scared of tigers. I get around, they say my sex on fire."</item>
		<item>"I do my best for you cause you my shorty so rest your head on my shoulders it feels good, dont it baby?"</item>
		<item>"Ima a niceguy but I never went to college."</item>
		<item>"Hard cash blood diamonds n-ggas violent babys crying."</item>
		<item>"Now you goofy. Im an asshole and my car dufus. Mikey rock chucks like the cool kids."</item>
		<item>"Tell em shut the f-ck up with that comotion. Im counting money get enough, get a promotion.Clm"</item>
		<item>"Lord please devour all my enemies, that was Pac talking B-tch now back up off me."</item>
		<item>"I aint never been cheap. I spend it all, never made Varsity but I f-cking ball."</item>
		<item>"Tyga psycho, dont play tyco, 50 tyson Ill bite you."</item>
		<item>"It killes me to know it, you Melanie Fiona. Ohhh, remove yourself from my scrotum."</item>
		<item>"They say Im bout to blow up like super nova put your helmet on, the bulldozing dopest."</item>
		<item>"Im Leonardo in Inception, reserve my section I do dreams put you in a bubble, benz or Lexus."</item>
		<item>"I ain't a killer but don't push me."</item>
		<item>"Snapbacks back!"</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
