<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"I'm going to pretend this never happened."</item>
		<item>"The world should hear my story."</item>
		<item>"Bump dat Lil Boosie all day. And I play dat UNK Beatin down yo block. And I stay bumpin dat Young Jeezy all da time."</item>
		<item>"I don't respond to skepticism because they not gonna be skeptical for long. My life right now is like a TV show; you watch every day to see a new episode. They waiting to see what I'mma do next."</item>
		<item>"The Internet had been a BIG help with my career. My advice to musicians Internet is the key. It gets your music heard all across the world."</item>
		<item>"Watch me lean and watch me rock, Super man dat hoe, then watch me crank dat robocop."</item>
		<item>"I mean, is the guy in the $5,000 necklace going to care about slavery? COME ON!"</item>
		<item>"To have 50 have my back, that's definitely exciting, it's an achievement."</item>
		<item>"Wait wait wait. He isn't glad he's here because he has a successful career, or lives in the 'land of the free', or anything, but because he has 'ice and tattoos'8 ? Go slave trade!"</item>
		<item>"So when the slaves got back from the fields, they was too tired to revolt against they masters. So what we're sayin' now is: Yo, we got some hats now, muh-f***as."</item>
		<item>"He makes me so glad that music is not nearly as lucrative as it once was."</item>
		<item>"It's in a safe deposit bank in Soulja Bank over in Japan that you never heard of."</item>
		<item>"I definitely look at it like that, I know I opened a lot of doors but there's other people that opened a lot of doors that don't get the respect that they need."</item>
		<item>"My flow sicker, your dough thick, well my dough thicker you talk sh-t. I will kick your door n-gga."</item>
		<item>"A big part of my success came from the internet scene, the MySpace, the YouTube, all that."</item>
		<item>"Wow. Between this and the Segway shit (Which I had not seen), I guess I'm officially a hater now."</item>
		<item>"I thought that he was taking shots at me, when it was just jokes. It was a misunderstanding, a mis-communication ... I'm about making money."</item>
		<item>"That was really to strike that emotion, to tell that story."</item>
		<item>"A big part of my success came from the internet scene, the MySpace, the YouTube, all that."</item>
		<item>"Ain't got time for chitchat I'm tryin to get this money, So get up out my face You shit-breath dummy."</item>
		<item>"Skeet Skeet Skeeted on that hoe yea boy, I make it rain, Shawty dont do me, I don't play no games."</item>
		<item>"I can't wait for the 'Shout out to the slave masters!' dance."</item>
		<item>"See, back in the day when there were slaves and stuff, we was forced to work in the hot sun all day, hatless. I mean, not even a babushka."</item>
		<item>"Word. Heads totally exposed to the sun."</item>
		<item>"The most bitch ass, flaugin ass so called rapper to ever touch da mic."</item>
		<item>"A person who makes song in 15 minutes and thinks it's cool."</item>
		<item>"A person who can't understand that such songs are shitty."</item>
		<item>"An undercover agent sent by goverment to kill hip hop."</item>
		<item>"All the girls that wrote comments on this page are desperate as hell. ps, this doesn`t apply to the girls who posted that are not desperate."</item>
		<item>"All yall be stupid cuz yall think he reads these comments but he dont really read em."</item>
		<item>"Yall just have to see if he would read all of this that we are wrighting on here so u yall have to shut up okii!"</item>
		<item>"Yall dont get mad at these girls cuzzzzz they aint do nothing to yall for a matter of a fact they are just trying to tell himm that they love him."</item>
		<item>"Watch me crank and watch me roll, watch me crank dat soulja boy then superman that hoe, now watch me."</item>
		<item>"A person with large number of fans (See Soulja Boy's fans for exact definition) who just like to dance, and that's all they do."</item>
		<item>"Person who cannot see well, and thus buys clothes bigger than himself."</item>
		<item>"A person who thinks yelling words such as 'yaaaah! 'oooooh' 'meeeeee' and 'boooooooo' are hard work."</item>
		<item>"Well before I was rapping. I was just a regular kid in school. I just liked to chill my friends and play games and stuff like that. One day at school my friends were freestyling at the lunch table and thats where it all started."</item>
		<item>"I won't sign a deal until they offer me what Im really worth."</item>
		<item>"Cop the true religion tee and threw 300 in the sky. Polo shoes on my feet."</item>
		<item>"My pants are saggin, looking so pretty. You wouldve thought I was a faggot."</item>
		<item>"Soulja Boy Ill bust your brain a n-gga talking all that sh-t, yall n-ggas cannot represent."</item>
		<item>"Im on another level, b-tch you heard me say that do you SOD I never mentioned you cause you not worthy."</item>
		<item>"Choppers on me, n-ggas we dont give a f-ck Im in the club, n-gga f-ck your mean mugs."</item>
		<item>"Any f-cking game n-gga pass me the ball and watch a n-gga ball, Im Gucci to the draws."</item>
		<item>"Im money over all, I dont really give a f-ck, Im money over all, I dont really give a f-ck."</item>
		<item>"Man, thats why I pick you up off the ground, if you make a f-cking sound disrespect my f-cking crew b-tch is you f-cking clown."</item>
		<item>"Let it be known I got rappers on my hit list, I got so many gifts you would swear I stole Christmas!"</item>
		<item>"SOD simpset bitch I know you've heard of me. I stay off in the hood, boy I post up 'bout 30 deep."</item>
		<item>"The money out the roof, I'm drop top bentley coupe. Soulja gots the juice, bitch nigga I thought you knew."</item>
		<item>"Drop top chevy, that's some shit you've never seen. Flexin so hard like I'm on a magazine."</item>
		<item>"Soulja got the juice. Throwin money out the roof."</item>
		<item>"Boy I got the juice, birds in the coupe. Flexin in my hood, throwin money out the roof."</item>
		<item>"I'm in that Zan with that Lean, Smoke nuthin but Irene. Them hoes going crazy when I'm on the scene."</item>
		<item>"Racks on the way busting out them jeans. I keep the head of my army, I ain't worried bout a thing."</item>
		<item>"I got all these bandz on me, all this ice on me, all these hoes on me. Everything on me."</item>
		<item>"Bentley on them 4's got me shittin on they ass. When I step inside the club wit them mutha fuckin zans."</item>
		<item>"Boy beat this case, now we got them racks. Now you got them hoes, now you got them tats."</item>
		<item>"Girls on my dick when I pretty boy swag, girls scream my name when I pretty boy swag."</item>
		<item>"Ain't got time for chitchat I'm tryin to get this money, So get up out my face You shit-breath dummy."</item>
		<item>"Toot that thang up Mami make it roll Once you pop pop lock it for me girl get low If ya Moma gave it to ya babygurl let is show Once you pop lock drop it for me maybe we can roll. (oh!!!)"</item>
		<item>"The Internet had been a BIG help with my career. My advice to musicians Internet is the key. It gets your music heard all across the world."</item>
		<item>"I don't respond to skepticism because they not gonna be skeptical for long. My life right now is like a TV show; you watch every day to see a new episode. They waiting to see what I'mma do next."</item>
		<item>"He makes me so glad that music is not nearly as lucrative as it once was."</item>
		<item>"I mean, is the guy in the $5,000 necklace going to care about slavery? COME ON!"</item>
		<item>"See, back in the day when there were slaves and stuff, we was forced to work in the hot sun all day, hatless. I mean, not even a babushka."</item>
		<item>"The most bitch ass, flaugin ass so called rapper to ever touch da mic."</item>
		<item>"A person which reportedly has lack of brain cells, as seen in his songs that lack good lyrics."</item>
		<item>"All yall be stupid cuz yall think he reads these comments but he dont really read em."</item>
		<item>"All the girls that wrote comments on this page are desperate as hell. ps, this doesn`t apply to the girls who posted that are not desperate."</item>
		<item>"If my last tweet offended you I won, Bowwow... f**k bank accounts. f**k followers. let's see who new album sell the most 1st week."</item>
		
	</string-array>
</resources>
