<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed."</item>
		<item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes you just gotta let shit go and say to "hell with it" and move on."</item>
		<item>"These times are so hard, and their getting even harder."</item>
		<item>"Don’t do drugs, don’t have unprotected sex, don’t be violent. Leave that to me."</item>
		<item>"To the people I forgot, you weren't on my mind for some reason and you probably don't deserve any thanks anyway."</item>
		<item>"I am whatever you say I am; if I wasn't, then why would you say I am."</item>
		<item>"Holy Gigantical Completely Natural Bulges!!!"</item>
		<item>"When I say I'll murder my baby's mother, maybe I wanted to, but I didn't. Anybody who takes it literally is ten times sicker than I am."</item>
		<item>"I think my first album opened a lot of doors for me to push the freedom of speech to the limit."</item>
		<item>"I felt like it's my time to shine, I have to rip this. At that time, I felt that it was a life or death situation."</item>
		<item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, \"Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this\"."</item>
		<item>"I don't hate women - they just sometimes make me mad."</item>
		<item>"I'm stupid, I'm ugly, I'm dumb, I smell. Did I mention I'm stupid?"</item>
		<item>"I might talk about killing people, but that doesn't mean I do it."</item>
		<item>"It's funny how all the magazines can dwell on my race, but they could never say that my shit is whack because they know my shit is tight!"</item>
		<item>"I try not to look at it that way. Being white. I don't wake up every day and look in the mirror, \"Oh. I'm white\"."</item>
		<item>"They say music can alter moves and talk to you. Well can it load a gun up for you and cock it too? WIll if it can and the next time you assault a dude, just tell the judge it was my fault...and I'll get sued!"</item>
		<item>"Anybody with a sense of humor is going to put on my album and laugh from beginning to end."</item>
		<item>"If there's not drama and negativity in my life, all my songs will be really wack and boring or something."</item>
		<item>"It'd be stupid for me to sit here and say that there aren't kids who took up to me, but my responsibility is not to them. I'm not a baby sitter."</item>
		<item>"My family has never been there for me. They expect things because we’re blood."</item>
		<item>"Will Smith don't got to cuss in his raps to sell records - well I do, so fuck him and fuck you too."</item>
		<item>"Whoever likes my stuff, likes my stuff. But just know Slim Shady is hip."</item>
		<item>"We just kept moving back and forth because my mother never had a job. We kept getting kicked out of every house we were in. I believe six months was the longest we ever lived in a house."</item>
		<item>"My father? I never knew him. Never even seen a picture of him."</item>
		<item>"It doesn't exactly feel like a shock, but it's all new to me, and I'm taking it in as it comes."</item>
		<item>"Who's Tony Blair, did he get his dick sucked?, oh he ain't shit then..."</item>
		<item>"Why is it so hard for people to believe that white people are poor?! I wouldn't say I lived in a ghetto, I'd say I lived in the 'hood. The same friends I had back then are the same people on tour with me now."</item>
		<item>"I took a lot of them, I took a bunch of pain killers."</item>
		<item>"At this point, I'm like Come up with something new. I hate the same old questions. But it seems like white magazines such as Spin and Rolling Stone focus on my whiteness more than Black magazines."</item>
		<item>"Look. I was pissed off! That's all I could say. I really felt that I wanted to do that shit. At one point in time, I really wanted to do that shit. For real."</item>
		<item>"Sucess is my only motherfucking option, failure's not."</item>
		<item>"All my life I've been dealing with my race because of where I grew up [Detroit] and being in the rap game. I'm at a boiling point...Anybody who pulls the race card is getting it right back in their face."</item>
		<item>"Unless you want to fuck me, why do you care what I look like?"</item>
		<item>"Somewhere deep down there's a decent man in me, he just can't be found."</item>
		<item>"A lot of truth is said in jest."</item>
		<item>"I do promote violence and I don’t give a fuck."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I'm real cool, but sometimes I could be a real asshole. I think everyone is like that."</item>
		<item>"If you had one shot, one opportunity, to seize everything you ever wanted, one moment, would you capture it, or just let it slip?"</item>
		<item>"I act like sh*t don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
		<item>"To know I chose my own fate I drove through the fork in the road and went straight."</item>
		<item>"I suppose it’s old, partner, but the beat goes on."</item>
		<item>"The Real Slim Shady."</item>
		<item>"Some asshole kept throwing oranges and other fruit at me while I was onstage. Fucker had an arm like a major league pitcher..."</item>
		<item>"You can do anything you set your mind to, man."</item>
		<item>"Coz what you say is what you say. Sometimes what you mean is two different things, depending on your mood if it swings."</item>
		<item>"It has to happen. There's probably somebody right now. We'll probably see someone on MTV news sometime soon: 'Just signed."</item>
		<item>"I had this whole Slim Shady concept of being two different people, having two different sides of me. One of them I was trying to let go, and I looked at the mirror and smashed it. That was the whole intro of the Slim Shady EP. Slim Shady was coming to haunt me..."</item>
		<item>"I’m not alone in feeling the way I feel. I believe that a lot of people can relate to my bleep whether white, black, it doesn’t matter. Everybody has been through some bleep, whether it’s drastic or not so drastic. Everybody gets to the point of `I don’t give a bleep."</item>
		<item>"I mean I got jumped, fucked up shit happened to me a few times, but that happens to everybody. I don't think it has anything to do with color or any of that shit. It's just all a part of growing up."</item>
        <item>"If you had one shot, one oppurtunity to seize everything you ever wanted. One moment. Would you capture it or just let it slip?"</item>
        <item>"But what's this sh*t you said about you like to cut your wrists too?...I say that shit just clowning dog...c'mon - how f***ed up is you?"</item>
        <item>"You're the One."</item>
        <item>"have some songs that a lot of people like, ... I have some songs that only I like. This album is obviously for the \"lot\" of people."</item>
        <item>"You can do nothing if you set your mind to it man."</item>
        <item>"When I say I'm taking a break, I'm taking a break from my music to go in the studio and produce my other artists and put their albums out."</item>
        <item>"I grew up listening to 2 Live Crew and N.W.A. and I never went out and shot nobody."</item>
        <item>"Somethimes it feels like the world is on my shoulder, everyone is leaning on me. Sometimes it feels like the world is almost over, but when she comes back to me all changes."</item>
        <item>"I'm gonna give you the world, I'm gonna buy a diamond ring for you, I'm gonna sing for you...I'll do all the things to see your smile!!"</item>
        <item>"I need drama in my life to keep making music."</item>
        <item>"If there's not drama and negativity in my life, all my songs will be really wack and boring or something."</item>
        <item>"When you're a little kid, you don't see color, and the fact that my friends were black never crossed my mind. It never became an issue until I was a teenager and started trying to rap."</item>
        <item>"The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed."</item>
        <item>"A lot of truth is said in jest."</item>
        <item>"Anybody with a sense of humor is going to put on my album and laugh from beginning to end."</item>
        <item>"I am whatever you say I am; if I wasn't, then why would you say I am."</item>
        <item>"I always wished for this, but it's almost turning into more of a nightmare than a dream."</item>
        <item>"Fame hit me like a ton of bricks."</item>
        <item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
        <item>"Before I was famous, when I was just working in Gilbert's Lodge, everything was moving in slow motion."</item>
        <item>"These times are so hard, and they're getting even harder."</item>
        <item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, 'Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this'."</item>
        <item>"Somewhere deep down there's a decent man in me, he just can't be found."</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I feel like rap music is almost the key to stopping racism."</item>
        <item>"My thing is this; if I'm sick enough to think it, then I'm sick enough to say it."</item>
        <item>"My only scheme was to be a rapper."</item>
        <item>"My father? I never knew him. Never even seen a picture of him."</item>
        <item>"It'd be stupid for me to sit here and say that there aren't kids who took up to me, but my responsibility is not to them. I'm not a baby sitter."</item>
        <item>"It sometimes feels like a strange movie, you know, it's all so weird that sometimes I wonder if it is really happening."</item>
        <item>"I'm stupid, I'm ugly, I'm dumb, I smell. Did I mention I'm stupid?"</item>
        <item>"I'd go to, like, six different schools in one year. We were on welfare, and my mom never ever worked."</item>
        <item>"I was poor white trash, no glitter, no glamour, but I'm not ashamed of anything."</item>
        <item>"I want to solidify as an artist and show that as I grow as a person and make mistakes and learn from them, I'm going to grow artistically."</item>
        <item>"I think my first album opened a lot of doors for me to push the freedom of speech to the limit."</item>
        <item>"I say what I want to say and do what I want to do. There's no in between. People will either love you for it or hate you for it."</item>
        <item>"I might talk about killing people, but that doesn't mean I do it."</item>
        <item>"I don't hate women - they just sometimes make me mad."</item>
        <item>"I come from Detroit where it's rough and I'm not a smooth talker."</item>
        <item>"I am who I am and I say what I think. I'm not putting a face on for the record."</item>
        <item>"To the people I forgot, you weren't on my mind for some reason and you probably don't deserve any thanks anyway."</item>
        <item>"But you lied again. Now you get to watch her leave, out the window. Guess that's why they call it window pane"</item>
        <item>"You know, I don't know this about me or not, but I'm kind of a big deal"</item>
        <item>"Ain't nothin but a whole lot of suckin' goin' on in rap"</item>
        <item>"When I die, so does hip hop"</item>
        <item>"Tryin' to give me the finger is kinda like givin' the spider the web. I'm just gonna spin and try to use it to my advantage. I catch a fly in that bitch. You think you fly, you just food."</item>
        <item>"I'm so tired of this, I could blow. Fire in the hole"</item>
        <item>"I'm thankful for the talent in which God gave me and I'm thankful for the environment that he placed me."</item>
        <item>"Believe it or not, I thank my mom for how she raised me in a neighborhood daily to jump and chase me. It only made me what I am today"</item>
        <item>"See regardless of what anybody believes who hates me; you ain't gonna make or break me"</item>
        <item>"Try to strip me of my credibility and make me look fake, G you only gonna be in for a rude awakening"</item>
        <item>"Act like shit don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive"</item>
        <item>"But i know one fact: I'll be one tough act to follow."</item>
        <item>"Don't let them say you ain't beautiful. They can all get f***ed, just stay true to you."</item>
        <item>"You've got enemies? Good. That means you actually stood up for something in your life"</item>
        <item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned"</item>
        <item>"What you think, I'm doing this for me, so f--- the world"</item>
        <item>"And all those who look down on me I'm tearing down your balcony"</item>
        <item>"As long as the wrong feels right - it's like I'm in flight."</item>
        <item>"You don't get another chance. Life is no Nintendo game"</item>
        <item>"I think my first album opened a lot of doors for me to push the freedom of speech to the limit."</item>
        <item>"I don't like rap anyways, I`m just trying to get my porno career started"</item>
        <item>"Don't do drugs, don`t have unprotected sex, don't be violent. Leave that to me"</item>
        <item>"A lot of my rhymes are just to get chuckles out of people. Anybody with half a brain is going to be able to tell when I'm joking and when I'm serious"</item>
        <item>"I grew up listening to 2 Live Crew and N.W.A. and I never went out and shot nobody."</item>
        <item>"Anybody with a sense of humor is going to put on my album and laugh from beginning to end"</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I'm real cool, but sometimes I could be a real asshole. I think everyone is like that."</item>
        <item>"I try not to look at it that way; being white. I don't wake up every day and look in the mirror, Oh. I'm white"</item>
        <item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this"</item>
        <item>"I had nothing to lose, but something to gain"</item>
        <item>"All those who look down on me I'm tearing down your balcony."</item>
        <item>"It's a little too late to say that your sorry now, you kicked me when I was down. But what you say just don't hurt me no more. You get no love."</item>
        <item>"I'm alive again."</item>
        <item>"Get these cock suckers off stage, where the f--k is Kanye when you need him."</item>
        <item>"I am whatever you say I am; if I wasn't, then why would you say I am."</item>
        <item>"I act like sh*t don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
        <item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this."</item>
        <item>"I act like shit don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
        <item>"But i know one fact: I'll be one tough act to follow."</item>
        <item>"Don't let them say you ain't beautiful. They can all get f***ed, just stay true to you."</item>
        <item>"You've got enemies? Good. That means you actually stood up for something in your life."</item>
        <item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
        <item>"What you think, I'm doing this for me, so f--- the world."</item>
        <item>"And all those who look down on me I'm tearing down your balcony."</item>
        <item>"As long as the wrong feels right - it's like I'm in flight."</item>
        <item>"You don't get another chance. Life is no Nintendo game."</item>
        <item>"But you lied again. Now you get to watch her leave, out the window. Guess that's why they call it window pane."</item>
        <item>"You know, I don't know this about me or not, but I'm kind of a big deal."</item>
        <item>"Ain't nothin but a whole lot of suckin' goin' on in rap."</item>
        <item>"Tryin' to give me the finger is kinda like givin' the spider the web. I'm just gonna spin and try to use it to my advantage. I catch a fly in that bitch. You think you fly, you just food."</item>
        <item>"I'm so tired of this, I could blow. Fire in the hole."</item>
        <item>"I'm thankful for the talent in which God gave me and I'm thankful for the environment that he placed me."</item>
        <item>"Believe it or not, I thank my mom for how she raised me in a neighborhood daily to jump and chase me. It only made me what I am today."</item>
        <item>"See regardless of what anybody believes who hates me; you ain't gonna make or break me."</item>
        <item>"Try to strip me of my credibility and make me look fake, G you only gonna be in for a rude awakening."</item>
        <item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this."</item>
        <item>"I act like shit don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
        <item>"But i know one fact: I'll be one tough act to follow."</item>
        <item>"Don't let them say you ain't beautiful. They can all get f***ed, just stay true to you."</item>
        <item>"You've got enemies? Good. That means you actually stood up for something in your life."</item>
        <item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
        <item>"What you think, I'm doing this for me, so f--- the world."</item>
        <item>"And all those who look down on me I'm tearing down your balcony."</item>
        <item>"As long as the wrong feels right - it's like I'm in flight."</item>
        <item>"You don't get another chance. Life is no Nintendo game."</item>
        <item>"But you lied again. Now you get to watch her leave, out the window. Guess that's why they call it window pane."</item>
        <item>"You know, I don't know this about me or not, but I'm kind of a big deal."</item>
        <item>"Ain't nothin but a whole lot of suckin' goin' on in rap."</item>
        <item>"Tryin' to give me the finger is kinda like givin' the spider the web. I'm just gonna spin and try to use it to my advantage. I catch a fly in that bitch. You think you fly, you just food."</item>
        <item>"I'm so tired of this, I could blow. Fire in the hole."</item>
        <item>"I'm thankful for the talent in which God gave me and I'm thankful for the environment that he placed me."</item>
        <item>"See regardless of what anybody believes who hates me; you ain't gonna make or break me."</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I'm real cool, but sometimes I could be a real asshole. I think everyone is like that."</item>
        <item>"I try not to look at it that way; being white. I don't wake up every day and look in the mirror, Oh. I'm white"</item>
        <item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this."</item>
        <item>"I act like shit don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
        <item>"You've got enemies? Good. That means you actually stood up for something in your life."</item>
        <item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
        <item>"And all those who look down on me I'm tearing down your balcony."</item>
        <item>"As long as the wrong feels right - it's like I'm in flight."</item>
        <item>"You don't get another chance. Life is no Nintendo game."</item>
        <item>"But you lied again. Now you get to watch her leave, out the window. Guess that's why they call it window pane."</item>
        <item>"You know, I don't know this about me or not, but I'm kind of a big deal."</item>
        <item>"Ain't nothin but a whole lot of suckin' goin' on in rap."</item>
        <item>"Tryin' to give me the finger is kinda like givin' the spider the web. I'm just gonna spin and try to use it to my advantage. I catch a fly in that bitch. You think you fly, you just food."</item>
        <item>"I'm so tired of this, I could blow. Fire in the hole."</item>
        <item>"I'm thankful for the talent in which God gave me and I'm thankful for the environment that he placed me."</item>
        <item>"See regardless of what anybody believes who hates me; you ain't gonna make or break me."</item>
        <item>"I act like sh*t don`t phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
        <item>"I had nothing to lose, but something to gain."</item>
        <item>"I don't like rap anyways, I`m just trying to get my porno career started."</item>
        <item>"Don't do drugs, don`t have unprotected sex, don't be violent. Leave that to me."</item>
        <item>"A lot of my rhymes are just to get chuckles out of people. Anybody with half a brain is going to be able to tell when I'm joking and when I'm serious."</item>
        <item>"Never take ecstasy, beer, baccardi, weed, pepto bismol, vivarin, tums, tagamet hb, xanax, and valium in the same day. It makes it difficult to sleep at night."</item>
        <item>"Anybody with a sense of humor is going to put on my album and laugh from beginning to end."</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I'm real cool, but sometimes I could be a real asshole. I think everyone is like that."</item>
        <item>"I get a hard dick from this shit, now I stick it in."</item>
        <item>"When you're so good that you can't say it cuz it ain't even cool for you to sound cocky anymore."</item>
        <item>"I hope you can't sleep and you dream about it and when you dream I hope you can't sleep and you scream about it. I hope your conscience eats at you and you can't breathe without me."</item>
        <item>"I shoot for the moon but I'm too busy gazing at stars, I feel amazing."</item>
        <item>"I feel I'm strong enough to go to the club or the corner pub and lift the whole liquor counter up cause I'm raising the bar."</item>
        <item>"To all the people I've offended - yeah fuck you too! For everytime I reminisce - yo I miss my past. But I still don't give a fuck, y'all can KISS MY ASS."</item>
        <item>"I don't give a fuck if u don't like my shit cause I was high when I wrote this, so suck my dick."</item>
        <item>"When I say I'm a do something I do it, I don't give a damn what you think, I'm doing this for me."</item>
        <item>"You couldn't make the crowd throw up their hands if they swallowed their fingers."</item>
        <item>"I drank a fifth of vodka, dare me to drive?"</item>
        <item>"Slim shady - hotter then a set of twin babies. In a mercedes benz wit the windows up. When the temp goes up to the mid 80's."</item>
        <item>"See I'm a poet to some, a regular modern day Shakespeare. Jesus Christ the King of these Latter Day Saints here"</item>
        <item>"I say what I want to say and do what I want to do. Theres no in between. People will either love you for it or hate you for it."</item>
        
	</string-array>
</resources>
