<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed."</item>
		<item>"Dealing with backstabbers, there was one thing I learned. They're only powerful when you got your back turned."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes you just gotta let shit go and say to "hell with it" and move on."</item>
		<item>"These times are so hard, and their getting even harder."</item>
		<item>"Don’t do drugs, don’t have unprotected sex, don’t be violent. Leave that to me."</item>
		<item>"To the people I forgot, you weren't on my mind for some reason and you probably don't deserve any thanks anyway."</item>
		<item>"I am whatever you say I am; if I wasn't, then why would you say I am."</item>
		<item>"Holy Gigantical Completely Natural Bulges!!!"</item>
		<item>"When I say I'll murder my baby's mother, maybe I wanted to, but I didn't. Anybody who takes it literally is ten times sicker than I am."</item>
		<item>"I think my first album opened a lot of doors for me to push the freedom of speech to the limit."</item>
		<item>"I felt like it's my time to shine, I have to rip this. At that time, I felt that it was a life or death situation."</item>
		<item>"There was a while when I was feeling like, \"Damn, if I'd just been born black, I would not have to go through all this\"."</item>
		<item>"I don't hate women - they just sometimes make me mad."</item>
		<item>"I'm stupid, I'm ugly, I'm dumb, I smell. Did I mention I'm stupid?"</item>
		<item>"I might talk about killing people, but that doesn't mean I do it."</item>
		<item>"It's funny how all the magazines can dwell on my race, but they could never say that my shit is whack because they know my shit is tight!"</item>
		<item>"I try not to look at it that way. Being white. I don't wake up every day and look in the mirror, \"Oh. I'm white\"."</item>
		<item>"They say music can alter moves and talk to you. Well can it load a gun up for you and cock it too? WIll if it can and the next time you assault a dude, just tell the judge it was my fault...and I'll get sued!"</item>
		<item>"Anybody with a sense of humor is going to put on my album and laugh from beginning to end."</item>
		<item>"If there's not drama and negativity in my life, all my songs will be really wack and boring or something."</item>
		<item>"It'd be stupid for me to sit here and say that there aren't kids who took up to me, but my responsibility is not to them. I'm not a baby sitter."</item>
		<item>"My family has never been there for me. They expect things because we’re blood."</item>
		<item>"Will Smith don't got to cuss in his raps to sell records - well I do, so fuck him and fuck you too."</item>
		<item>"Whoever likes my stuff, likes my stuff. But just know Slim Shady is hip."</item>
		<item>"We just kept moving back and forth because my mother never had a job. We kept getting kicked out of every house we were in. I believe six months was the longest we ever lived in a house."</item>
		<item>"My father? I never knew him. Never even seen a picture of him."</item>
		<item>"It doesn't exactly feel like a shock, but it's all new to me, and I'm taking it in as it comes."</item>
		<item>"Who's Tony Blair, did he get his dick sucked?, oh he ain't shit then..."</item>
		<item>"Why is it so hard for people to believe that white people are poor?! I wouldn't say I lived in a ghetto, I'd say I lived in the 'hood. The same friends I had back then are the same people on tour with me now."</item>
		<item>"I took a lot of them, I took a bunch of pain killers."</item>
		<item>"At this point, I'm like Come up with something new. I hate the same old questions. But it seems like white magazines such as Spin and Rolling Stone focus on my whiteness more than Black magazines."</item>
		<item>"Look. I was pissed off! That's all I could say. I really felt that I wanted to do that shit. At one point in time, I really wanted to do that shit. For real."</item>
		<item>"Sucess is my only motherfucking option, failure's not."</item>
		<item>"All my life I've been dealing with my race because of where I grew up [Detroit] and being in the rap game. I'm at a boiling point...Anybody who pulls the race card is getting it right back in their face."</item>
		<item>"Unless you want to fuck me, why do you care what I look like?"</item>
		<item>"Somewhere deep down there's a decent man in me, he just can't be found."</item>
		<item>"A lot of truth is said in jest."</item>
		<item>"I do promote violence and I don’t give a fuck."</item>
		<item>"Sometimes I'm real cool, but sometimes I could be a real asshole. I think everyone is like that."</item>
		<item>"If you had one shot, one opportunity, to seize everything you ever wanted, one moment, would you capture it, or just let it slip?"</item>
		<item>"I act like sh*t don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy, my insecurities could eat me alive."</item>
		<item>"To know I chose my own fate I drove through the fork in the road and went straight."</item>
		<item>"I suppose it’s old, partner, but the beat goes on."</item>
		<item>"The Real Slim Shady."</item>
		<item>"Some asshole kept throwing oranges and other fruit at me while I was onstage. Fucker had an arm like a major league pitcher..."</item>
		<item>"You can do anything you set your mind to, man."</item>
		<item>"Coz what you say is what you say. Sometimes what you mean is two different things, depending on your mood if it swings."</item>
		<item>"It has to happen. There's probably somebody right now. We'll probably see someone on MTV news sometime soon: 'Just signed."</item>
		<item>"I had this whole Slim Shady concept of being two different people, having two different sides of me. One of them I was trying to let go, and I looked at the mirror and smashed it. That was the whole intro of the Slim Shady EP. Slim Shady was coming to haunt me..."</item>
		<item>"I’m not alone in feeling the way I feel. I believe that a lot of people can relate to my bleep whether white, black, it doesn’t matter. Everybody has been through some bleep, whether it’s drastic or not so drastic. Everybody gets to the point of `I don’t give a bleep."</item>
		<item>"I mean I got jumped, fucked up shit happened to me a few times, but that happens to everybody. I don't think it has anything to do with color or any of that shit. It's just all a part of growing up."</item>
        <item>"If you had one shot, one oppurtunity to seize everything you ever wanted. One moment. Would you capture it or just let it slip?"</item>
        <item>"But what's this sh*t you said about you like to cut your wrists too?...I say that shit just clowning dog...c'mon - how f***ed up is you?"</item>
        <item>"You're the One."</item>
        <item>"have some songs that a lot of people like, ... I have some songs that only I like. This album is obviously for the \"lot\" of people."</item>
        <item>"You can do nothing if you set your mind to it man."</item>
        <item>"When I say I'm taking a break, I'm taking a break from my music to go in the studio and produce my other artists and put their albums out."</item>
        <item>"I grew up listening to 2 Live Crew and N.W.A. and I never went out and shot nobody."</item>
        <item>"Somethimes it feels like the world is on my shoulder, everyone is leaning on me. Sometimes it feels like the world is almost over, but when she comes back to me all changes."</item>
        <item>"I'm gonna give you the world, I'm gonna buy a diamond ring for you, I'm gonna sing for you...I'll do all the things to see your smile!!"</item>
        
	</string-array>
</resources>
