<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="facts">
	<item>"Ashanti's remix album came out in April 2004."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti says that she is a fan of reggae music."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti ranked at #13 on the Maxim Hot 100 List of 2005."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti: I need, like, 12 (kids)... I love kids. I definitely want to get married... I'm so family oriented. I want the big wedding, I want the long marriage, I want kids. (But) I've got to stack my cheese a little bit more... I want to be able to bring my kids into the world nice and comfortable."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti has had three singles, Foolish, Always On Time, and What's Luv in the top 10 in one week."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's hit song Foolish samples Stay With Me by DeBarge. Hip hop fans will remember this same sample used in the video and radio version of the late Notorious B.I.G.'s One More Chance."</item>
	<item>"She played the role of Dorothy in the 2005 TV movie The Muppet's Wizard of Oz."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti released her own fragrance line \"Precious Jewel\" in 2005."</item>
	<item>"Mary J. Blige, Ella Fitzgerald, and Blue Magic are musical artists whom inspired Ashanti."</item>
	<item>"When she was six, Ashanti sang in a gospel choir, but her mother discovered her full singing potential when she overheard Ashanti singing Mary J. Blige's \"Reminisce\" at age 12."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti embraces her new role as an inspiration for abused woman. She says that she has gotten letters from female fans saying that she saved them and helped them walk away from abusive relationships, all because of her music and videos."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti plays Heather in the 2006 movie John Tucker Must Die. She said that she based her character on Stacy Dash's role on \"Clueless\"."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti went to Bernice Johnson Cultural Arts Center, where she studied different dance styles, including tap, jazz, ballet, African, modern, and hip hop."</item>
	<item>"She was born on October 13, 1980 in Glen Cove, New York."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti launched her career in 1994 when she was recognized at a talent show."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti stands at 5'3\"."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's nickname is Five-O."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti: You know how some guys smell like old clothes, like they've been in a hamper? They wanna hug up all on you, smelling like they've been playing ball all day. That doesn't work."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti released a book called Ashanti Style, which showcases her style, in fall 2007."</item>
	<item>"Her mother, Tina Douglas, is a former dance teacher, and her father, Ken-Kaide Thomas Douglas, is a former singer."</item>
	<item>"Her mother named her after the Ashanti Empire in Ghana. In this nation, women had power and influence, and Ashanti's mother wanted her daughter to follow that model."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti likes the band Maroon 5."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's aunt lives in Rhode Island."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's father Ken-kaide is half African-American, half Chinese, and her mother Tina is African-American."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti has her own clothing line called Delicious Curves."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti wrote all 12 of her tracks on her self titled debut album."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti was ranked #37 in Maxim 's Hot 100 Women 2008."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti: (on how she lost weight for promotional appearances in 2007) I did the lemon-pepper-maple syrup diet for seven days. When I got really hungry, I ate fruit. I lost eight pounds and kept it off."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti holds a track record for her old high school."</item>
	<item>"She was ranked at #63 on VH1's list of the 100 Hottest Hotties."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's full name is Ashanti Shequoiya Douglas."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti stared as Nurse Betty in 2007's Resident Evil: Extinction."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti is hoping to appeal to \"gangstas and thugs\"."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti sold more copies of her debut album than any other female artist debut in history."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti had a role in the movie Malcolm X with Denzel Washington."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti appeared in Ain't It Funny video with Jennifer Lopez and Ja Rule."</item>
	<item>"She also performed at the 1994 Caribbean Awards and dancing with Judith Jamison of the Alvin Ailey Dance Company."</item>
	<item>"She ranked #81 in FHM's ""100 Sexiest Women in the World 2005""."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti: Find something you love, and do it well!"</item>
	<item>"The rap remix to her song Rain On Me contains interpolations of Can I Live? by Jay-Z. It also contains the same sample used by Jay-Z, which is Isaac Hayes The Look Of Love."</item>
	<item>"Before joining Murder Inc., Ashanti was signed to Jive Records."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti's name is actually the name of an African Tribe."</item>
	<item>"The rap verse by Notorious B.I.G. on Ashanti's song Foolish is the same first verse from Notorious B.I.G.'s F---ing You Tonight."</item>
	<item>"Her grandfather, James, was a civil rights activist who associated with Martin Luther King, Jr. in the 1960s."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti turned down a track scholarship to Hampton University to pursue her singing career."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti is the first woman to simultaneously hold positions 1and 2 on the US singles chart."</item>
	<item>"She danced with the Senior Pro Ensemble at Carnegie Hall, the Apollo Theater, Brooklyn Academy of Music, Avery Fisher Hall, and the Black Spectrum Theater."</item>
	<item>"Her nickname is \"Bon Bon\" given to her by her family."</item>
	<item>"She has a younger sister named Kenashia."</item>
	<item>"Ashanti: When you think of hip hop, you think grungy, dirty like concrete. When you think of R'n'B, you think smooth, sensuous - like a rose."</item>

</string-array>
</resources>
