<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="facts">
		<item>"Miley Cyrus'  birth name was Destiny Hope Cyrus."</item>
		<item>"Her parents named her Destiny because they believed that she would accomplish great things."</item>
		<item>"She was later given the nickname \"Smiley\" because she smiled all the time, but as she grew older her family shortened it to \"Miley\"."</item>
		<item>"Miley officially changed her name to Miley Ray Cyrus on May 1, 2008. "</item>
		<item>"Miley Cyrus is an animal lover."</item>
		<item>"She has many pets that include, horses, dogs, cats, fish, and chickens."</item>
		<item>"Her dog's names are: Sofie, Roadie, Loco, Tex and Mate."</item>
		<item>"Charity In 2007 Miley Cyrus pledged to give the City of Hope $1 for every \"Hannah Montana\" concert ticket she sold. "</item>
		<item>"Miley also donated $1 million to the charity Youth Service America in 2008."</item>
		<item>"She taught her Hannah Montana co-star Emily Osment how to play the guitar and Emily taught her how to knit!"</item>
		<item>"Miley Cyrus suffers from hypoglycemia, a condition that results in a lower than normal amount of sugar in the blood. Miley keeps her hypoglycemia under control with her diet."</item>
		<item>"When she was very young, Miley used to go onto the stage after her father had performed, and she'd help collect the flowers and homemade bracelets that people threw at him. Then they would go and donate everything to a local hospital."</item>
		<item>"Miley wakes up at 5:00 a.m. every day and reads her Bible, then falls back to sleep. She calls it \"her time\"."</item>
		<item>"Miley was born left-handed, just like her father, Billy Ray Cyrus. He believes that lefties have to learn everything backwards in life, so he trained Miley to write with her right hand from a very early age."</item>
		<item>"To this day, she does use her right hand to write, but she is a lefty with everything else. She has joked that if anyone dislikes her handwriting, they should talk to her dad about it."</item>
		<item>"Goals: reading the entire Bible."</item>
		<item>"Goals: opening a school for children with disabilities"</item>
		<item>"Goals: paying her grandmother Mammie's bills"</item>
		<item>"Goals: visiting sick children in the hospital in each of the 50 states"</item>
		<item>"Goals: to one day produce her younger sister Noah's first record"</item>
		<item>"She celebrated her sixteenth birthday party at Disneyland in California. The entire place was closed down on a weeknight, and each guest paid $250 to attend. All the money went to charity."</item>
		<item>"In April 2008, \"People Magazine\" reported that Miley earned a million dollars per week for her previous 17-week tour."</item>
		<item>"On April 22nd, 2008, it was announced that Miley signed a multi-million dollar deal with Disney-Hyperion Books to write her life story."</item>
		<item>"The red Valentino dress that Miley wore to the 2008 Academy Awards was said to have cost $10,550."</item>
		<item>"Miley first auditioned for \"Hannah Montana\" when she was 11, trying for the part of Lilly. She later tried out for the part of Hannah and was turned down for both parts because she was too young."</item>
		<item>"Miley's godmother is singer/actress Dolly Parton."</item>
		<item>"Miley's grandmother is the only person who still calls her by her birth name, Destiny."</item>
		<item>"Miley says that she looks up to former Disney teen queen Hilary Duff for staying true to herself and not being fake."</item>
		<item>"Miley says that Shania Twain is one of her favorite singers, because she is fun and not afraid to be different with her music."</item>
		<item>"She is a vegetarian, but doesn't eat anything green."</item>
		<item>"Her song \"I Miss You\" was written by Miley after her grandfather died. "</item>
		<item>"In 2007, it was reported that her father, who helps manage her career and finances, gave her a $300 dollar allowance per month."</item>
		<item>"She was on the green team for two years in a row in the \"Disney Channel Games\"."</item>
		<item>"She attended the \"Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix\" premiere with her dad. "</item>
		<item>"She says that she has three best friends. Her Mother, Tory Sparkman, and Emily Osment."</item>
		<item>"She broke up with her boyfriend in first grade because he was going to be in the talent show, and she thought if he really liked her, he should let her win. But he wouldn't!"</item>
		<item>"Miley was chosen as one of People Magazine's annual 100 Most Beautiful People in the World, in May 2007."</item>
		<item>"Won: Outstanding Female Lead in a Comedy Series (Child or Adolescent) at the 2008 Gracie Allen Awards."</item>
		<item>"Won: \"Choice TV Actress in a Comedy\" at the 2007 Teen Choice Awards."</item>
		<item>"Won: \"Favorite TV Actress\" at the 2007 Kid's Choice Awards, but she was unable to make it to the event."</item>
		<item>"Won: \"Favorite TV Actress\" at the 2008 Kid's Choice Awards."</item>
		<item>"Won: \"Favorite Female Singer\" at the 2008 Kid's Choice Awards."</item>
		<item>"The furthest she has ever been from her home is Paris, France."</item>
		<item>"Someday she would like to sing with Kelly Clarkson."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Clothing Store: Nordstrom and Hollister"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Song: \"Beating Heart Baby\" by Head Automatica"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Scent: Vanilla"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Crayon: Tickle Me Pink"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Flower: Lavender"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Candy: Starburst, Gummy Bears, Peach Rings and Dots"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Breakfast Food: Lucky Charms or a bowl of oatmeal with two scoops of ice cream"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Novel: \"Don't Die My Love\" by Lurlene McDaniel"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Snack: Cookie Dough and Cashews"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Condiment: Ketchup"</item>
		<item>"Favorite TV Show: \"Laguna Beach\" and \"The Suite Life of Zack and Cody\"."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Cookie: Sugar Cookie"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Movie: Steel Magnolia's"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Album: \"Breakaway\" by Kelly Clarkson"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Animal: Dog"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Sound: The Rain"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Time of Day: 1:00 A.M."</item>
		<item>"Favorite Season: Summer"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Food: Chinese"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Sport: Cheerleading"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Outdoor Activities: Running and Biking"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Singer: Hilary Duff, Kelly Clarkson and Ashlee Simpson"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Style of Music: Pop and Rock"</item>
		<item>"Favorite Color: Pink, Green and Purple"</item>
		<item>"She keeps a journal. "</item>
		<item>"Miley is afraid of spiders. "</item>
		<item>"She spends rainy afternoons watching sappy chick flicks with her sister."</item>
		<item>"Miley is ticklish and has said in interviews that she absolutely hates being tickled. "</item>
		<item>"She attended the Cheetah Girls 2 premiere. "</item>
		<item>"Miley was surprised with a Daisy Rock guitar on stage at a music festival in Nashville when she was twelve, because she wanted to play guitar like her father."</item>
		<item>"When Miley has to perform in concerts she gets really nervous. She helps herself calm down by realizing that this is her dream, and it's what she really wants to do."</item>
		<item>"Miley helped Emily Osment learn to play guitar."</item>
		<item>"She attended the premiere of \"Hannah Montana/Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert Tour\"."</item>
		<item>"She is really bad at keeping secrets."</item>
		<item>"She says that her biggest splurge was on a Coach bag. "</item>
		<item>"Her hidden talent is her monkey voice. "</item>
		<item>"Her room has a garden theme and uses cream, turquoise, mint green and brown colors."</item>
		<item>"Her least favorite part of working with her dad is the car drive up to the studio."</item>
		<item>"She says that her most embarrassing moment was when she was trying out for her school's dance team. She was practicing in the hallway, but then she fell and ripped her denim skirt."</item>
		<item>"She started riding horses when she was only two years old."</item>
		<item>"She use to enjoy braiding the tails of the horses that live on her families ranch. In fact, that's what she misses the most about living in Tennessee."</item>
		<item>"She says Dylan and Cole Sprouse are like her brothers."</item>
		<item>"Her first CD, The \"Hannah Montana Soundtrack\", was released on October 24th, 2006 and before the year was out over two million copies had sold. "</item>
		<item>"She was voted MVP for leading her team to victory in the quiz show relay and the egg toss game during the \"Disney Channel Games\"."</item>
		<item>"She has a bad habit of biting her nails."</item>
		<item>"She said the first time she sang in a concert was when she went up on stage with her dad and sang \"Hound Dog\"."</item>
		<item>"She almost always wears a ring with the word "Love" inscribed on it. It was a gift from her father to mother, Tish."</item>
		<item>"She was the opening act for the band \"The Cheetah Girls\" during their 2006 concert tour."</item>
		<item>"She attended the Hollywood premiere for the DVD version of \"High School Musical\"."</item>
		<item>"She is a born-again Christian."</item>
		<item>"Her song, \"Pumpin' Up the Party Now\", was featured in a 2006 Disney Channel \"So Hot Summer\" commercial."</item>
		<item>"Her likeness was used to create the \"Jackson's Beach Treat Delivery\" for Disney Channel's website."</item>
		<item>"Her likeness (and her character likeness, Hannah Montana) was used to create the \"Rock Star Fashion Challenge\" for Disney Channel's website."</item>
		<item>"Miley's uncle works as her bodyguard. "</item>
		<item>"She admits that anything and everything makes her laugh."</item>
		<item>"She says that she wants to go to Italy someday. "</item>
		<item>"She says the person she admires most is her mother, Tish. "</item>
		<item>"She had to have braces put on her teeth in early 2006, but because the dentist's was able to hide them by putting on the other side of her teeth, no one notices them. "</item>
		<item>"She will be singing at \"Radio Disney's Totally 10 Birthday Concert\" in Anaheim, Ca on July 22nd."</item>
		<item>"Since she no longer goes to regular school due to the hectic schedule for \"Hannah Montana\", she is tutored on the set. She is in the 9th grade and she says that the school subjects she likes the most are math and creative writing."</item>
		<item>"She has naturally curly brown hair."</item>
		<item>"She has pierced ears."</item>
		<item>"She was bitten by the acting bug on the set of her father's show \"Doc\"."</item>
		<item>"She had to leave almost all of her pets with her grandmother when she moved to Los Angeles. However, she was able to bring her dog, Loco with her."</item>
		<item>"Some of Miley's hobbies are dancing, cheerleading, singing, shopping, playing the guitar and writing music."</item>
		<item>"She has signed with Hollywood Records for a four-album record deal. Hollywood Records is also the recording label for Hilary Duff's music."</item>
		<item>"She has already written over 100 songs, some featured in the new show \"Hannah Montana\"."</item>
		<item>"Has a younger brother named Braison Cyrus. "</item>
		<item>"Has an older half-brother named Trace Cyrus. "</item>
		<item>"Has an older half-brother on her father's side named Christopher Cody Cyrus. "</item>
		<item>"Has an older half-sister named Brandi Cyrus. "</item>
		<item>"She is 5 feet, 5 inches tall. "</item>
		<item>"She has blue eyes."</item>
		<item>"Music videos she has appeared in (as Hannah Montana): \"The Best of Both Worlds\", \"Who Said?\", \"This Is The Life\", \"Pumpin' Up The Party\"."</item>
		<item>"Music videos she has appeared in (as herself): \"Start All Over\", \"7 Things\" and \"Fly On The Wall\"."</item>
		<item>"The first song Miley ever wrote was about her love for Dream Street singer Jesse McCartney. She finally got to meet her long time crush when he made a guest appearance on \"Hannah Montana\"."</item>
		<item>"Has a younger sister named Noah Lindsey Cyrus. "</item>
		<item>"Her \"Hannah Montana\" co-star Emily Osment is a talented knitter and taught Miley how to knit while they were on the set."</item>
		<item>"Miley Ray Cyrus born Destiny Hope Cyrus on November 23, 1992."</item>

		
	</string-array>
</resources>
